Chapter 410: Snow Lion

Due to the dark clouds and heavy snowfall, visibility on the ice field was extremely low, and even though Han Li couldn't detect any clear spiritual power fluctuations with his spiritual sense, he could never be sure where there were any unforeseen hazards lurking in this alien environment.

The snowfall was gradually becoming heavier and heavier, and visibility certainly wasn't improving.

The azure spirit boat was flying through the air quite slowly at Han Li's behest, and the wings on either side of it were releasing a layer of azure light that enveloped the entire boat, as well as Han Li's duo.

Dense flurries of snow were falling upon the azure light barrier, only to be kept at bay, and the heavy snowfall didn't have much of an impact on the advancement of the spirit boat.

"This snowstorm is rather strange. My spirit eye ability is severely limited here. Can you see a bit further with your Illusory Ghost Eyes?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"I'm not able to see very far, either. On top of that, my spiritual sense is also being disrupted as well, and I'm only able to just barely detect things several kilometers away at most," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li nodded in response. As the snowfall became heavier and heavier, he also found his spiritual sense being severely limited, and his sensory range was also fluctuating in an inconsistent manner.

After flying for several dozen more kilometers, Han Li suddenly pointed in a certain direction down below as he said, "There seems to be something over there."

"It seems to be some type of palace," Lu Yuqing mused as she turned in that direction.

The rooftops of a series of pavilions and tall pagodas could just barely be made out deep within the snow.

"Let's go down and take a look," Han Li said, and the spirit boat swooped directly downward at his behest, arriving in front of the cluster of buildings.

Only after the spirit boat was stowed away and the two of them landed on the ground did they discover that the snow here wasn't as deep as they had imagined. It only just barely reached their ankles, and beneath their feet were solid stone slabs.

After taking a moment to inspect their surroundings, they began to trudge over the snow-covered plaza deeper into the cluster of buildings.

Standing directly in front of them was a red archway that was several dozen feet tall. It had only two pillars, and it wasn't particularly ostentatious. There was a thick layer of snow on top of the archway, and the characters inscribed on it were rather indistinct, making it impossible to tell what had been written.

Only after getting close to the archway did Han Li and Lu Yuqing notice that its pillars were riddled with runes, but the spiritual qi that they contained had already completely run out, indicating that they no longer served their original purpose.

The two of them didn't linger here for long, passing through the archway before arriving in front of a large palace with a resting hill roof.

From the outside, the palace appeared mostly intact, with only one half of its gate missing. The stone staircase in front of the entrance was under the eave, so no snow had fallen upon it. However, there was a deep black mark on its surface, as if someone had cleaved it in half with some type of weapon.

"I can understand the presence of runes on the pillars of the archway, but why are there runes on their stone steps as well?" Lu Yuqing asked with a perplexed expression.

"If I'm not mistaken, this area was mostly encompassed within a concealment array, and the archway, these stone steps, and some of the bricks on the plaza collectively served as the core of the array, but they've clearly been destroyed," Han Li mused.

"Are you saying someone came here before us?" Lu Yuqing asked in a quiet voice as she took an uneasy glance at her surroundings.

"The spiritual qi in the array here has already completely faded, so the array had to have been destroyed a very long time ago. I'm presuming someone came here during a previous occasion of the immortal manor's emergence before destroying the array and taking whatever treasures were in here," Han Li replied.

Lu Yuqing was quite relieved to hear this, but also a little disappointed that the treasures here were already gone, and she said, "In that case, let's keep going and not waste any more time here."

"There's no hurry. There should be many places like this in the immortal manor, and we could encounter the same type of array going forward. If we examine how the array here was set up, we'll be able to save a lot of time bypassing further arrays of a similar nature if we encounter any," Han Li said.

"You're right! Why didn't I think of that? You're much more experienced and thoughtful than I am, Brother Liu," Lu Yuqing said with a hint of admiration in her eyes.

Han Li merely smiled as he made his way up the stone steps, then strode into the palace through the semi-destroyed gates.

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing trailed along behind him in a cautious manner.

The palace was completely empty, and there were several holes in the roof that snow was falling through, but the snow dissipated on its own before it could land on the ground.

After emerging from the back door of the palace, Han Li and Lu Yuqing were greeted by the sight of several more palaces and a three-story pavilion. Just like the palace from before, there wasn't any clear damage, and everything inside had already been looted.

"Let's go."

Standing at the foot of the pavilion, Han Li summoned the azure spirit boat again, then called out to Lu Yuqing, and the two of them continued on their journey.

The snowfall up ahead was still quite dense and heavy, and the deeper they progressed into the ice field, the more clusters of buildings that they encountered. The largest one of them was over 10 times larger than the one they had first encountered, while the smaller ones were just individual pavilions and pagodas, and it seemed that was where the servants stayed.

However, all of them had already been looted, while the restrictions around them had been destroyed.

Han Li wasn't surprised by this at all, but Lu Yuqing was pouting in disappointment, seemingly quite dismayed.

Fortunately, their journey proved to be quite peaceful thus far, and they didn't encounter any other people or demon beasts.

The two of them continued deeper and deeper into the ice field, and the snowstorm was gradually becoming more and more ferocious, while their spiritual sense was also being more and more heavily restricted, to the point that even Han Li's spiritual sensory range had been cut down to only a few dozen kilometers.

After flying over a short snow-covered mountain range, Han Li spotted another cluster of buildings situated in a valley up ahead.

He alerted Lu Yuqing to this, then directed the spirit boat into the valley.

As they drew close to the valley, they saw a snow-covered stoned lion that was several dozen feet tall, standing to the left of the valley's entrance. There was another stone lion on the right, and it was also covered in snow, but this one was laying on its side.

After descending in front of valley, Han Li made his way over to the stone lion on the left before brushing away the snow on it to reveal a series of complex runes that were slightly different from the ones that he had seen earlier, but he could tell that they were roughly the same type of restriction.

"The restrictions here have already been destroyed, so it looks like we won't have to enter the valley," Lu Yuqing mused with a disappointed expression.

Han Li was just about to respond when his brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he grabbed onto Lu Yuqing's shoulder before hurtling back in retreat until his back hit the rock wall behind him.

All of a sudden, the stone lion that was laying on the right side of the valley's entrance abruptly sprung to life, springing up from the ground before sending a massive paw crashing down toward Han Li and Lu Yuqing with tremendous force.

A thick layer of snow fell off the stone lion's body, yet there was nothing under the snow aside from more snow, and it was as if it were a snow beast that had a body of ice and snow.

Only in the instant right before it reared up from the ground was Han Li able to detect that it wasn't just a lifeless stone lion as it seemed.

Han Li raised a fist, and a layer of azure light appeared over it as he threw a punch directly upward.

An azure fist projection tore through the wind and snow before clashing against the paw of the snow lion, and a resounding boom rang out as the paw exploded into a cloud of snowy mist upon contact with the fist projection.

Before Han Li had a chance to withdraw his fist, his brows furrowed slightly, and he could feel a burst of intense chill seeping into his fist, upon which a layer of white frost instantly appeared over his knuckles.

He hurriedly withdrew his fist in alarm, and in the meantime, a blue vortex was taking shape on the snow lion's raised front paw.

Bursts of fierce suction force were emanating out of the blue vortex, sucking in all of the surrounding snow.

As more and more snow surged into the vortex, the destroyed front paw of the snow lion was mostly healed in the blink of an eye.

"That's not a puppet or anything like that, Brother Liu, it's a frost beast that's unique to this immortal manor. If you don't shatter the frost core in its body, it'll be able to keep drawing upon the snow in the area indefinitely to heal its own wounds, making it near unkillable!" Lu Yuqing hurriedly said.

"Frost core? What's that?" Han Li asked while staring intently at the recovering frost beast.

"It's an extreme frost crystal that's nurtured in the body of the beast. It's a bit like a demon beast's demon core, and it's commonly found directly behind a snow beast's eyes," Lu Yuqing hurriedly replied.

Han Li' immediately focused his gaze on the blue eyes of the snow lion upon hearing this, following which an azure flying sword shot out of his sleeve, reaching the left eye of the snow lion in a flash.

The frost beast didn't appear to be very intelligent, and in the face of the oncoming flying sword, it swatted directly at it with its front paw, the same one that was still yet to make a full recovery.

The flying sword was very fast, but it wasn't imbued with much power. However, in the instant that it came into contact with the paw of the snow lion, a flurry of swordlight erupted forth in all directions like a blooming sword lotus flower, instantly destroying the entire leg connected to the snow lion's paw.

At the same time, a streak of azure sword qi shot straight through the snow lion's left eye, cleaving its head in half.

A sharp clang rang out as the tip of the flying sword pierced into the blue crystal that was around the size of a human head, but it was only able to penetrate around an inch into the crystal.

Traces of white light were surging over the crystal, and a flurry of snow instantly converged toward the snow lion's head.

Chapter 411: Familiar

Han Li naturally wasn't going to give the snow lion a chance to recover, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the flying sword that was embedded into the blue crystal, forming a net of golden lightning that instantly swallowed up the snow lion's entire head.

The flurries of snow that was converging toward the snow lion's head instantly exploded upon contact with the net of golden lightning, unable to reach the snow lion to facilitate its healing.

A resounding boom rang out as the frost core in the snow lion's head was reduced to powder by the eruption of golden lightning, and the snow lion instantly stiffened before collapsing to the ground, disintegrating into a pile of snow that fell away in all directions.

Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the azure flying sword instantly flew back up his sleeve as a streak of light.

"That was amazing, Brother Liu!" Lu Yuqing cheered as she clapped her hands together with glee, then hurriedly made her way over to the snow lion's remains before rummaging through the pile of snow.

Moments later, she stood up with a hint of disappointment on her face and sighed, "Your attack was too powerful, Brother Liu. The frost core was completely destroyed."

"Why do you want its frost core?" Han Li asked.

"The frost cores of these frost beasts contain immense glacial qi, but they're not of the yin-attribute. They're very much sought-after in the Black Wind Sea, and they can be sold for quite a bit of spirit stones in Black Wind City," Lu Yuqing explained.

Han Li merely nodded in response and didn't say anything as he made his way into the valley, then strode toward the cluster of buildings inside.

The mountain path in the valley was rather narrow, and the snow covering it was even thicker than what was outside the valley, easily reaching up to waist height. Hence, Han Li used a levitation technique to float above the snow as he strode into the valley.

Lu Yuqing did the same as she trailed along behind Han Li.

The two of them continued into the valley for a few more minutes without encountering any further frost beasts, and they arrived on a flat and level plaza.

Just like before, the snowstorms in all of the places where there were buildings were a bit less ferocious, and the snow on the ground also wouldn't be as deep.

The cluster of buildings in the valley was quite large, taking up virtually the entire valley, and it would've looked like a small town had it not been for the fact that all of the buildings were extremely grand and majestic.

Many of the pillars and eaves had profound runes inscribed upon them, but almost all of them had been destroyed as well, and the treasures in this place had naturally also already been looted.

It took Han Li and Liu Yuqing close to two hours to examine all of the buildings one by one, and they only discovered some destroyed treasures inside that were completely worthless.

After emerging from the final pavilion, Han Li cast his gaze into the distance to find that there was a translucent icy mountain face at the end of the valley.

At the foot of the mountain face was a cave that was several dozen feet tall, and it was impossible to tell how deep the cave ran.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing exchanged a glance with one another, then made their way to the end of the valley, arriving in front of the cave.

The two of them then peered into the cave to find that it was quite dim inside, but there was a speck of white light several thousand feet away, and that seemed to be where the cave ended.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he released his spiritual sense into the cave, and moments later, he shook his head before making his way into the cave.

Lu Yuqing was about to ask if he had detected anything, but with Han Li striding forward in silence, she could only follow along.

Only after entering the cave did Han Li discover that the walls on either side, the roof of the cave, and even the ground beneath his feet were all flat surfaces of hard, blue ice that were as smooth as mirrors.

It was very quiet inside the cave, and only the sound of Han Li and Lu Yuqing's footsteps could be heard ringing out within it.

Han Li wasn't walking very quickly, and he would occasionally stop and inspect his surroundings momentarily before continuing onward.

After this had happened three times, Lu Yuqing was finally unable to suppress her curiosity, and she asked, "Why do you keep stopping, Brother Liu? Have you discovered something?"

Instead of giving a response, Han Li merely shook his head, then continued with what he was doing in silence.

Lu Yuqing could only follow along with a puzzled expression.

Upon reaching the exact middle point of the cave, Han Li stopped once again.

He stood with his eyes closed for a while, then crouched down and pressed a palm against the ground. Blue light was flashing in his eyes, and he fell into deep thought.

Moments later, he said, "I can hear something down there."

Before Lu Yuqing had a chance to reply, Han Li abruptly thrust his palm downard, and a loud crack rang out, following which the ice beneath his palm was shattered, and a series of cracks spread outward in all directions like a system of cobwebs.

Han Li stood back up and took a few steps backward, following which the area that he had just pressed down on caved in to reveal an ovular hole that was around 10 feet in size.

The sound of blowing wind could be heard coming from the hole, and it seemed that there was a huge space in there.

Han Li immediately jumped into the hole, and Lu Yuqing didn't even get a chance to ask him what he had discovered before he was already out of sight.

Hence, she had no choice but to jump down as well.

The two of them fell through the hole one after another, and it was only a short fall before they landed on the ground.

Han Li could feel that the soil beneath his feet was a little damp and loamy, and he looked up to find a sheet of blue ice that was around three feet thick above his head.

Lu Yuqing looked around to find that they were standing in a pitch-black underground passageway, and she asked in a puzzled voice, "What is this place, Brother Liu? It feels a little strange here."

Han Li raised a finger to his lips in a quieting gesture as he said, "Stay quiet for now and come with me."

Lu Yuqing immediately fell silent and trailed long behind Han Li as he made his way down the passageway, which led downward on a gradual slope.

After descending for over 1,000 feet along the passageway, the two of them drew to a halt.

Faint rays of light were shining into the passageway from up ahead, and bursts of dull rumbling could also be heard ringing out in the distance.

The two of them exchanged a glance, then concealed their auras in unison before continuing onward.

Upon arriving at the end of the passageway, they discovered that the rumbling had grown even louder, and it was reverberating throughout the entire passageway.

Han Li strode over to the exit of the passageway to find himself standing atop a sheer cliff, beneath which was an enormous underground karst cave.

He cast his gaze toward the center of the cave to find that there was a battle taking place there between a pair of humanoid figures and several enormous frost beasts.

At the very center of the cave was a large white stone plaza that had been artificially carved out, upon which stood a palace, but it had been destroyed and reduced to rubble.

Han Li noticed that the attire worn by the two figures on the plaza was quite familiar. One of them was a tall and imposing middle-aged man dressed in a black robe with a skull design embroidered onto the collar, and he was clearly a Ghost Wail Sect cultivator.

The other figure was a short and wizened elderly man dressed in a black vest with a black bandana around his head, and he was a Southern Dawn being.

Prior to this, Han Li's attention had been focused entirely on the Golden Immortals of the two factions, so he hadn't paid any heed to the other Ghost Wail Sectand Southern Dawn Race cultivators. As a result, he had no recollection of these two.

Taking a closer look, Han Li discovered that despite the elderly man's small stature, his powers were quite formidable. He was wielding a huge golden halberd that was twice as tall as himself, and it resembled a giant golden fan as he swung it through the air.

He was facing a pair of snow lions that were both dozens of feet tall, and whenever they tried to lash out at the elderly man with their paws, they would be struck by the halberd, which would either inflict huge gashes or sever the paws entirely from their bodies.

As for the middle-aged man from the Ghost Wail Sect, he was completely unarmed and locked in battle against a pair of snow apes. White light was radiating from his fists, and there were specks of blue light shimmering within the white radiance.

With each punch that he threw, a resounding boom would ring out, and whatever part of the snow apes' bodies that came into contact with his fist would instantly explode into powder.

It seemed that the two of them held a decisive upper hand, but in reality, this was far from a favorable situation for them. The frost beasts seemed to be unable to feel any pain, and regardless of how severe their injuries were, they were always able to quickly make a full recovery, regenerating significantly faster than the snow lion that Han Li and Liu Yuqing had faced earlier.

What was most damning of all was that aside from these four frost beasts, there was also a snow dove that looked as if it had been carved out of ice standing atop the wreckage of the destroyed palace, and it was staring intently at the two cultivators.

It was clear that if either of the two of them were to display any signs of weakness or lapses in concentration, then the snow dove would instantly strike with lightning speed.

In contrast with the four other frost beasts, it was able to shoot arrow-like strands of silver ice out of its sharp beak, and the strands of ice were imbued with ice-attribute law powers, so the two cultivators had to be wary even with their True Immortal Stage cultivation bases.

After observing the ongoing battle and the cultivation arts being used by the two cultivators for some time, Han Li's brows furrowed ever-so-slightly, following which a hint of surprise and recognition appeared on his face.

Could it really be them?

Chapter 412: Let’s Follow Them

Right Han Li was lost in thought, the snow dove suddenly spread its wings before swooping down from above, gliding past the pair of snow apes in the blink of an eye before lashing out with its talons at the black-robed middle-aged man, who was still slightly off balance after throwing a punch.

The black-robed man was quite startled by this abrupt sneak attack, but he seemed to have quite a vast wealth of battle experience, and seven specks of blue light appeared over his chest and abdomen, immediately following which 11 more specks of blue light emerged over the rest of his body.

A layer of starry white light then surfaced over his entire body, just in time to protect him from the snow dove's talon strike.

The hideous sound of metal grating on metal rang out as the snow dove's talons scraped over the black-robed man's neck and shoulder, causing the layer of white light over his body to shudder, but it was ultimately able to remain intact.

After passing by the black-robed man, the snow dove suddenly twisted around and opened its beak to release a strand of silver ice, which shot forth directly toward the black-robed man's heart like a speeding arrow.

At this point, the black-robed man had already managed to withdraw his fist, and he immediately threw another punch toward the silver arrow as a ball of dazzling white light erupted out of his fist.

A resounding boom rang out as the silver arrow and the white light around the black-robed man's fist exploded in unison. A cloud of glacial qi immediately spread through the air, while a layer of blue ice crystals appeared over the black-robed man's right arm.

Before he had a chance to remove the layer of ice crystals, one of the snow apes that he had been locked in battle against barreled into him from the side, sending him flying through the air.

Another resounding boom rang out as the black-robed man crashed into a stone wall, and his entire body was embedded into it, while a series of cracks spread out over the wall around him in all directions.

However, the black-robed man was quickly able to pull his arm out of the wall, then slammed his fist into the wall to propel his own body forward, and it didn't appear as if he had suffered any injuries.

A displeased look appeared on the black-robed man's face as he yelled at his companion, "Fellow Daoist Xiong Shan, if you continue to insisting on holding back and refrain from displaying your full power, then I think it would be best for us to go our separate ways."

The elderly man was also quite disgruntled, and he countered, "What right do you have to criticize me? If you hadn't insisted on taking this detour, we wouldn't have fallen into this trap. Not only have we not managed to reap any rewards here, we've been forced to engage these frost beasts in this pointless battle."

"I only made a suggestion to come down here, and you raised no objections. There's always an inevitable element of risk when it comes to searching for treasures in a place like the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. There are only a few frost beasts here, so let's just take care of them and move on instead of wasting any more time here," the black-robed man argued.

"I said that we should focus on our primary objective, but you were determined to come down here, so what could I do but agree?" the elderly man grumbled.

The two cultivators in the cave were none other than Xiong Shan and Patriarch Cold Flame, both of whom Han Li was quite familiar with.

What was rather perplexing to Han Li was that one of them had clearly come here as part of the Ghost Wail Sect, while the other had concealed himself among the Southern Dawn beings, so how had they met up with one another?

Furthermore, not only had they appeared in the same place, judging from their conversation, it appeared that they were working together. Could it be that they had been acquaintances prior to entering the immortal manor.

Patriarch Cold Flame knew that he wasn't going to be able to win this argument, so he conceded, "Fine, I'll admit that I'm at fault on this occasion. If you insist on assigning blame, then once we get to that place and find what we're looking for, you can go first and pick out whichever item you want. For now, let's take care of these frost beasts and get out of here as soon as possible."

Xiong Shan didn't waste any more time with words upon hearing this, and with a flick of his wrist, he stowed the golden halberd away before making a hand seal.

Immediately thereafter, late-True Immortal Stage spiritual power fluctuations began to emanate from his body, and layers upon layers of golden sword projections appeared behind him like the unfurling train of a peacock, radiating dazzling golden light.

All of the golden sword projections then instantly shot forth at his behest, surging toward the pair of snow lion frost beasts before completely inundating them like a turbulent wave.

Loud clangs rang out in rapid succession within the wave of sword projections, and white and golden light flashed incessantly.

By the time all of the sword projections had swept through the air, the bodies of the pair of snow lions had been completely stripped away to reveal their frost cores, which were hovering in mid-air while absorbing the nearby snow and glacial qi.

Xiong Shan lunged forward with his golden longsword held in his grasp, instantly shattering the pair of frost cores with a single slash of his sword to put a complete end to the pair of snow lions.

Meanwhile, the snow dove circled around in mid-air before swooping toward him.

On the other side, all of Patriarch Cold Flame's profound acupoints were glowing with dazzling blue light as he took a stride forward, and starpower converged toward his fist as he threw a vicious punch toward an oncoming snow ape.

The snow ape retaliated with a punch of its own, and the two fists clashed with immense power.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of tremendous force erupted out of Patriarch Cold Flame's fist, culminating in a formidable shockwave that spread through the air in all directions.

The passageway that Han Li and Lu Yuqing were situated in wasn't very wide, and as the shockwave swept through it, Lu Yuqing involuntarily stumbled.

Thankfully, Han Li was right beside her, and before she had a chance to cry out in surprise, he grabbed onto her sleeve with one hand while clasping his other hand over her mouth. At the same time, a faint light barrier emerged to encompass both of them.

Only after the shockwaves had subsided did Han Li make a quieting gesture before slowly removing his hand from over Lu Yuqing's mouth.

Lu Yuqing pursed her lips tightly as she pressed herself against the stone wall of the passageway, not daring to make another sound.

Meanwhile, Han Li turned his attention back to Patriarch Cold Flame, and a contemplative look had appeared on his face.

In the wake of the clash, the snow ape's arm had already completely exploded, and there was a rapidly revolving blue vortex where its arm used to be, absorbing the nearby glacial qi in order to facilitate regeneration.

Patriarch Cold Flame naturally wasn't going to give it the chance to heal, and after evading an attack from the other snow ape, he sprang up into the air before stomping his foot heavily down onto the snow ape's head.

A layer of white starlight appeared on the underside of his foot, and a resounding boom rang out as the snow ape's head exploded under the tremendous force of his stomp.

A translucent frost core shot out of its head before being caught in Patriarch Cold Flame's grasp, and he quickly flipped his other hand over to produce a purple talisman that he adhered to the frost core, then hurriedly stowed it away into his storage ring.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang up into the air once again, charging toward the other snow ape.

Right at this moment, a sharp screeching sound rang out from up above, and an enormous streak of golden swordlight swept through the air. The snow dove was struck by the streak of golden swordlight, and its body was instantly torn in half down the middle.

The streak of golden swordlight continued onward, and the roof of the cave was unable to withstand its tremendous power as giant rocks the size of millstones came crashing down from above, opening up a massive rift that was several dozen feet wide.

A ray of natural light shone down through the rift in the roof of the cave, and gusts of fierce wind also blew in through the rift.

Xiong Shan stood atop the pile of fallen rocks as he slowly withdrew his longsword while casting his gaze toward Patriarch Cold Flame.

The battle over there had drawn to a conclusion as well. The second snow ape also proved to be no match for Patriarch Cold Flame's tremendous starpower, and its head had exploded into powder with a single punch along with the frost core inside.

"Let me remind you that the circumstances surrounding this emergence of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor are far more complex than on previous occasions, so we cannot afford to take any further detours from here onward," Xiong Shan said in a cold voice as Patriarch Cold Flame approached him.

"It was only discovered during the previous emergence of the immortal manor that the already explored area of the immortal manor is collectively known as the Light Frost Region. The Light Frost Region is only the outermost section of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and there's no telling what manners of treasures could be found deeper in the immortal manor.

“With that in mind, it's no wonder that the circumstances have become a lot more complicated," Patriarch Cold Flame sighed.

"We've only managed to sneak into the immortal manor on this occasion through the Transient Guild and the Ubiquitous Pavilion. Surely you don't need me to tell you how much of a risk we're taking here," Xiong Shan said with solemn expression.

"Of course I'm aware of that. However, there's no need to be overly concerned. That place is situated in a very secluded area, and all of the other people who discovered it with us back then have already perished, so there's no way anyone would find that place before we get there," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

Xiong Shan's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "In any case, let's get there as soon as possible, and after we've obtained what we want from that place, we can split up and go our separate ways."

"That's precisely my intention as well," Patriarch Cold Flame replied with a nod.

With that, the two of them didn't waste any more time as they rose up into the air, flying through the rift in the roof of the cave to emerge into the wind and snow outside.

"Let's follow them," Han Li said to Lu Yuqing, then flew out of the passageway, while Lu Yuqing hesitated momentarily before following along.

Chapter 413: Rumor

Lu Yuqing's cultivation base was far inferior to that of Han Li, Patriarch Cold Flame, and the others, so she was naturally struggling to keep up.

Han Li noticed this, and he raised a hand to summon his azure flying boat, then gestured for her to fly onboard.

Lu Yuqing offered him her gratitude, then flew onto the spirit boat, as did Han Li.

Immediately thereafter, he began to chant an incantation, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of heavy water, which transformed into a layer of black light that quickly spread over the boat to envelop it in its entirety.

Enshrouded within the black light barrier, all of the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the spirit boat instantly subsided, and it transformed into an undetectable shadow that wasn't giving off even the slightest aura.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this. This was a concealment ability that he had invented by combining his heavy water and the laws of water that he had gleaned, and it seemed that it was quite effective.

As the flying boat continued onward, it didn't take long before it caught up to Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan, but Han Li made sure to stay out of their spiritual sensory range, trailing along behind them from afar.

"Why are we following them, Brother Liu?" Lu Yuqing asked.

She didn't dare to release her spiritual sense earlier for fear of being detected, so she didn't hear the conversation between Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan.

"Judging from their earlier conversation, they seemed to have discovered an interesting place the last time the immortal manor was opened, and they're revisiting that place now. This is our first time in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so we don't know much about it at all, and this isn't one of the areas on your map, so as opposed to stumbling around without any direction, we may as well follow them," Han Li explained.

"It sounds like we're in luck. These two are quite formidable, but they're no match for you, Brother Liu. If they're going after some treasures, then we can just spring up on them at the last second and claim those treasures for ourselves!" Lu Yuqing said with a smile.

Han Li also smiled in response, then began to focus his attention on tracking Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan.

He wasn't concerned about Patriarch Cold Flame, but Xiong Shan possessed quite an advanced cultivation base and was also very cautious and alert, so he didn't dare to take him lightly.

Lu Yuqing could see that Han Li was trying to focus, so she fell silent in order to refrain from disturbing him, then sat down with her legs crossed on the spirit boat to meditate.

……

Meanwhile, elsewhere in the immortal manor.

There was a vast ice field that spread as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and aside from some small hills, there was only a lone snow-covered peak at the center of the ice field, extending all the way up into the clouds.

The area was very quiet aside from the sound of the occasional gusts of wind, and right at this moment, a semi-transparent white vortex emerged in front of the lone peak amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

The vortex then faded to reveal a green jade flying carriage that was around 100 feet in length.

The carriage was long and sleek, and there were intricate engravings on its surface, much like what one would expect to see on a jade scepter. Standing on the carriage was a tall man, and there were also a pair of halberd-wielding puppets clad in golden armor on the carriage.

The man's entire body was enshrouded within a layer of white light, giving him a rather hazy appearance, but one could still just barely make out his facial features.

As soon as he appeared, he swept his gaze over the surrounding area before setting his sights on a certain direction.

"It looks like I'm not too late," the man murmured to himself, following which the flying carriage beneath his feet shot forward as a ball of green light, vanishing into the distant sky shortly thereafter.

……

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan continued in their travels without pause, and three or four days flew by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, the vast ice field down below had been replaced by a mountainous region that was covered in a thick layer of glistening ice and snow, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

Occasionally, some clusters of palaces could be spotted among the snow-covered mountains, and some were even releasing hints of spiritual power fluctuations, indicating that they contained certain treasures.

However, Patriarch Cold Flame's duo didn't even bother to take a glance at any of these buildings as they continued to fly onward.

Han Li was rather intrigued and wanted to go down to take a look, but he had no opportunity to do so as he had to keep following the duo.

"Looks like they're going someplace very far away. I hope they won't disappoint us," Lu Yuqing sighed.

"Let's just wait and see," Han Li replied with a nod.

A few more days passed by in a flash, but even after flying for so long, they still didn't seem any closer to reaching the end of the Light Frost Region.

Han Li was quite taken aback to see this. He had thought that this was only an immortal manor, yet the Light Frost Region alone seemed to be comparable in size to the Black Wind Sea. With that in mind, the entirety of the immortal manor was most likely just as enormous as a small plane.

Patriarch Cold Flame showed no intention of stopping as they continued to fly onward, and a few more days passed by in the blink of an eye.

The snow-covered mountains below gradually faded away, and a boundless sea emerged up ahead.

The water in the sea was as black as inky and appeared to be extremely viscous, as evidenced by the fact that there weren't many waves sweeping over the surface of the sea despite the fierce wind.

The entire surface of the sea resembled an infinitely vast black mirror, presenting a rather unsettling sight to behold.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan flew directly onward without any hesitation, but Han Li stopped at the edge of the black sea with slightly furrowed brows.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had been flying without pause this entire time, and he couldn't help but wonder if they had perhaps already noticed him and Lu Yuqing and were intentionally leading them into a trap.

In this unfamiliar environment that was fraught with peril, he couldn't afford to get complacent.

He cast his gaze toward the black sea up ahead, then turned to Lu Yuqing as he asked, "Do you know anything about this black sea?"

"I'm afraid not, Brother Liu," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he fell into deep thought.

Lu Yuqing took a glance at her surroundings, then asked, "Should we keep following them, Brother Liu?"

At this point, she was also beginning to grow a little uneasy.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then replied, "It would be a waste to stop here after following them for so long. I want to see this through to the end."

With that, he made a hand seal and spurred the azure flying boat onward.

At this point, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had already vanished out of sight, but that wasn't a cause for concern as Han Li could still follow the spiritual power traces that they had left behind.

It didn't take long for Han Li to catch up to the duo, and close to two more days passed by in a flash.

Han Li was standing atop his flying boat with slightly furrowed brows. He didn't know just how vast this black sea was, but after flying for so long, he was certain that they were already quite deep in the area.

They had already been following Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan for close to 10 days. If they had spent that time searching for treasures on their own, they would've been sure to have reaped some spoils, yet they were still empty-handed right now, and they could only hope that the duo that they were following really was leading them to some exceptional treasures. Otherwise, the incurred opportunity cost would be quite significant.

All of a sudden, Han Li leaned forward slightly as if he had spotted something up ahead.

"What is it, Brother Liu?" Lu Yuqing asked.

As soon as her voice trailed off, clouds of white mist suddenly appeared over the sea up ahead.

Specks of white light were visible within the mist, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Wisps of bone-chilling glacial qi were emanating out of the white mist, significantly lowering the nearby air temperature.

A contemplative look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan stopped in their tracks, and they were ecstatic to see this white mist.

"We finally found it!" Patriarch Cold Flame exclaimed in an excited voice, and his elation was mirrored on Xiong Shan's face as well.

The two of them then inspected their surroundings momentarily to check if they were being followed.

At this point, Han Li's flying boat had also drawn to a halt, and his eyes instantly lit up as he heard the exchange between Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan.

It seemed that they had finally arrived at their destination.

As Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan began to scour their surroundings, Han Li hurriedly backtracked a little with his flying boat.

Thankfully, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan didn't notice anything amiss, and they quickly continued onward, flying into the mist at a far faster speed than before.

Han Li's azure flying boat also accelerated at his behest, and as soon as it flew into the white mist, it was instantly infiltrated by bursts of glacial qi.

This glacial qi was quite peculiar in that it resembled needles, making it extremely penetrative, able to pierce through the heavy water barrier, and a layer of frost was slowly beginning to appear on the surface of the flying boat.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a set of several dozen small blue flags that flew to the edges of the flying boat before vanishing into it.

A blue light barrier instantly emerged to envelop the flying boat, keeping the glacial qi at bay.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing suddenly sprang to her feet.

Han Li was slightly alarmed, and he immediately asked, "What's wrong?"

"Brother Liu, I just recalled a rumor about the Light Frost Region. It's said that there's a sea of mist in the region that contains extremely formidable glacial qi, and within the sea of mist lies the Light Frost Palace, the premier treasure trove of the entire region! However, no one has ever been able to find it. Could it be..."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

Thinking back to the excitement that Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had displayed while discussing their destination, it was very likely that their objective was indeed to reach this Light Frost Palace.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately spurred on his flying boat to accelerate a little further.

The more they advanced through this area, the denser the white mist became until visibility was virtually zero.

However, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan seemed to be very familiar with this place, and they were traversing through the mist without pause.

After flying for around three hours, the two of them abruptly drew to a halt.

Han Li had been keeping tabs on them this entire time, and he immediately stopped as well, concealing his flying boat in a cloud of white mist as he cast his gaze forward.

His eyes then instantly lit up as he spotted a black island situated in the sea up ahead. It was only a small island that was around 10 to 15 kilometers in size, and it was entirely enshrouded in a layer black light that looked as if it were formed by countless tiny black needles.

The black light was flowing like liquid, and beyond the black light barrier was the faint outline of a majestic palace.

Chapter 414: Exposed

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were observing the island down below with excitement in their eyes.

"It looks like no one's found this place yet," Patriarch Cold Flame remarked as he took a glance at his surroundings.

"That's only to be expected. This is an extremely secluded place, and I wouldn't have stumbled upon this island back then if I hadn't been frantically fleeing from that pack of frost beasts," Xiong Shan replied as he stared at the palace within the light barrier with fervent excitement in his eyes.

"You seem very confident, Fellow Daoist Xiong Shan. You must've made some extensive preparations for this trip," Patriarch Cold Flame chuckled.

"I bet you've done the same, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. You've most likely already completely mastered the Great Universe Origin Arts. I'm assuming you weren't going all-out against those frost beasts from earlier," Xiong Shan harrumphed coldly in response.

"How could my paltry powers possibly compare with yours?" Patriarch Cold Flame chuckled in a modest fashion.

The two of them exchanged a glance, and both of them fell silent as a slightly tense atmosphere began to set in.

"We still haven't entered the Light Frost Palace yet, so there's no need for the two of us to be praising one another like this. Besides, our objectives are different, so there are no conflicts of interest between us. Let's break this restriction as quickly as possible to avoid any unforeseen mishaps," Patriarch Cold Flame proposed.

"That sounds like a good plan," Xiong Shan replied with a smile, then patted the storage pouch strapped to his waist, and a small golden sword instantly emerged, followed immediately by an azure wooden ruler and a small blue flag.

All three treasures were giving off astonishing spiritual qi fluctuations, and they weren't far off from immortal treasures.

At the same time, Patriarch Cold Flame swept a sleeve through the air to release two bursts of light, one red and one yellow, and they were revealed to be a crimson bowl and a small yellow seal, both of which were also top-grade spirit treasures.

As soon as the five spirit treasures were summoned, they immediately flew high up into the sky as five dazzling balls of spiritual light before vanishing out of sight in a flash.

The sky up above shuddered as a vast expanse of radiant five-colored light emerged, encompassing the entire area within a radius of dozens of kilometers down below.

The five spirit treasures were visible deep within the five-colored light, and they had formed a circular array.

All of the world's origin qi in the space encompassed within the five-colored light became completely stagnant, as if it had been frozen in place by some type of invisible force.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he observed what was unfolding up ahead using his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

"What are they doing, Brother Liu?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"They're using spirit treasures of the five elements to unleash the Great Five-elemental True Light," Han Li replied.

As the two were conversing with one another, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had already begun chanting an incantation, upon which the five-colored light swirled momentarily before quickly transforming into a five-colored pillar of light that shone down upon the black light barrier.

The black light barrier instantly brightened, and countless threads of thin black light emerged one after another like streaks of black sword qi, then converged to form a black sword dragon that pounced at the pillar of five-colored light.

The two clashed, and the black sword dragon was able to keep the pillar of light at bay while tearing at it viciously with its claws, fangs, and tail.

Streaks of formidable black sword qi were erupting out of the sword dragon's claws and mouth, but the pillar of five-colored light remained stable and completely unmoved despite the sword dragon's best efforts.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan continued to chant their incantation while making hand seals, and five-colored spiritual light was rapidly revolving within the pillar of light, forming a series of five-colored balls.

Each ball was the size of a millstone, and all of them were semi-transparent. They were quite spectacular to behold, but also struck the beholder with a sense of awe and foreboding.

The five-colored spiritual light at the forefront of the pillar of light flashed momentarily, following which all of the balls of five-colored light shot forth, crashing into the black sword dragon's body.

The five-colored balls of light then exploded into a vast expanse of light that completely inundated the black sword, tearing it apart with ease amid an anguished howl.

Lu Yuqing's eyes widened with incredulity upon seeing this, while Han Li's expression remained unchanged, and it seemed that this was the anticipated outcome for him.

After vanquishing the sword dragon, the five-colored balls of light continued onward without pause to strike the black light barrier down below, which instantly began to warp and twist violently.

In the end, the black light barrier was only able to withstand the assault for a few seconds before it was torn apart and disintegrated into countless specks of black spiritual light.

However, an azure light barrier then emerged, and it seemed to be no less formidable than the black light barrier.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan didn't seem surprised at all to see this, and the five-colored pillar of light continued to descend while releasing more five-colored balls of light that surged toward the azure light barrier.

The five-colored light barrier brightened considerably while releasing gusts of fierce azure wind, and a string of earth-shattering booms rang out as the gusts of wind clashed against the balls of five-colored light.

Ultimately, the azure light barrier wasn't able to fare much better than its black counterpart, and it only lasted a few minutes before it was also torn apart, following which a white light barrier emerged.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

The restrictions outside the palace were more complex than he had imagined, and they were all quite formidable, so even for him, it would've taken a great deal of time and effort to bypass them.

However, judging from the expressions of Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan, they were clearly already aware of this and had prepared countermeasures.

The two of them continued to make more hand seals, and the five-colored pillar of light shone brighter and brighter as more balls of five-colored light emerged before raining down upon the white light barrier.

Several hours passed by in the blink of an eye, and rumbling booms were ringing out incessantly on the island, while spiritual lights of different colors flashed erratically.

The five-colored pillar of light had become thicker than before, and it was releasing countles balls of five-colored light that were raining down upon a gray light barrier.

The gray restriction was releasing extremely dense gray light that formed a dark gray cloud, and all of the balls of five-colored light that fell upon it exploded violently on contact.

The gray cloud didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but it proved to be extremely resilient, able to keep the barrage of five-colored balls of light at bay, albeit with great difficulty.

At this point, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were both looking rather weary.

During this time, they had already broken through over 10 different restrictions, of which each successive one was more formidable than the previous one, and the balls of five-colored light weren't making inroads anywhere near as quickly as before.

However, the barrages of attacks were still effective, and the gray cloud was slowly being stripped away bit by bit.

Close to an hour later, the gray cloud was finally completely eradicated, thereby revealing the gray restriction down below.

Both Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan instantly seized this opportunity, renewing their efforts to send close to 100 balls of five-colored light erupting out of the pillar of light at once.

Instead of crashing down right away, the balls of light converged to form an enormous ball of light the size of a house.

Furthermore, this ball of light was no longer semi-transparent. Instead, it had a virtually substantial form and was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations.

The giant ball of light circled around in the air before crashing heavily down onto the gray restriction and exploding violently.

A five-colored sun that was over 1,000 feet in diameter appeared in the sky, and shockwaves that were visible even to the naked eye erupted forth in all directions, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

The gray light barrier was severely warped before exploding, and Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan heaved a collective sigh of relief upon seeing this.

Han Li was observing the proceedings from afar, and he was also quite pleased to see the restriction being broken.

The gray light barrier disintegrated into countless specks of gray light that quickly dissipated, only to be replaced by another starry light barrier.

There were countless starry specks of light on the light barrier, and they were moving in a profound rhythm, as if they really were stars in the night sky.

"There's still more? How many restrictions are there?" Lu Yuqing exclaimed upon seeing this.

"Don't worry, this should be the last one. Those two sure have been made to work hard," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Right at this moment, his expression suddenly changed slightly as a burst of dazzling starlight emerged to encompass his entire body, and the source of the starlight was the storage pouch strapped to his waist.

The starlight was extremely bright, and it immediately burst through his concealment ability.

Lu Yuqing was greatly startled by this unforeseen turn of events, and she had to clap a hand over her own mouth to prevent herself from yelling out loud.

The starry light barrier in the distance also began to glow brightly, and the specks of starlight moving over its surface suddenly accelerated by severalfold, forming a series of profound constellations.

It seemed that the starry light barrier was resonating with the starlight radiating from Han Li's body.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were also caught completely off guard, and they immediately swung around with bewildered expressions.

Han Li immediately tried to search for the source of the starlight in his storage pouch, only for a ball of dazzling starlight to fly out from within on its own, containing a gray stone slab.

Chapter 415: Abrupt Battle

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this.

This was the very same stone slab that contained the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts that he had obtained from Patriarch Cold Flame.

At this moment, all of the runes etched upon the stone slab were glowing with radiant starlight, and as soon as it appeared it immediately began flying toward the starry light barrier in the distance as if it were being summoned by something.

The stone slab was quite valuable to Han Li, and this was clearly an abnormal turn of events, so Han Li certainly wasn't going to just let it fly away, and he immediately reached out to grab it.

The starlight radiating from the stone slab began to sway and struggle as it attempted to force its way out of Han Li's grasp, and it was doing so with such tremendous force that even Han Li's arm was trembling incessantly.

If an average late-True Immortal cultivation had been in his place, there was a very good chance that the stone slab would've already flown out of their grasp.

With his attention diverted, there was a momentary lapse in his concealment secret technique, and as a result, he and Lu Yuqing were exposed.

"Who's there?"

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan immediately stopped what they were doing as they spotted Han Li's duo, and as a result, the pillar of five-colored light in the sky faded into nothingness.

Lu Yuqing reflexively took a couple of steps backward at the sight of the hostile looks on the faces of Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan, and she turned to Han Li with a concerned expression.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed, and he did away with his concealment secret technique altogether.

Xiong Shan took a glance at Han Li's duo, then said, "If I recall correctly, the two of you entered the immortal manor with the True Flame Sect. Why are you sneaking around and following us in secret?"

"That stone slab... You're Fellow Daoist Han!" Patriarch Cold Flame exclaimed at the sight of the gray stone slab that Han Li was holding.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame," Han Li said with a faint smile.

At the same time, he made a hand seal with his free hand, and countless azure runes instantly surged out of the hand that was locked around the stone slab, forming a seal around it.

The light radiating from the stone slab instantly diminished significantly, and its struggles also ceased.

Han Li then flipped a hand over to produce several talismans, which he adhered to the stone slab in an unhurried fashion, and only then did the starlight on the stone slab completely vanish, following which he was able to stow it away.

"Fellow Daoist Han? Do you know this person, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame?" Xiong Shan asked as he turned to Patriarch Cold Flame with a suspicious expression.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist. I've met him on several past occasions, but I definitely wasn't expecting to run into him here," Patriarch Cold Flame hurriedly explained.

Lu Yuqing's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Even if he is an acquaintance of yours, isn't it far too rude of him to have followed us in secret all the way up to this point?" Xiong Shan asked in a cold voice.

"I just so happened to see the two of you traveling together, and it seemed that you were going somewhere, so I decided to follow you out of curiosity. I certainly wasn't expecting to be led to the Light Frost Palace. Given how massive this palace is, surely you two won't mind if the two of us enter it with you," Han Li said with a smile.

At the same time, he casually made a hand seal, and the azure flying boat beneath his feet instantly shrank down significantly before flying up his sleeve.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which swept up himself and Lu Yuqing before carrying both of them to a spot not far away from Xiong Shan's duo.

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Xiong Shan.

Back at the Holy Puppet Sect, he had already established that he was no match for Han Li, and he didn't want to engage Han Li in a direct battle unless there were no other alternatives.

Xiong Shan's expression darkened slightly, and a cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he said, "If you want to enter the Light Frost Palace, then you'll have to show me if you have what it takes!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, his robes billowed outward as golden light erupted out of his body, and thick streaks of golden sword qi emerged, resembling the branches of a flowering tree as they swept directly toward Han Li with astonishing might.

Initially, each streak of sword qi was only around a foot in length, but they swelled to close to 100 feet mid-flight, and they had converged to form a golden sword lotus flower that was descending directly upon Han Li.

Even before the sword lotus flower arrived, a burst of formidable sword intent had already completely enshrouded Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

Han Li felt a burst of sharp pain over his entire body, and the flashing golden light radiating from the sword lotus flower struck him with some type of illusion, as if he could already see himself being torn to shreds by the streaks of sword qi.

He immediately drew upon his own vast spiritual sense as an instinctive reaction, and the illusion was instantly dispelled.

In contrast, there was a horrified look on Lu Yuqing's face, and her eyes were dazed and hollow, as if she had been plunged into the depths of despair by Xiong Shan's immense sword intent.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he positioned himself in front of Lu Yuqing as 18 specks of starlight emerged over his body. As a result, he instantly grew a little taller, then threw a punch directly upward.

A burst of tremendous force was released from his fist, causing the surrounding space to warp and twist, and ripples that were visible even to the naked eye could be seen sweeping through the air.

The golden sword lotus flower's downward momentum was instantly halted, following which it shattered and disintegrated into countless specks of golden light.

The tremendous sword intent in the air also faded with the sword lotus flower's destruction, and Lu Yuqing shuddered before gasping for air, but at the very least, she had returned to her senses.

She had been completely immobilized by the sword intent just now, but she was still able to see what had just unfolded, and a complex look appeared in her eyes as she cast her gaze toward Han Li, who was standing up ahead with his back facing her.

The fearsome power released by Han Li's punch was only stopped momentarily by the golden sword lotus flower before continuing to sweep toward Xiong Shan with astonishing might.

Xiong Shan instantly felt the space around him constrict, and it was as if he had suddenly been trapped within a wall of iron and steel.

"You're also using the Great Universe Origin Arts!" Xiong Shan exclaimed as he made a hand seal with one hand, and his golden longsword instantly appeared in his grasp.

With his longsword summoned, his aura began to rapidly swell and take on a peerlessly sharp quality.

Immediately thereafter, he let loose a thunderous roar before slashing his longsword through the air with a flick of his wrist, and several huge streaks of golden sword qi swept through the air around him to free him from the constricting space.

He then began to chant an incantation, and his golden longsword flew out of his grasp before transforming into a giant golden sword that was several thousand feet in size, giving off formidable metal-attribute law fluctuations.

The giant golden sword slashed through the air before crashing into the force generated by Han Li's punch with an earth-shattering boom, and neither side seemed to be able to get the better of the other, with sword qi and fist intent erupting in all directions, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

Right at this moment, an indetectable smirk appeared on Xiong Shan's face, and a giant golden flag abruptly appeared behind Han Li amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

The flag was radiating golden light with countless runes flashing on its surface, and it was also giving off bursts of metal law fluctuations.

As soon as the golden flag appeared, it instantly released countless thin golden threads that shot rapidly toward Han Li's defenseless back.

Lu Yuqing's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, but the golden threads were too fast for her to react to.

Right as the two of them were about to completely inundated by the wave of golden threads, a burst of starlight suddenly flashed over Han Li's body, and the Seven Bright Star Rings flew out, arranging themselves into the formation of the Big Dipper as they situated themselves behind Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

Radiant starlight erupted out of the Seven Bright Star Rings, instantly forming a thick wall of light.

A string of dull thuds rang out in rapid succession as countless tiny holes were pierced into the surface of the wall of light, but it was ultimately able to keep all of the golden threads at bay, much to Xiong Shan's alarm and dismay.

Right at this moment, another resounding boom rang out as Xiong Shan's giant golden sword was sent flying back through the air, while the tremendous force unleashed by Han Li's punch also faded away.

All of this had transpired in the blink of an eye, and Han Li remained standing on the spot in a calm and composed fashion, while Xiong Shan stumbled back a couple of steps before steadying himself.

He then made a hand seal, and the giant golden sword shrank down to half its original size before circling around in the air above his head.

Xiong Shan paid no heed to the giant sword as he glowered intently at Han Li and the Seven Bright Star Rings behind him.

The Seven Bright Star Rings had appeared at the perfect time, and it was as if Han Li were a clairvoyant that had predicted the emergence of the giant golden flag.

"I've been here this entire time, so did you think that I wouldn't notice when you summoned that golden flag in secret before concealing it while the two of you were breaking the restrictions here?" Han Li asked with a faint smile.

Xiong Shan's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and he made a hand seal, upon which the giant golden flag vanished from the spot before appearing behind him the next instant.

"I wonder if you had summoned that golden flag as a precautionary measure to deal with unforeseen danger, or if you were planning to use it on someone else," Han Li said with a faint smile as he took a meaningful glance at Patriarch Cold Flame.

A furious look immediately appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon hearing this, and he flew over 1,000 feet away from Xiong Shan in the blink of an eye.

Chapter 416: Joining Forces

"Don't fall for his attempt to drive a wedge between us, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame! I had no other intention than to take some precautionary measures in case enemies arrived on the scene while we were busy breaking these restrictions, and it seems that my efforts were very much necessary," Xiong Shan said.

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, but he was still looking rather hesitant about who to believe.

"Is that so? In that case, why did you summon the flag in secret without telling Fellow Daoist Cold Flame?" Han Li asked with a faint smile.

"That... was indeed an oversight on my part," Xiong Shan conceded in a slightly awkward manner.

He hadn't actually summoned the flag for the purpose of attacking Patriarch Cold Flame. Instead, it was just a hidden trump card that he could call upon to seize the initiative in the case of any mishaps. Of course, he was prepared to use it against Patriarch Cold Flame if necessary, but given the circumstances, things weren't so easy to explain.

"You're not to blame, Fellow Daoist Xiong. I was simply too gullible and susceptible to the words of others," Patriarch Cold Flame said in an indifferent voice.

Xiong Shan knew that he was at fault here, so he didn't dwell on the subject any longer.

"I would consider you to be an acquaintance of mine, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. There are bound to be many precious treasures in this Light Frost Palace, it's sure to be a very dangerous place as well, so why don't we join forces and explore it together? You're aware of my powers, and I'm sure you know that I can be of great assistance to you," Han Li said.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame, I simply want to repay you for bestowing the Great Universe Origin Arts upon me. I'm no saint, but at the same time, I wouldn't stoop as low as to plot against my own allies," Han Li said as he took a subtle glance at Xiong Shan, in response to which Xiong Shan gave a cold harrumph.

Patriarch Cold Flame weighed up his options for a moment, then smiled as he said, "Alright, in that case, I'll be in your care, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Likewise, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. Shall we break this final restriction first?" Han Li proposed with a smile.

"What is the meaning of this?" Xiong Shan interjected with a dark look on his face.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Xiong. It's not like there's any vendetta between us, it's just that you attacked me without allowing me a chance to explain myself, and that resulted in a misunderstanding. In my opinion, let's leave this matter behind us. At the moment, all of us have a shared objective, so we should work together to break this restriction. Time is of the essence, after all," Han Li said as he turned to Xiong Shan.

Xiong Shan was silent for a moment, then smiled as he replied, "I agree, Fellow Daoist Han. Please forgive me for my earlier rash actions, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. If we do find any treasures in the palace, you can have the first pick."

"There's no need to apologize, Fellow Daoist Xiong Shan. Now that Fellow Daoist Han and this fellow daoist have joined us, our chances of success will naturally be greater than before. By the way, may I know your name, fellow daoist?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked as he turned to Lu Yuqing.

Xiong Shan also turned his attention to Lu Yuqing upon hearing this.

"You're far too kind, Senior. I wouldn't dare to regard myself as an equal to the two of you with my paltry cultivation base. I'm only accompanying Brother Han to broaden my horizons, and I would be more than satisfied if you could spare me a few treasures that aren't up to your standards," Lu Yuqing hurriedly replied.

It was clear that Han Li had presented himself under a different identity to Patriarch Cold Flame, so she had immediately made an adjustment and begun referring to Han Li as Brother Han instead of Brother Liu.

Both Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan's expressions eased slightly upon hearing this.

"The more time we waste here, the higher the likelihood that something could go wrong, so let's begin right away. Keep doing what you were doing before, and I'll also lend you my assistance to break this restriction," Han Li said.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan both nodded in response, and the latter swept a sleeve through the air to stow away his golden longsword and golden flag, then flew to the same position as before to resume his efforts.

Patriarch Cold Flame also sprang into action, and the five spirit treasures in the air lit up once again as the pillar of five-colored light re-emerged.

A layer of dazzling starlight emerged from the starry light barrier, and there were countless stars surging over its surface, presenting a profound sight to behold.

Balls of five-colored light flew out of the pillar of light before striking the starry light barrier, and a string of resounding booms rang out as the starry light barrier trembled incessantly.

Meanwhile, Han Li stowed his Seven Bright Star Rings away, then channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts with all his might, and radiant starlight instantly appeared over his arms.

Immediately thereafter, he lashed out at the starlight restriction down below with ferocious might, unleashing a barrage of fist projections that rained down upon the starry light barrier.

Lu Yuqing was also doing what she could to help, summoning an azure feather fan that she swept through the air to send countless azure blades of wind hurtling toward the starry light barrier.

Their combined efforts were extremely formidable, and the starry light barrier was unable to withstand the assault, quickly being stripped down to only a thin layer.

However, right at this moment, the sky above the island suddenly began to rumble, and the white mist up above began to swirl, forming an enormous vortex.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he looked up into the sky, while Xiong Shan yelled,

"The restriction is trying to draw upon starpower from the heavens to replenish itself! If we can't destroy it now, it won't be long until it makes a full recovery, so it's now or never!" Xiong Shan yelled.

"That's right, we can't allow it to recover!" Patriarch Cold Flame chimed in.

The two of them made a rapid series of hand seals, and the pillar of five-colored light brightened considerably as countless balls of five-colored light shot out from within, then converged to form another enormous ball of light in the blink of an eye before descending toward the starry light barrier.

Han Li also responded to the call, taking on his Giant Mountain Ape form amid a flash of golden light.

At the same time, 18 specks of starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen to complement the golden light radiating from the rest of his body.

The Giant Mountain Ape pounded its own chest with its fists, then let loose a thunderous roar before swinging its fist viciously through the air.

An enormous golden fist projection instantly appeared with streaks of starlight revolving around it, and the fist projection fell upon the starry light barrier.

Lu Yuqing also renewed her efforts as her azure feather fan began to radiate dazzling azure light, and it released an azure wind dragon that swooped down with ferocious might.

Several earth-shattering booms rang out in succession, and a series of cracks finally began to spread over the starry light barrier.

With one final resounding boom, the starry light barrier exploded into a vast expanse of starlight, but instead of dissipating, all of the starlight rapidly converged to form an enormous vortex that was releasing indescribably formidable suction power.

Han Li and the others didn't have any time to react before they were sucked into the vortex, and Han Li was instantly overcome by a rush of dizziness as the entire world transformed into an indistinguishable blur.

Upon recovering his vision, he found himself standing on a spacious stone platform. Patriarch Cold Flame and the others were also nearby, but their eyes were tightly shut, seemingly still yet to regain consciousness.

The stone platform was quite antiquated in appearance. It had a dark azure hue and was over 1,000 feet in size.

Beneath Han Li and the others was a teleportation array that was still operating and radiating bursts of white light.

Han Li was still feeling a little dizzy, and he shook his head vigorously to clear away the dizziness before inspecting his surroundings.

At this moment, he was situated in a blue space with a sun up above. There were white clouds drifting through the sky and a light breeze blowing through the air, in stark contrast with the misty and forbidding black sea from before.

This must be the real Light Frost Palace.

Around half a kilometer ahead of the stone platform was a mountain with a summit that was concealed within the clouds, indicating that it had to have been at least 40,000 to 50,000 feet tall.

The mountain was extremely steep and entirely silver in color.

There was a ball of faint purple light situated on the mountain summit, and Han Li could see the outlines of a purple palace within the ball of light.

A steep staircase extended straight from the purple palace to the foot of the mountain, and the staircase was a sparkling purple color, presenting a spectacular sight to behold, as if it were a staircase to heaven.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

For some reason, this environment struck him with a sense of familiarity.

He inspected his surroundings once again while trying to recall when he had seen this place before, but to no avail, so he could only set aside that train of thought for now as he prepared to leave the teleportation array.

However, as soon as he attempted to leave the array, a burst of tremendous force surged out of it, locking his body into place and rendering him immobilized.

He immediately cast his gaze toward the white light around him, and a contemplative look flashed through his eyes.

Before long, Patriarch Cold Flame, Xiong Shan, and Lu Yuqing also regained their consciousness one after another, and Lu Yuqing began to look around with an awestruck expression.

In contrast, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan completely ignored their surroundings as they turned to stare at the purple palace on the mountain summit with a fervent look in their eyes.

However, neither of them moved.

"So this is the Light Frost Palace... It really is a spectacular place," Lu Yuqing praised as she tried to take a step forward, only to find herself also locked into place, just like Han Li.

"The teleportation array is still operating. We'll only be able to get out once it completely ceases operation," Patriarch Cold Flame explained.

Lu Yuqing turned to him with a grateful nod upon hearing this, while Han Li also took a glance at him in silence.

He had intentionally driven a wedge between Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan in order to recruit the former to his side, and he had done this because Patriarch Cold Flame had already entered this place once.

Having explored many secret areas in the past, Han Li knew how much an asset having an experienced guide could be.

Chapter 417: Pursuers

The teleportation array beneath Han Li and the others continued to operate, but it was getting slower and slower, and the white light that it was releasing was also rapidly fading.

In the meantime, the four of them remained silent and didn't make any further attempts to move. They took this time to inspect their surroundings, but of course, the majority of their attention was focused on that silver mountain.

The longing in Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan's eyes was becoming more and more intense, while Han Li remained expressionless, and Lu Yuqing's eyes were constantly darting around, occasionally stealing glances at Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan.

A short while later, the operation of the teleportation array finally completely ceased, and all of the white light also faded, allowing Han Li and the others to emerge from the array.

"Let's go."

Upon stepping out of the array, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan made their way down from the stone platform, then rushed toward the long staircase at the foot of the silver mountain, but they refrained from taking flight.

"Let's follow them," Han Li said to Lu Yuqing, then quickly strode down from the stone platform as well.

Not long after the four of them left the teleportation array, the stone platform behind them abruptly shuddered, immediately following which the teleportation array began to radiate dazzling white light once again.

Han Li and the others were all quite startled by this turn of events, and they immediately stopped in their tracks before turning around, right as a group of six or seven figures appeared within the teleportation array.

These people were none other than the black-robed Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, and they were led by their sect master, Chen Pi.

"Xue Han!" Patriarch Cold Flame exclaimed at the sight of Ghost Wail Sect Master.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

The Ghost Wail Sect Master had clearly been introduced as Chen Pi earlier, while Xue Han was the name of one of the Ubiquitous Pavilion's Golden Immortal Stage elders and one of the two Golden Immortals who had attacked the Holy Puppet Sect.

Having just appeared in the teleportation array, Xue Han's expression was a little dazed, but he then immediately returned to his senses.

He took a glance at his surroundings, and his gaze settled momentarily on Han Li and Lu Yuqing before immediately shifting to Xiong Shan and Patriarch Cold Flame.

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan and Patriarch Cold Flame exchanged a bewildered glance with one another.

It didn't take long before Xue Han spotted the purple palace on the mountain summit, and an ecstatic look instantly appeared on his face as he cackled, "I knew it!"

A fearful look flashed through Patriarch Cold Flame's eye as he asked, "Xue Han, why are you here?"

"You thought you managed to shake us off, didn't you? I knew you had an ulterior motive for entering the immortal manor, so I intentionally let you leave, but we've been following you this entire time! Having said that, I didn't think you would lead us to the Light Frost Palace," Xue Han chortled.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

It was rather disturbing to him that he had completely failed to detect the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators on the way here.

However, given Xue Han's Golden Immortal Stage cultivation base, if he had some special concealment techniques up his sleeve, then it was certainly possible for them to have remained undetected by Han Li this entire time.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan's expressions had darkened significantly at this point.

They had thought that they had been quite sneaky and cautious, but this entire time, they had been followed by two groups of people and remained completely oblivious.

The two of them exchanged a glance, then turned in unison to rush toward the staircase as quickly as they could.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing exchanged a glance, then immediately followed along.

Xue Han remained completely unconcerned upon seeing this, and he chuckled coldly, "You think you can get away! In your dreams!"

There was no way that a group of four True Immortals would be able to escape from a seasoned Golden Immortal like himself, particularly in what was clearly a sealed space with no way out.

With that in mind, he proceeded to pursue Han Li and the others, only to also find himself being held in place by a burst of tremendous force, rendering him immobilized despite his Golden Immortal Stage cultivation base.

He immediately let loose a low roar as he struggled with all his might, but to his surprise, his efforts proved to be futile.

At this point, the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators were also beginning to regain their consciousness one after another, only to find that they were also unable to move.

Han Li and the others seized this opportunity to rush to the foot of the silver staircase as quickly as they could, following which Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan immediately led the way up the staircase.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he noticed that the two of them had slowed down significantly upon stepping onto the staircase, and he cautiously set foot onto the first step.

A layer of faint yellow light surfaced over the step beneath his foot, and a burst of tremendous force instantly descended upon him.

Lu Yuqing also stepped onto the staircase, following which her body immediately swayed slightly as an alarmed look appeared on her face.

Her brows furrowed slightly as a layer of azure light appeared over her body, then transformed into a crane projection that spread its wings in an attempt to take flight, but no matter how frantically the azure crane projection flapped its wings, the suction force acting upon Lu Yuqing from the step beneath her foot wasn't diminished in the slightest.

"The gravitational restriction on this staircase can't be countered through the use of immortal spiritual power or any spirit treasures, so you can only rely on your own physical prowess," Patriarch Cold Flame explained. "Given the urgency of the situation, I'm afraid I'll have to go on ahead. Good luck."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, while Lu Yuqing's complexion paled slightly in response.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame continued to quickly scale the staircase. Having also cultivated the Great Universe Origin Arts, he had attained immense physical prowess, and at this point, he had already scaled 30 to 40 steps.

Xiong Shan's physical prowess was lacking compared with Patriarch Cold Flame, but he was clearly also prepared, and he was able to keep up with Patriarch Cold Flame just fine.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to take a glance at the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, who were still trapped in the teleportation array.

The white light radiating from the array was rapidly fading, and it wouldn't be long until they were freed.

"Hurry!" he urged as he began to quickly scale the staircase.

Lu Yuqing swept a sleeve through the air to dispel the azure light around her, then took a deep breath as she also began to climb the staircase.

The gravitational restriction on the staircase was indeed quite formidable, but as an early-True Immortal cultivator, her physical constitution was nothing to be scoffed at, so she was also climbing up the steps at a decent pace.

An agitated look appeared on Xue Han's face as he watched Han Li and the others scaling the staircase.

At this point, he had already realized further struggles would only be futile, so he had resigned himself to waiting.

Finally, the white light radiating from the teleportation array completely faded, and he instantly instructed, "After them!"

Immediately thereafter, he flew toward Han Li and others as quickly as he could, followed by the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, but as soon as they flew out of the stone platform, they abruptly began to plummet toward the ground like dead weights.

They slammed into the ground one after another amid a string of resounding booms, smashing several huge craters into the ground in the process.

They hurriedly clambered to their feet, and even though they weren't injured, they had been reduced to a rather disheveled state. A few of them had landed head-first and were a little dazed as a result.

Xue Han was furious at the embarrassment that he had been subjected to, and none of the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators dared to say anything at the sight of his enraged expression.

"So what if there's a flight restriction here? I'll hunt you all down regardless, and once I do, I'm going to make you regret ever going against me!" Xue Han spat through gritted teeth.

Immediately thereafter, he charged toward the staircase as quickly as he could, followed closely by the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators.

Before long, all of them arrived at the foot of the silver staircase before immediately embarking on the climb.

As soon as he set foot on the first step, Xue Han's brows instantly furrowed slightly, and he took a deep breath as he cautioned, "There's quite a formidable restriction here, so be on your guard!"

All of the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators hurriedly gave affirmative responses, while Xue Han took a glance at Han Li and the others before setting off in pursuit of them.

He was able to scale the staircase at a remarkable speed, quickly opening up quite a large gap between himself and the rest of the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, and it seemed that the gravitational restriction here wasn't affecting him much at all.

At this point, Han Li and the others had already scaled 400 to 500 steps, and Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were still leading the way from the forefront, with Han Li and Lu Yuqing progressing up the staircase together a short distance behind them.

Upon noticing what was happening down below, a grim look appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face, and a layer of faint starlight appeared over his body as he abruptly accelerated.

Xiong Shan's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a layer of golden light emerged over his body as he also sped up in an urgent fashion.

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing was already sweating profusely, and with each step that she took, her body would shudder slightly.

With each successive step, the gravitational restriction would become slightly more formidable, and at this point, the gravitational force was already three to four times stronger than it had been on the first step.

Lu Yuqing turned to glance at Han Li, and she was surprised to find that he didn't appear to be struggling at all.

However, there was a rather peculiar dazed look in his eyes, as if his thoughts were somewhere else entirely.

"Brother Liu," Lu Yuqing called out to him through voice transmission.

Han Li immediately snapped back to his senses, then turned to her as he asked, "What is it?"

Lu Yuqing forced a smile onto her own face as she said, "The restriction here is too strong for me to continue. Go ahead without me, Brother Liu. "

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to find Xue Han rapidly scaling the staircase, doing so with such ease that he wasn't even pausing from one step to the next.

At this point, it wasn't going to take long before he caught up to them.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were only accelerating further, and they had already left Han Li and Lu Yuqing far behind.

Chapter 418: Arduous Climb

"Don't worry about me, Brother Liu. These people have no vendetta against me, and I'm just a nobody anyway, so I'm sure they won't do anything to me," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then suddenly strode over to Lu Yuqing's side before picking her up in his arms.

Lu Yuqing was swept off her feet before she even had a chance to react, and the force weighing down on her was instantly lifted, while the gravitational force acting upon Han Li was doubled.

However, this was still well within his tolerance capacity, and he began to quickly bound up the staircase.

"Brother Liu..."

"I agreed to bring you with me, so I have to do everything in my power to keep you safe," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

A complex look appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes as she lowered her head.

Both Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had noticed what Han Li was doing, and they were quite taken aback by his actions.

"Looks like you've found yourself quite a womanizer of an ally, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. I must say, I do admire his courage," Xiong Shan jeered with a mocking look in his eyes.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. Even with his physical prowess and extensive preparation, he didn't dare to take this gravitational restriction lightly at all, and he certainly wasn't optimistic about Han Li's chances of scaling the staircase while carrying an extra burden.

With that in mind, a cold look flashed through his eyes as he turned his gaze away from Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li was accelerating further and further, to the point that his speed was comparable with Xue Han's, and as a result, the gap between them was steadily maintained.

Xue Han's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, while Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were both quite surprised.

Never had they anticipated that Han Li would only be getting faster in this situation. In fact, he was beginning to slowly catch up to them.

Both of them immediately renewed their efforts, accelerating further themselves, and before long, over an hour had already passed by.

At this point, all of them had already crossed the halfway mark of the staircase, and Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were still leading the way, but Han Li was only fewer than 30 steps behind them, while Xue Han was around 100 steps behind Han Li.

As for the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators, they had already been left so far behind that they were nothing more than tiny black dots in the distance.

At this point, the gravity on the staircase had already reached an extremely formidable level, and everyone had slowed down significantly.

Patriarch Cold Flame's entire body was enshrouded in a layer of bright starlight that resembled a veil, giving him a mysterious and powerful appearance.

He was still leading the way from the front, and he was climbing up the steps at a roughly consistent speed.

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan's skin had also taken on a golden hue in addition to the radiant golden light emanating from his body, and he resembled a golden statue that was giving off a tremendous aura of physical prowess.

He was a few steps behind Patriarch Cold Flame, but he was progressing just as smoothly.

Patriarch Cold Flame was rather taken aback to see this. He could tell that Xiong Shan was using a very formidable body refinement secret technique.

Xiong Shan hadn't mastered this ability the last time they were here, so he had most likely attained this ability since the last emergence of the immortal manor specifically for this purpose.

Having said that, this was no surprise as he had also made extensive preparations over the years.

Patriarch Cold Flame cast his gaze even further down the staircase to find that a layer of starlight had also appeared over Han Li's body, and even though he was carrying Lu Yuqing, he wasn't showing any signs of strain at all as he continued to scale the staircase in a calm and measured fashion.

As for Lu Yuqing, she had fallen completely still, and her eyes were tightly shut, as if she had fallen asleep.

Patriarch Cold Flame was astonished to see this, and he was only just beginning to realize that Han Li's physical prowess was far more formidable than he had imagined.

Han Li seemed to have detected Patriarch Cold Flame's gaze, and as he looked up, their eyes met.

Patriarch Cold Flame gave Han Li a rather forced smile, then hurriedly averted his gaze.

Han Li's expression remained indifferent as he also averted his gaze from Patriarch Cold Flame and turned his attention to the top of the silver staircase.

By his estimates, there were roughly 10,000 steps on this staircase, and he still had over 3,000 steps left until he reached the top.

He had only used a small portion of his physical powers at this point, so if the rate of increase of gravitational force remained consistent, then he anticipated that he would be able to reach the top of the staircase just fine.

However...

Han Li turned around to find that Xue Han wasn't falling behind at all.

His physical prowess was rather average, so he held no special advantage when it came to scaling this staircase, but ultimately, he was still a Golden Immortal. At this rate, perhaps he wouldn't be able to catch up to Han Li and the others, but he would most likely also be able to reach the top of the staircase, and once that happened, he would undoubtedly immediately lash out at them.

While Han Li didn't fear him, a battle against a Golden Immortal was naturally something that he wanted to avoid.

With that in mind, the starlight emanating from his body grew even brighter as he accelerated even further.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan were both astonished to see this, and they could only accelerate themselves in order to maintain their lead.

However, it didn't take long at all before Han Li was directly behind them, and at this rate, he would even overtake them soon.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. Even though he had agreed to forge an alliance with Han Li, the Light Frost Palace was just up ahead, and he certainly wasn't going to allow Han Li to get there before him.

Hence, he let loose a low roar, and the starlight radiating from his body also became significantly brighter, while his True Extreme Film also emerged over his skin.

At the same time, his body swelled drastically in size, with his limbs in particular becoming significantly thicker, and he was able to speed up once again.

Xiong Shan naturally wasn't willing to be left behind, and he began to chant an incantation as his skin took on a darker hue and a metallic gleam, giving him an even stronger resemblance to a golden statue.

Furthermore, his stature was also dramatically enhanced, and with that came a significant increase in speed.

With Han Li's trio picking up the pace in unison, Xue Han was instantly left behind, much to his alarm and fury.

His cultivation base far surpassed those of Han Li's trio, but his physical prowess wasn't remarkable in the slightest, and he hadn't prepared for this in advance, so he was already going all-out just to maintain this speed.

An urgent look appeared in his eyes as he watched Han Li's trio getting further and further away from him.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of white light, which contained a white talisman, upon which was inscribed an image of what appeared to be a giant humanoid deity.

He slapped the talisman against himself, and it instantly vanished into his body, upon which a burst of dazzling white light appeared around him.

At the same time, a series of white spirit veins quickly spread over his body, and his physical prowess was significantly enhanced, thereby allowing him to remain in the race to the top.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he identified the white talisman to be the Giant Strength Spirit Talisman, a powerful immortal talisman that could enhance one's physical prowess.

However, he wasn't all that concerned by this. After all, a talisman like this was inevitably going to wear off soon.

Around 15 minutes passed by, and at this point, everyone was only around 1,000 steps from reaching the top of the staircase.

At this point, even though Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan had sped up, Han Li was still able to catch up to them, but he didn't overtake them, and the three of them were scaling the staircase alongside one another.

As for Xue Han, he was clearly beginning to struggle. The white spirit veins on his body had become quite dim, and a faint sheen of sweat had appeared on his forehead, while his breathing had also become rather labored.

Earlier, he had only been lagging behind by about 100 steps, but that gap had since widened to somewhere between 200 to 300 steps.

Furthermore, his pace was becoming stagnant, while Han Li's trio continued to make rapid progress, and the gap between them was only continuing to widen.

Ultimately, his talisman was unable to bridge the enormous disparity in physical prowess.

An uncertain look appeared on Xue Han's face as he looked up at Han Li's trio.

At this rate, they were going to reach the top far ahead of him.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to summon a palm-sized black jade box, which was giving off a warm and comforting aura, clearly indicating that the box had been crafted from some type of extremely precious material.

There were several talismans plastered to the box, all of which were shimmering with spiritual light, indicating that whatever was in the box was being kept tightly under wraps.

Xue Han opened his mouth to release a burst of black light that enveloped the jade box, and all of the talismans on the box immediately flew off their own, following which the spiritual light emanating from them completely faded, indicating that they were disposable talismans.

Xue Han paid no heed to those spent talismans as he carefully opened the jade box to reveal a black pill inside that was roughly the size of a pigeon egg.

The pill was giving off a burst of black light, within which a demon beast projection could be seen.

The beast resembled a dragon with a lone horn on its head and a pair of wings on its back.

Tremendous energy fluctuations intermingled with a hint of law power fluctuations were emanating from the black pill, and a hint of reluctance flashed through Xue Han's eyes, but he ultimately swallowed the pill, nonetheless.

Even though Han Li's trio was far ahead of Xue Han, the black pill gave off such formidable energy fluctuations that their attention was instantly drawn to him, and a stunned look appeared on Xiong Shan's face as he exclaimed, "That's... a Profound Beast Essence Pill!"

"What kind of pill is that, Fellow Daoist Xiong?" Patriarch Cold Flame immediately asked.

Chapter 419: Battle Prohibition

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this exchange.

Thanks to the Heaven Controlling Vial, his cultivation advancement had relied heavily on pill consumption since his return to the Immortal Realm. Hence, whenever he got the opportunity, he would read through all types of books related to pill refinement. This was particularly true back when he was still in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and during his readings, he had learned about the Profound Beast Essence Pill.

The pill was refined using the placentas or eggs of certain powerful beasts as the primary ingredients. These demon beasts often possessed incredibly powerful physical bodies, and taking this pill would infuse the power of the demon beast's bloodline into the body of the consumer. Not only would this drastically enhance their physical prowess, the consumer also had a chance of attaining that demon beast's innate abilities.

If the primary ingredients were acquired from immortal beasts that had innate mastery over certain law powers, then there was a chance that the resulting Profound Beast Essence Pill would also be imbued with the same law powers, thereby serving the same purpose as a dao pill.

However, not only was the pill no less difficult to refine than a dao pill, the supplementary ingredients were also very difficult to find, thereby making them exceedingly rare. This one was clearly imbued with law powers, so it was even more remarkable than the average Profound Beast Essence Pill.

Xiong Shan briefly explained the effects of the Profound Beast Essence Pill to Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame through voice transmission, and the latter's expression instantly changed drastically upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, a burst of radiant black light erupted out of Xue Han's body, and his slightly pale complexion instantly returned to normal, then turned as red as blood.

At the same time, a string of cracks and pops were ringing out from within his body as thick veins began to bulge all over the exposed parts of his body.

His entire body then began to expand rapidly, reaching twice its original size in the blink of an eye, and a layer of thick black scales that was giving off a metallic sheen appeared over his skin, while sharp black claws emerged from the tips of his fingers.

All of a sudden, he had transformed into a half-human, half-draconic creature.

Not only that, but the muscles on his forehead and his back were squirming violently, as if something were about to emerge from those spots.

However, right at this moment, the black light surging over his body subsided, and his squirming muscles also fell still.

As the black faded, Xue Han's new form was revealed in its full glory.

A stunned look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. The effects of the Profound Beast Essence Pill were comparable to that of his true spirit transformations.

Attaining those transformations had been an extremely grueling task for Han Li, yet for Xue Han, he was able to achieve the same effect just through taking a pill.

Han Li looked at Xue Han for a moment longer, then withdrew his gaze and continued to scale the staircase, and Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan hurriedly followed along.

Xue Han gently exhaled, and a sharp gust of wind shot out of his mouth, striking the stone step in front of him with an audible sound.

He then looked down at his own body before heaving a faint sigh.

Having taken the Profound Beast Essence Pill on such short notice, it hadn't been very efficacious at all, and most of the pill's power had been squandered, but this was already enough.

Xue Han took a step forward, climbing up two steps at a time as he recommenced his pursuit of Han Li's trio.

Han Li and the others didn't turn around to see what was happening behind them, but they could detect Xue Han's rapid approach with their spiritual sense, and they hurriedly picked up the pace themselves.

However, in this new form, Xue Han's speed far exceeded theirs, and it didn't take long before the gap between them was shortened to only just over 100 steps.

At this rate, he would be able to catch up to them in no more than 15 minutes.

Xiong Shan's expression darkened slightly as he chanted an incantation, and his body swelled even further in size amid a flash of golden light.

At the same time, all of the hair on his head quickly vanished, and a golden monk robe also appeared over his body.

In the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a golden Arhat.

Following this transformation, Xiong Shan was also able to scale two steps at a time, and he was climbing the staircase at a comparable speed to Xue Han.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he also began to channel his Great Universe Origin Arts with all his might.

A string of cracks and pops rang out within his body, while 18 specks of starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen, and a burst of tremendous power erupted out of his body, causing the surrounding space to tremble and quiver.

Han Li continued to only take one step at a time, but he wasn't lagging behind Xiong Shan at all.

As a result, Patriarch Cold Flame was instantly overtaken by the two of them, and an urgent look appeared in his eyes as he also began to channel his Great Universe Origin Arts with all his might, and 18 specks of starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen as well, but even though they were using the same body refinement art, it was clear that Han Li's physical prowess far surpassed Patriarch Cold Flame's.

Hence, even though Patriarch Cold Flame was also able to accelerate by a large margin, he was still a little slower than Han Li, Xiong Shan, and Xue Han.

As a result, Xue Han was beginning to catch up, and in his urgency to get away, Patriarch Cold Flame flipped a hand over to summon four or five talismans of different colors, all of which he plastered onto his own body in quick succession.

The talismans instantly fused into body, and the starlight around him grew brighter as he sped up once again, allowing him to just barely keep up with Han Li and Xiong Shan.

At this point, they were fewer than 200 steps from the top.

The steps here had become even steeper, while the gravitational force was increasing at a far faster rate than before, thereby forcing everyone to slow down.

Han Li and Xiong Shan were still able to make steady progress, despite being forced to decelerate, but the same couldn't be said for Patriarch Cold Flame.

The starlight radiating from his body had dimmed significantly, and he was also getting short of breath, indicating that he wasn't going to be able to keep this up for much longer.

Having said that, Xue Han was also in a similar situation. Large sections of the black scales over his skin had already receded, and his face was looking a little pale, while his footsteps were also becoming rather unsteady.

A look of fury and frustration appeared on Xue Han's face.

The bloodline power in the Profound Beast Essence Pill still hadn't completely fused with his body, and he wasn't going to be able to maintain this form for much longer.

All of a sudden, more of the black scales on his body faded, and he was forced to stop in his tracks.

Patriarch Cold Flame was ecstatic to see this, and he paused momentarily to catch his breath while also summoning a blue pill that was giving off tremendous starpower.

He immediately swallowed the pill without any hesitation, then channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts to digest it, and the starlight emanating from his body instantly became significantly brighter, following which he continued to scale the staircase.

A cold gleam flashed through Xue Han's eyes, and he abruptly raised both hands before flicking his fingers through the air in rapid succession.

10 thin black threads instantly shot out of his fingertip before vanishing in a flash.

In the next instant, the 10 black threads appeared behind Patriarch Cold Flame without any warning, then hurtled directly toward his back at an alarming speed.

However, right at this moment, a layer of bright yellow light appeared over the silver staircase, and a burst of tremendous gravitational force began to act upon the black threads.

Seven of the black threads were instantly diverted away from their original trajectories, but the remaining three were still hurtling directly toward Patriarch Cold Flame.

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression changed drastically upon sensing this, and he let loose an alarmed cry as he dodged to the side.

However, despite his best efforts, he was unable to evade the three black threads, which tore through the protective spiritual light around him before piercing into his body, then exploded violently.

Three massive holes were instantly blown into his body, and blood was gushing out profusely.

He let loose an agonized wail as he fell to his knees, and both Han Li and Xiong Shan immediately turned around upon hearing this.

As for Xue Han, he was looking rather surprised, seemingly taken aback by how easily his sneak attack had landed.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, a resounding boom suddenly rang out directly above him, and a thick bolt of reddish-purple lightning appeared out of thin air before striking him with tremendous power.

His entire body was instantly inundated by radiant lightning, and a blood-curdling howl rang out before being abruptly cut off.

Xue Han's body was torn to shreds within the lightning, and his nascent soul sprang out of his destroyed remains, only to be instantly destroyed by the lightning as well.

All of this had happened extremely abruptly, and Han Li was completely rooted to the spot in astonishment, but naturally also quite relieved that Xue Han had been eliminated.

"What a fool!" Xiong Shan chuckled coldly, then paid no further heed to what was happening behind him as he continued to scale the staircase.

It was clear that there was some type of battle prohibition restriction on the staircase.

Instead of following Xiong Shan, Han Li remained on the spot as he cast his gaze toward Patriarch Cold Flame, who had just suffered extremely severe injuries, but was also quite relieved to see the demise of Xue Han.

He pulled out a crimson pill in a shaky manner before swallowing it, and a layer of bright crimson light instantly appeared over his body. The three holes in his body quickly healed, following which he struggled to his feet.

However, Han Li could tell that Patriarch Cold Flame's internal injuries were still far from healed, and it was most likely going to take some time before he could continue to scale the staircase.

Thankfully, the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators were still very far behind, and that should give Patriarch Cold Flame enough time to recover.

With that in mind, Han Li was just about to continue up the staircase when his expression abruptly stiffened.

Chapter 420: Reaching the Top

As the bolt of reddish-purple lightning faded, Xue Han's severely ravaged remains were revealed.

However, what had been revealed was not a body. Instead, it was a dark red wooden puppet with mysterious patterns engraved upon all of its parts.

Standing not far away from the wooden puppet was none other than Xue Han, and his face was looking a little pale, but aside from that, he was completely unharmed.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan's expressions instantly changed drastically upon hearing this.

That's a substitution puppet!

Xue Han summoned a pill that he promptly swallowed, and his pale complexion quickly recovered.

"I didn't anticipate there to be a restriction like this, but no matter. There are plenty of ways to kill someone without directly attacking them," he chuckled coldly, then began to slowly ascend the staircase once again.

Patriarch Cold Flame shuddered as he hurriedly tried to get away, but he had only just raised a foot when an unnatural flush appeared over his face, and he threw up a mouthful of blood before falling feebly to the ground once again.

A look of despair appeared in his eyes, and in an act of desperation, he turned to Han Li as he implored through voice transmission, "Save me, Fellow Daoist Han!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he remained unmoved.

It was already quite a struggle for him to carry Lu Yuqing, and if he were to accept another burden, then there was no way that he would be able to reach the top of the staircase.

The final glimmer of hope in Patriarch Cold Flame's faded at the sight of Han Li's expression, but in the next instant, a thought seemed to have suddenly occurred to him.

"Fellow Daoist Han, do you want the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts?" he asked in an urgent manner through voice transmission.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and suppressed his own excitement as he asked, "Do you have it?"

"No, but if you save me, I can take you to it," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. "Are you saying that the second half of the cultivation is in this Light Frost Palace?"

"That's right. The stone slab that contains the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts was actually something that I obtained after unintentionally triggering a restriction in the Light Frost Palace, and the main reason I came here this time is to secure the second half. That place is extremely secretive, so there's no way you'll be able to find it without me," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

Han Li didn't offer an immediate response, and a contemplative look appeared on his face as he pondered the validity of Patriarch Cold Flame's claims.

Judging from the conversation between Patriarch Cold Flame and Xiong Shan from earlier, both of them seemed to have reaped significant rewards the last time they visited the Light Frost Palace, and Patriarch Cold Flame hd once told him that he had obtained the Great Universe Origin Arts from a secret area, so it wasn't all that far-fetched to imagine that this was the secret area he had been referring to.

Furthermore, the stone slab that contained the first half of the cultivation had resonated with the starry light barrier earlier, indicating that there was definitely some connection between this place and the cultivation art.

With that in mind, Patriarch Cold Flame's claims were very likely to be true.

At this point, Xue Han had already scaled around a dozen steps, and he wasn't far away from Patriarch Cold Flame.

A panicked look appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly continued, "Are you suspecting that I'm lying to save myself? I'm willing to swear a vow on my life! If I'm lying to you, then let me be racked with inner demons and suffer the most painful death imaginable!"

Han Li finally made up his mind upon hearing this. "Alright, I'll believe you this time."

"Wait here for me," Han Li said as he set Lu Yuqing down onto the stone step, then began to make his way toward Patriarch Cold Flame.

Lu Yuqing immediately nodded in response and did as she was told, standing still on the stone step.

Descending the staircase was far easier than scaling it, and Han Li was able to reach Patriarch Cold Flame in the blink of an eye before picking him and immediately returning the same way that he had come from.

Xue Han was furious to see this, but Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame were still out of reach,and he didn't dare to unleash any further attacks, so he could only watch as the two of them sped away from him.

Meanwhile, a hint of derision flashed through Xiong Shan's eyes as he witnessed Han Li's actions.

Perhaps he could carry one person to the top, but in his eyes, carrying two people was no different from committing suicide for a mere True Immortal.

It didn't take long before Han Li reached the same step as before, and from there, he picked up Lu Yuqing as well.

With the burden of two people on his shoulders, his body instantly swayed slightly in an unsteady manner, much to the alarm of Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing.

Han Li took a deep breath, then began to chant an incantation as a layer of dazzling purplish-golden light appeared over his body.

Immediately thereafter, several true spirit projections emerged before vanishing into his body, and he instantly swelled to several times his original size, while a layer of purplish-golden scales emerged over his skin.

At the same time, two additional sets of heads and arms appeared over his body.

With these six arms, he picked up Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing, then began to scale the staircase once again, and compared with before, he hadn't slowed down in the slightest.

An incredulous look appeared on Xue Han's face seeing this, and his expression was mirrored by Xiong Shan, who took an astonished glance at Han Li before withdrawing his gaze and continuing his ascent.

"Your physical prowess is extraordinary, Fellow Daoist Han! I am truly in awe!" Patriarch Cold Flame praised as a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

"There's no need to flatter me, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice. "Also, I have a question for you."

A slightly awkward look appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face, and he prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Earlier, you referred to the person behind us as Xue Han. We were both there at the battle of the Holy Puppet Sect, could it be that this is the same Xue Han from back then?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he was silent for a moment before nodding in confirmation.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this. "In that case, are all of those other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators also adopting fake identities?"

"Fellow Daoist Han, for your own sake, it's best for you to know as little about this matter as possible," Patriarch Cold Flame replied in a meaningful voice.

"You're right, I was curious," Han Li replied with a smile, then asked no further questions.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already scaled quite a few more steps, and he was only 30 to 40 steps from reaching the top.

Xue Han had been left far behind, while Xiong Shan continued to make steady progress and was about to reach the endpoint.

Han Li was observing the steps up ahead with a solemn look on his face.

These remaining steps were going to be the most difficult ones to conquer, and he didn't dare to take them lightly at all.

Purplish-golden light continued to surge over his body as he steadily progressed up the staircase, and after scaling around a dozen more steps, he finally slowed down, having to take a short break with each step that he scaled.

The same was also happening to Xiong Shan.

The gravity here was astonishingly overbearing, to the point that even the air was buzzing audibly.

Han Li was looking slightly weary, and the purplish-golden light emanating from his body was also flashing incessantly.

Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame couldn't help but feel concerned upon seeing this.

"Fellow Daoist Han, how about you put one of us down and take the other to the top, then come back and repeat the process?" Patriarch Cold Flame suggested.

"That would waste too much time. Rest assured, this is still not too much for me to bear," Han Li replied, and as he did so, he scaled another step.

Xiong Shan's eyelids twitched slightly as he observed Han Li out of the corner of his eye, and he also took another step.

Han Li's body was trembling slightly, and he took a deep breath as he braced himself before taking another step.

The summit was already within reach, and the sooner he could reach the top, the sooner he would be able to commence his treasure hunt.

With that in mind, both he and Xiong Shan were making one final all-out effort.

The gravitational force on the final dozen or so steps was so formidable that it took the two of them a full 15 minutes to reach the top, and in the instant Han Li stepped onto the summit, the gravity instantly returned to normal, leaving him feeling as light as a feather.

As a result, he inadvertently sprang up over 100 feet before landing on the ground again.

Even though he had scaled the staircase as quickly as he could, he had been forced to withstand three times the normal gravity due to the two people that he was carrying, so Xiong Shan was able to reach the top before him.

He heaved a long sigh of relief, then turned back to find that Xue Han was still 50 to 60 steps away, glowering up at him with a furious expression.

Han Li withdrew his gaze before setting down Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing, then reverted back to his normal form as he cast his gaze forward.

Directly up ahead was a purple gate that was several hundred feet tall, on either side of which was a pillar with a golden dragon wound around it, and each of the golden dragons had a golden dragon bead clasped in its mouth.

There was no writing on the plaque above the gate, only an artwork of an ice that was quite rough around the edges, but also somehow extremely life-like.

On either side of the gate was a tall purple wall that stretched into the distance as far as the eyes could see.

Han Li took a glance at the purple gate and the walls on either side of it to find that they were completely ordinary construction that weren't giving off any spiritual power fluctuations, and the dragon beads clasped in the mouths of the two golden dragons were also just ordinary ornaments.

The only thing that caught Han Li's attention was the artwork of the vast ice field, which resembled the ice field that they had flown through on the way here.

Chapter 421: Infinite Worlds

While Han Li was inspecting the scene laid out before him, Xiong Shan had already arrived at the entrance, and he only stopped for a brief moment to inspect his surroundings before rushing into the palace.

Han Li turned back to take a glance at the stone staircase to find that Xue Han and the others were still on the way up, but he wasn't far away from reaching the top.

Hence, he also didn't hesitate any longer as he passed through the gate with Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame.

Upon arriving on the other side, Han Li caught sight of three enormous palatial buildings in the distance, all with glazed roof tiles and red painted walls, while statues of mythical beasts sat in a row atop the ridge of the roof.

The three palaces were situated in a triangular formation, with all of their main entrances facing the gate that Han Li had just passed through. They were built upon foundations that were several feet tall, making it appear as if they had been constructed atop raised platforms.

Between the gate and the palaces was a large white stone plaza that was completely empty.

Han Li swept his gaze across the plaza and the palaces, and the sense of familiarity that he had been feeling grew even more pronounced.

Before he had a chance to pinpoint the source of this feeling, Xiong Shan had already flown ahead toward the palaces.

However, as soon as he leaped into the air above the plaza, the space around him suddenly began to warp and ripple, immediately following which he vanished into thin air without any warning.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he began to inspect the plaza with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Through his spirit eye ability, he was able to see a layer of white mist over the white stone plaza that he had previously been unable to see with his naked eye. There were faint spiritual power fluctuations surging throughout the white mist, and it was clear that there was an extremely profound illusory array inside.

Han Li withdrew his gaze as he turned to glance at the gate behind him once again, and all of a sudden, he was struck by a sense of realization.

This is the Vast Glacial Palace... [1]

The staircase with the gravitational restriction, the illusory array on the plaza, the triangular formation of the palaces... This place was very similar to the Vast Glacial Palace that he had once visited.

Could it be that there was some type of connection between the two secret areas?

Right at this moment, a heavy thud suddenly rang out from the gate behind them, and the three of them turned to discover that Xue Han had reached the top of the staircase.

"We have to go!" Patriarch Cold Flame said in an urgent voice, then immediately flew toward the plaza, while Han Li and Lu Yuqing hurriedly followed along.

The three of them instantly vanished into thin air right before Xue Han burst through the gate, and he gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, but instead of charging blindly into the illusory array, he stopped at the edge of the plaza to inspect his surroundings.

While entering the illusory array, Han Li maintained his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he clearly saw himself fall into the misty array from above. In the next instant, the entire world spun around him, and he fell into another world.

"Steamed buns, warm and fluffy..."

"Top quality rouge, more fragrant than flowers and sweeter than honey..."

……

The sound of peddling rang out from the surrounding area, and Han Li found himself standing on a crowded street that was extremely lively and bustling.

Not far away from him stood a massive city gate, and near the foot of the gate was none other than Lu Yuqing, who was looking around with an uncertain expression.

Right at this moment, Patriarch Cold Flame emerged from the city gate, then hurriedly beckoned to Lu Yuqing and Han Li.

Han Li was just about to approach him when a loud voice rang out from behind him.

"Make way! Make way! I've got a batch of cakes fresh out of the steamer!"

Han Li reflexively stepped to the side upon hearing this, right as a short and stocky man quickly strode past him, carrying a pair of steamers and on either side of a carrying pole slung over his shoulder.

Only after the man had passed him by did Han Li realize that he wasn't the one being spoken to. Instead, the man had been speaking to a well-dressed young master.

It didn't take long before Han Li came to the realization that the three of them didn't seem to exist to the people in the illusion, and everyone was able to pass through their bodies like apparitions.

However, what was most striking to him was how realistic and lifelike this illusion was, even down to the fine details like the aroma of steamed cakes and the heat coming out of the steamers.

Even with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he was unable to see anything beyond the illusion presented to him.

Han Li made his way over to Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing, then remarked, "This illusion is extremely convincing. Even my spirit eye ability is unable to see through it at all."

"This is an array known as Infinite Worlds, and it's the most astonishing illusory array I've ever seen, bar none. The array is able to create entire illusory worlds, and if you don't know what you're doing, you could easily get lost in here and find yourself eternally trapped," Patriarch Cold Flame said.

"I see. By the way, have any of you seen Xiong Shan?" Han Li asked.

"The last time we came in here, we found ourselves on a primordial continent that was overrun by demon beasts, so that tells me that people who enter the array at different times are presented with different illusions. He came in ahead of us, and even though it was only by a slight margin, it's very likely that he's in another illusory world. Perhaps we'll only be able to see him again after we leave this array," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

"How did you two manage to get out of this array the first time?" Han Li asked.

"At the time, there were a total of eight people in our group, and some of them were extremely proficient in the art of the array. Through observing the stars at night, they were able to slowly piece together the way to exit the array, but even so, only four of us, including myself and Xiong Shan, were able to leave the array alive," Patriarch Cold Flame explained with a wry smile.

Han Li took a glance up at the sky to find that it was still early in the morning, so they were far from nighttime.

"Does the star observation method involve using the stars to determine the location of the bases of the array, then using the bases of the array to extrapolate the location of the array's exit?" Han Li asked.

"That's right," Patriarch Cold Flame replied with a slightly surprised expression. "It sounds like you're also a master in this art, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li paid no heed to his attempt at flattery as he took a glance up at the plaque above the city gate, then carefully inspected his surroundings.

"The plaque here says that this is the eastern city gate, but right now, it's still early in the morning, yet the sun is in the complete opposite direction of where it should be, so one of them has to be lying. Having said that, seeing as you were able to find your way out of the array last time thanks to the stars, it's more likely that the position of the sun is the more accurate point of reference. Hence, this should actually be the western city gate," Han Li said.

An enlightened look instantly appeared in the eyes of Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing upon hearing this.

"Now that we've determined our orientation, the next step is to observe the bases of the array. My spirit eye ability is unable to see through the array. How about yours, Fellow Daoist Lu? Can you see anything?" Han Li asked.

"I already gave it a try earlier, and as soon as I use my spirit eye ability, everything around me disappears, and all I can see is a boundless expanse of gray mist," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

"In that case, I only have one treasure that could possibly get us out of this bind," Han Li said, then swept a sleeve through the air overhead, and a giant golden eyeball instantly appeared up above amid a flash of golden light.

This golden eye wasn't actually a treasure. Instead, it was the Eye of Truth from his Mantra Treasured Axis, except he had concealed its full appearance.

He hadn't done this in order to conceal the fact that he was cultivating the laws of time. Instead, he simply didn't want them to see the 360 Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis. After all, this cultivation art was extremely renowned in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and there was a chance that Patriarch Cold Flame could've seen it before from somewhere else.

As soon as the golden eye emerged, Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame immediately detected the law fluctuations emanating from it, and the latter's expression instantly changed slightly, but out of respect, both of them refrained from using their spiritual sense to examine the so-called treasure.

Han Li was naturally quite pleased to see this, and he made a hand seal while closing his eyes so that he could see this space through the perspective of the Eye of Truth.

As soon as he did this, the entire world around him instantly vanished, and all that remained were near-transparent spiritual power fluctuations flowing through the air.

Everything was laid bare to him like the back of his hand, and after he had memorized everything that he had observed, he swept a hand through the air to withdraw the Eye of Truth.

"Did you find anything, Fellow Daoist Han?" Patriarch Cold Flame hurriedly asked as soon as Han Li opened his eyes.

"I've managed to find all of the bases of the array, but there could be some fake ones among them, so we'll have to rely on your memory of the direction that you took last time to find the right exit," Han Li replied.

Patriarch Cold Flame was ecstatic to hear this, and he immediately replied, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han, I'll do everything in my power to help."

[1]. For more information on the Vast Glacial Palace, please refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Vast_Glacial_Realm.

[Back]

Chapter 422: Replicating the Ploy

"If we go three kilometers down this street, there's an old house in an alley, and inside the yard of that house is a well, at the bottom of which is one of the bases of the array..."

Han Li began to lay out the locations of the bases of the array, while Patriarch Cold Flame listened with rapt focus while nodding or shaking his head in response, using his recollection to determine whether these bases were genuine or false.

In the real world, the white stone plaza that they were situated on wasn't very large at all, but this illusion was immeasurably massive. Starting from the well in the old house, the three of them passed through a wine shop and a brothel, and after a series of turns, they arrived in the backyard of a public office.

After that, they stepped onto a millstone to flip over a wall that was less than seven feet tall, arriving in a residential area in a quiet alley.

After emerging from the alley, they passed through seven or more streets before arriving at a school.

During this time, Lu Yuqing was gradually becoming more and more disoriented, as if she were about to lose herself in the array, but thankfully, Han Li was able to snap her back to her senses using a spiritual sense secret technique.

The tender voices of children reading aloud could be heard coming from inside the school, and outside the school gate was an elm tree that was over a century old. It wasn't very tall, but it was extremely thick, and at this moment, Han Li's trio was standing under its shadow.

"Last time, the exit of the array was the remains of a primordial demon beast, and it's completely different this time, so I can't be certain," Patriarch Cold Flame said in a hesitant voice as he looked at the old elm tree.

"The spiritual power fluctuations here are very different from what we've previously encountered, so I think this should be the place," Han Li said while observing the elm tree through his Eye of Truth.

He then cast an incantation seal toward the elm tree, and the Eye of Truth above his head trembled slightly, then released a burst of golden ripples.

The elm tree instantly brightened significantly upon contact with the golden ripples, and a blue vortex emerged within the golden light, through which a long passageway could be seen.

Patriarch Cold Flame approached the blue vortex and inspected it closely for a while, then turned back to Han Li and Lu Yuqing before nodding in confirmation as he said, "This should be the place. The passageway inside is almost identical as the one from last time."

"Alright, then let's go. We've already been delayed significantly here," Han Li said.

The Eye of Truth above his head faded as he spoke, and Patriarch Cold Flame led the way into the blue vortex, followed by Lu Yuqing, while Han Li brought up the rear.

A few minutes later, a burst of peculiar fluctuations spread through the air above the plaza, and Han Li's trio stumbled out into the open.

After taking a moment to steady himself, Patriarch Cold Flame immediately began looking around, but didn't find Xiong Shan.

"Save your energy. He's a master in arrays to begin with, and he's already passed through this array once before, so he's definitely already emerged ahead of us, and he should be on his way to the palaces by now," Han Li said, then turned around to look at plaza again with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

The mist here was churning violently, and that, coupled with the chaotic spiritual power fluctuations emanating out from within, clearly indicated that Xue Han had also made his way into the array.

"Let's get out of here while Xue Han is still trapped in the array. Take me to where the Great Universe Origin Arts is," Han Li said to Patriarch Cold Flame.

Patriarch Cold Flame nodded in response, then led the way toward the three palaces.

The central palace in the triangular formation was the one that was closest to Han Li's trio, and it was significantly taller than the two behind it.

In front of the palace were 10 golden pillars with countless runes inscribed upon them, and they had an extremely antiquated appearance.

The main gate of the palace was over 100 feet tall and entirely constructed from gold, and it was also riddled with runes. The left half of the gate was slightly ajar, and a section of its surface was charred black.

"This palace is just a trap. There's nothing inside aside from two puppets," Patriarch Cold Flame said, then skirted around the central palace as he made his way toward the palace on the right.

"Was the restriction on that palace destroyed the last time you came here?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"Do you recall how I said that a total of four of us emerged from the illusory array? The other two died in there," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

Lu Yuqing's face paled slightly upon hearing this, and the three of them remained silent as they made their way to the palace on the right.

This palace was smaller than the other one, but it was constructed using the same materials and in the same style. The only difference was that the gates of this palace were tightly shut, and the runes engraved upon it were also undamaged.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I found the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts in the rear hall of this palace, and the other half is also in there," Patriarch Cold Flame said.

"There must be some reason why you didn't secure both halves of the cultivation art at once last time, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The cultivation art is being guarded by an early-Golden Immortal Stage puppet," Patriarch Cold Flame replied with a nod.

A hint of suspicion appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Forgive me for being blunt, but if there's a Golden Immortal Stage puppet in there, then I don't see how it was possible for you to have stolen the first half of the cultivation art, particularly considering this was back before you cultivated the Great Universe Origin Arts."

"I understand your skepticism, Fellow Daoist Han. At the time, it was indeed true that I wasn't even able to withstand a single attack from the puppet. Hence, I didn't engage it in a direct battle. Instead, I released a few of my puppets to divert its attention, then used a concealment treasure to mask my aura before sneaking into the rear hall, and that was how I managed to obtain the first half of the cultivation art," Patriarch Cold Flame explained.

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Aside from some special puppets that possessed high levels of intelligence, like Daoist Xie, puppets were generally rather lackluster at sensing auras, so if Patriarch Cold Flame had an aura concealment treasure, then there was indeed a chance that he could've snuck past the puppet.

"However, as soon as I secured the stone slab that contained the first half of the Great Universe Origin Arts, the puppet immediately detected my presence, and I was severely injured after taking just a single punch from it. Fortunately, for some reason, it didn't chase me out of the hall, and that's the only reason I managed to survive," Patriarch Cold Flame recounted with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"What level of intelligence did the puppet possess?" Han Li asked.

"Even though I only had a very brief clash against it, I could tell that it didn't possess much intelligence at all. Otherwise, there's no way that it would've fallen for my crude ploy at distraction," Patriarch Cold Flame replied.

"In that case, it most likely didn't chase you out of the hall as its former owner restricted the area that it could move around in, thereby mandating it to remain in the hall to protect the cultivation art. Hence, it should be a simple task for us to secure the second half of the cultivation art," Han Li said.

"Are you suggesting that we use the same ploy again?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked in a rather hesitant voice.

"That's correct. However, I'll need your help in the execution," Han Li replied.

"Please tell me what you need me to do," Patriarch Cold Flame prompted.

Han Li gave Patriarch Cold Flame a rundown of his plan, and after listening to what Han Li had to say, Patriarch Cold Flame nodded in response to express his approval.

Lu Yuqing had also heard Han Li's plan in its entirety, and after a brief hesitation, she asked, "Why have you not involved me in your plan at all, Brother Han? Is it because you think I'm too weak to be of help?"

"That's not the case. Our plan is to infiltrate and steal, rather than confront and rob, so the fewer the number of people we can involve, the better. On top of that, the treasure that we're going after will only benefit Fellow Daoist Cold Flame and myself, so there's no reason for you to take the risk," Han Li explained.

"In that case, I'll just focus on staying out of your way," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame took a pill each, then took a moment to rest before making their way up the stone steps in front of the palace.

The runes on the palace gates were still completely intact, and the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from them indicated that the seal on the gates were still in operation. Han Li examined the runes momentarily to find that it wasn't a very advanced restriction, and he raised a hand to conjure up five balls of silver lightning, one on each fingertip, then abruptly thrust his palm toward the palace gates.

A loud thump rang out, and the gates of the palace instantly swung inward. A deep indentation had appeared on the spot on the gates where Han Li's palm had struck, and the runes there had all been scorched black by the balls of silver lightning.

At the center of the palace sat a copper humanoid puppet that was around 10 feet tall, and its eyes suddenly sprang open as a furious look appeared on its chiseled face as it bellowed in a thunderous voice, "All intruders must die!"

At the same time, its feet clanged against the ground as it rushed toward the palace gates.

Han Li took a glance inside the palace, then flicked his fingers through the air several times in succession, and streaks of yellow and azure light flew out of his fingertips before transforming into seven or eight giant ape puppets in a flash.

However, instead of attacking the copper puppet, all of the giant ape puppets split up and darted away in different directions as quickly as they could.

Chapter 423: Bait

The copper puppet immediately charged toward one of the ape puppets upon seeing this, while Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame exchanged a glance, then immediately took advantage of this opportunity to rush into the palace.

Han Li was using his Transient Guild mask to conceal his own aura, while Patriarch Cold Flame was achieving the same outcome through the use of a dark red robe, and they were rushing toward a giant screen at the rear of the palace.

However, as soon as they stepped into the palace, a string of loud booms rang out in rapid succession, and all of the giant ape puppets that Han Li had released were wiped out in an instant.

Immediately thereafter, the copper puppet stormed toward them before throwing a punch at both of them.

Han Li had his guard up for such an eventuality, so he was able to react quite calmly, crossing his arms to form a barrier in the face of the oncoming fist.

A resounding thump rang out, and both of his arms went numb as he slid along the ground before crashing heavily into the gate of the palace.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame had fared even worse. He seemed to have been caught completely off guard, and he tumbled through the air like a ragdoll before slamming into a wall, where he threw up a mouthful of blood.

After scrambling to his feet, he immediately turned to Han Li with a stunned expression before shaking his head.

It seemed that the circumstances were different from the last time he was here.

There was no time for Han Li to blame Patriarch Cold Flame for feeding him false information, and he yelled, "I'll deal with this thing, you go get the second half of the cultivation art!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately charged directly toward the copper puppet.

Han Li's original plan was for the giant ape puppets to keep the copper puppet distracted while Patriarch Cold Flame snuck in to steal the second half of the cultivation art, and Han Li would only be required to withstand a single attack from the puppet as Patriarch Cold Flame was getting away.

After that, both of them would be able to get away, while the puppet would remain trapped in the hall.

However, this was a complete deviation from the original plan, and he had no choice but to engage the puppet in a direct battle to buy time for Patriarch Cold Flame.

Patriarch Cold Flame immediately did as he was told, charging directly toward the rear hall while making no further attempt to conceal his own aura.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder how the puppet had suddenly developed such a high level of intelligence, and he was also worried that Han Li would think that he had intentionally fed him false information.

If Han Li were to arrive at that conclusion, then if they could obtain the Great Universe Origin Arts, Han Li was definitely not going to be pleased.

Having dealt with Han Li on multiple past occasions, Patriarch Cold Flame had developed an understanding of Han Li's character, and he knew just how unforgiving Han Li could be to those who betrayed or hurt him.

"How dare you!"

The copper puppet immediately swung around as soon as it sensed what Patriarch Cold Flame was doing, leaving Han Li behind to go after him.

Patriarch Cold Flame had only just reached the screen when the copper puppet swung a massive fist in his direction with astounding force.

He was just about to turn around to defend himself when Han Li's voice rang out from behind him.

"Focus on grabbing the cultivation art, I'll take care of the puppet!"

After a brief hesitation, he did as he was told, ignoring the fist that was hurtling toward him from behind as he rushed toward the screen.

Right as the copper puppet's fist was about to strike him in the back, a burst of lightning suddenly flashed over Han Li's body, and he flapped the Thunderstorm Wings on his back as he flew through the air, positioning himself between the puppet and Patriarch Cold Flame.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he stacked his hands together, one on top of the other, then thrust them both upward at once.

A pair of azure palm projections erupted forth, and they were also stacked on top of one another as they opposed the puppet's fist.

A burst of tremendous force erupted out of its fist, causing Han Li's robes to flap audibly around him, but he remained still and unyielding. However, his arms were bent, and a large section of his legs had also sunk deep into the ground.

The copper puppet was furious to see that its attack had been withstood, and a starry white cloud gathered around its fist as it lashed out at Han Li again.

Han Li's fighting spirit was also ignited, and he let loose a loud roar as the muscles on his body bulged, while a layer of golden fur appeared over his body. The tips of a pair of tusks also came protruding out of his mouth, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a Giant Mountain Ape.

He then threw a punch directly upward to oppose the oncoming fist of the copper puppet.

The two massive fists collided violently in mid-air, and a burst of dazzling white light appeared between them amid a resounding thunderclap. A burst of shockwaves that were visible even to the naked eye instantly swept through the air, causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

Han Li's arms bent slightly as he sank even deeper into the ground, while the copper puppet remained completely unmoved.

Even after drawing upon his Giant Mountain Ape bloodline, Han Li had still come off second best in a contest of strength against this puppet.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he pulled his legs out of the ground, then sprang up into the air, taking the initiative this time to lash out with a punch against the copper puppet. In response, the puppet lunged forward and retaliated with a punch of its own.

Han Li's entire body was enshrouded within a layer of dazzling blue light, and specks of dazzling starlight emerged on his chest and abdomen, while his aura also swelled drastically.

Specks of starlight also emerged over the copper puppet's body, and they had appeared in the exact same spots that corresponded to the profound acupoints cultivated through the Great Universe Origin Arts. However, the puppet had opened far more profound acupoints than Han Li, so the starpower that was swirling around its fist was naturally far more formidable than Han Li's.

Even before the two fists had collided, the outcome was already apparent.

However, right as the two fists were about to come into contact with one another, Han Li abruptly vanished into thin air before instantly reappearing behind the copper puppet, then threw a punch straight at the puppet's back.

A loud thump rang out as a vast expanse of starlight erupted out of the profound acupoints on the copper puppet's back, and it clashed violently against the starlight radiating from Han Li's fist, resulting in an eruption of blinding radiance.

The copper puppet's momentum was already shifting forward as a result of the punch it had thrown, and with Han Li landing a blow on it from behind, it immediately stumbled involuntarily forward.

Its enormous fist also slammed into the ground with a deafening boom as a result, and the entire palace shuddered violently as dust came raining down from the ceiling.

A bottomless rift that was over 100 feet in length had been smashed into the ground, and Han Li was very thankful for his own decision not to fight fire with fire.

Right before the clash was about to take place, he had reversed his Mantra Treasured Axis to accelerate himself, thereby allowing him to evade the copper puppet's punch. Otherwise, at the very least, he would've been missing an arm by now.

What he found most surprising was that the copper puppet was also able to use starpower, and it seemed to have opened up an even higher number of profound acupoints than him.

Could it be that it had also cultivated the Great Universe Origin Arts?

Before Han Li had a chance to ponder this matter any further, an urgent voice suddenly rang out from the rear hall. "I've got the cultivation art, Fellow Daoist Han! Let's get out of here!"

Immediately thereafter, Patriarch Cold Flame emerged from behind the screen, holding a gray stone slab aloft. The stone slab was riddled with countless antiquated characters, and it was clearly the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts.

Han Li immediately nodded in response, and the two of them arrived at the entrance of the palace almost at the exact same moment.

Han Li raised a hand to push the palace gates open, yet right at this moment, the entire palace suddenly began to tremble violently, and all of the runes engraved upon the entire structure joined together like squirming worms, as if they had sprung to life.

At the same time, a purplish-golden light barrier began to spread over the walls, the ceiling, and the ground, encapsulating the entire space within the palace.

An alarmed look immediately appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon seeing this.

At this point, Han Li had already reverted back to his human form, and he raised a hand before thrusting his palm toward the palace gates.

Five balls of silver lightning emerged over his fingertips as he attacked the purplish-golden light barrier, and a loud crackling sound rang out as countless antiquated runes emerged over the light barrier, accompanied by arcs of lightning that scattered the balls of silver lightning around Han Li's fingertips.

The purplish-golden lightning surged forth in a frenzy, devouring all of the scattered silver lightning, and Han Li couldn't help but draw a sharp breath as a numb sensation spread through his entire body.

At this point, the copper puppet had already returned to its feet, and it declared in a cold voice, "Unforgivable!"

At the same time, a layer of murky white light flashed through its eyes, and the purplish-golden light radiating from its body also gradually dimmed while starlight surged out of its profound acupoints, giving its entire body a translucent appearance.

In the wake of these changes, the aura that it was giving off was also elevated drastically, reaching the pinnacle of the early-Golden Immortal Stage.

"I swear I didn't lie to you, Fellow Daoist Han! None of this happened the last time I was here!" Patriarch Cold Flame hurriedly said in an urgent voice.

"I believe you," Han Li replied in a concise fashion.

Patriarch Cold Flame was quite taken aback to hear this, and he was temporarily at a loss for words.

"The restriction outside the palace isn't even comparable to the one inside it. Don't you find that strange?" Han Li asked while keeping a close eye on the copper puppet.

An enlightened look instantly appeared in Patriarch Cold Flame's eyes upon seeing this.

"This palace was never designed to keep people out. Instead, it's to ensure that those who come in aren't able to get away. Just like the other palace, this is also a trap, and perhaps the Great Universe Origin Arts is being used as bait."

Chapter 424: Collaborative Strike

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li speculated, "Perhaps it was because too much time had passed, and some issues arose in the array, so when you came here last time, the array wasn't completely activated, nor had this puppet completely awakened. I presume that's how you were able to escape with your life."

A hint of lingering fear welled up in Patriarch Cold Flame's heart, but at the same time, he was also very thankful for his own good fortune. Before he had a chance to reply, Han Li suddenly yelled in an urgent voice, "Here it comes!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, Han Li had already vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared directly above the copper puppet's head, then made a peculiar hand seal before thrust a palm directly downward.

A burst of ripples spread through the space beneath his palm, and a shimmering azure longsword emerged out of thin air in a flash, then flew down toward the copper puppet's head.

The sound of crackling lightning rang out as a burst of piercing golden light appeared over the azure longsword, and arcs of formidable golden lightning emerged over the entire sword before it crashed heavily down upon the top of the copper puppet's head.

A resounding boom rang out as a golden lightning vortex that was several dozen feet tall appeared within the palace, and arcs of golden lightning were springing out of the vortex in all directions to strike the surrounding purplish-golden light barrier.

Patriarch Cold Flame was peering intently into the lightning vortex, but he was unable to see the copper puppet at all, and he could only sense the vast and violent power contained within the golden lightning.

Is it dead?

All of a sudden, a strange sound rang out from within the golden lightning vortex, and a grim look instantly appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon hearing this.

Immediately thereafter, a thick and strong arm that was as fair and translucent as jade suddenly erupted upward out of the lightning vortex, then clenched threw a vicious punch at the azure longsword up above.

A resounding boom rang out as a white cloud of starlight erupted out of the fist with countless specks of blue light flashing within it, presenting a stunning sight that resembled a bright and starry sky.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of incredibly formidable power erupted forth, and layers upon layers of white light surged outward in all directions, expanding the golden lightning vortex further and further.

At the same time, the blue stars within the white light were snuffed out one after another as a destructive aura spread emanated through the air.

A thunderous roar rang out as the white light exploded once again, and the golden lightning vortex was finally torn apart, with countless arcs of golden lightning flying in all directions to strike the surrounding purplish-golden light barrier.

At the same time, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords up above was also sent flying back through the air, skidding across the purplish-golden light barrier on the ceiling to raise a trail of sparks before being repelled downward, where it was then it caught by Han Li right before it could pierce into the ground.

The azure longsword was trembling violently, and as a result, Han Li's arm was trembling slightly as well.

His complexion had also paled noticeably, while his breathing had become a little ragged.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he cast his gaze toward the copper puppet, upon which he discovered that it had taken on a completely different form. Its entire body had taken on the same hue and translucency as green jade, and there were specks of blue light all over its body.

At this moment, there were still some faint arcs of lightning flashing over its body, but it paid no heed to this at all as it took a step forward, then abruptly sped through the air as a blurry streak of light, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Instead of lashing out with a punch, it sliced its palm through the air in a chopping motion this time, lashing out at Han Li's neck with tremendous power.

It was so incredibly fast that Han Li didn't have a chance to defend himself at all, and a dull thump rang out as he was sent flying into the purplish-golden light barrier in a dizzy and disoriented fashion.

A vast expanse of lightning instantly erupted out of the light barrier, and Patriarch Cold Flame immediately called out to him in alarm.

His first instinct was to rush to Han Li's aid, but after taking a glance at the copper puppet, he decided to remain still on the spot.

However, the puppet didn't continue to pursue Han Li after striking him down. Instead, it turned to Patriarch Cold Flame with a pair of emotionless silver eyes.

A chill immediately ran down Patriarch Cold Flame's spine, and he took a glance at the gray stone slab in his hand before hurriedly tossing it away as if it were a hot potato.

It was unclear whether this was intentional, but the stone slab ultimately landed right beside Han Li, who had only just slammed down onto the ground after crashing into the purplish-golden light barrier.

There were plumes of white smoke rising up from his entire body, and many parts of his robes were also charred black.

He rose to his feet, using his azure longsword as a crutch, picking up the gray stone slab in the process, and after taking a quick glance at the stone slab, a pleased smile appeared on his face as he stowed it away.

The copper puppet seemed to have been completely infuriated upon seeing this, and it immediately sped directly toward Han Li once again as a blurry streak of light.

Once again, it lashed out in a chopping motion, and the white light on the palm of his hand took a serrated form as it thrust its hand directly toward Han Li's heart.

This time, Han Li was already prepared, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

All of the active Time Dao Runes on it lit up in unison, releasing a layer of golden ripples that encompassed the area around him.

As soon as the copper puppet's arm pierced into the golden ripples, it instantly became extremely slow, as if it had been thrust into quicksand.

However, all of the specks of blue light on the puppet's body then suddenly grew even brighter, and all of the white radiance emanating from its body also surged toward its arm in a frenzy.

The light radiating from the copper puppet's hand instantly turned from white to blue, and it also expanded to around twice its original size as it tore viciously at the surrounding golden ripples.

The golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis were starting to become a little unstable, and the puppet's arm was beginning to travel forward again. It still wasn't very fast, but the time-slowing effect of the Mantra Treasured Axis was undeniably being countered, and this was something that had never happened before.

"Are you still not ready, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked while struggling to support his Mantra Treasured Axis.

"I'm ready!" Brother Xie replied, and as soon as its voice trailed off, a burst of golden radiance suddenly erupted out of Han Li's body, then expanded drastically into a flood of golden lightning that filled the entire palace in the blink of an eye.

It was as if the entire area had been inundated by a wave of golden lightning.

Ever since entering the palace, Patriarch Cold Flame had already been astonished so many times that he was beginning to feel a little numb.

At this moment, his mouth was slightly agape, and there was a dazed look in his eyes as he clung onto an azure bianzhong with all his might, conjuring up an azure light barrier to protect himself.

Within the vast expanse of golden lightning, a giant golden crab emerged, and its enormous shell was grinding against the purplish-golden light barrier beneath the ceiling, sending lightning of two different colors erupting in all directions.

A giant crab pincer shot out of the golden lightning, then snapped itself around the copper puppet's waist, and two bursts of crisscrossing golden lightning flashed past amid a rumbling thunderclap.

The purplish-golden light barrier around the palace was instantly torn apart before fading away, and a giant rift was also sliced into the walls and the ceiling of the palace.

Immediately thereafter, all of the golden lightning within the palace gradually began to subside back into the golden crab's body, and it transformed into Daoist Xie's yellow-robed human form.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I'm afraid all of the Immortal Origin Stones that you gave me earlier have been used up in that attack," Daoist Xie said as he took a glance at the copper puppet, which had been snapped into two.

"That's fine, I'll give you some more a bit later. You have my thanks, Brother Xie," Han Li replied as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis.

"There's no need to thank me. This puppet is quite formidable, and even though its intelligence was intentionally suppressed during the refinement process, its very similar in power to a Golden Immortal Stage Profound Immortal, so unless we joined forces, it wouldn't have been so easy to defeat it," Daoist Xie replied, and he alluding to Han Li that it was best to keep the remains of the puppet rather than let it go to waste.

"I'll be sure to take it with me. Do you have a way to repair it once we leave this place?" Han Li asked.

"I didn't hold back at all in that attack, and I've already damaged its core, so it's hard to say whether it can be repaired or not," Daoist Xie replied in an ambiguous fashion.

At this point, the copper puppet had already reverted back to its original form, and it had been snapped all the way from its left shoulder to its right oblique. A dark golden metal ball could be seen exposed in its severed abdomen, and the ball had been severed as well.

A slightly forlorn look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he knew that it couldn't be helped. After all, this was a Golden Immortal Stage opponent, and holding back could've easily spelled death.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Patriarch Cold Flame, who was still frozen in shock, then said, "If there's nothing else you need from me, then I'm going back."

After that, he flew back up Han Li's sleeve as a streak of golden light, following which Han Li stowed the two halves of the copper puppet away with a sweep of his sleeve before making his way toward the rear hall.

Patriarch Cold Flame continued to stare at Han Li as he slumped to the ground, and his entire body was already drenched in cold sweat.

Only now did he come to understand just how massive the gap between himself and Han Li was, and how foolish his earlier actions had been.

Han Li made his way around the giant screen, where he was greeted by the sight of a hidden doorway that could fit two people through at once.

He strode through the doorway to arrive in a completely isolated and windowless space, but it wasn't dark despite the lack of natural light as a layer of luminescent stone powder had been painted over the walls, giving off a faint glow that illuminated the room.

At the very center of the rear hall was a small copper platform that was only around three feet tall, with complex patterns engraved onto its surface.

On the upper face of the platform were two indentations that were the exact same shape and size as the Great Universe Origin Arts stone slabs, and there were also runes engraved inside.

Chapter 425: Treasure Hunt

Strewn across the ground behind the copper platform in a haphazard fashion were seven or eight black wooden chests with talismans adhered to them.

It was clear that Patriarch Cold Flame hadn't been able to take what was in the chests on the previous two occasions that he was here.

Han Li swept his gaze across his surroundings before striding forward, and a layer of azure light appeared over his hand as he swept his palm over one of the chests, upon which the talismans adhered to its surface instantly disintegrated into dust.

He then opened the wooden chest, and a faint smile immediately appeared on his face as the chest's contents were revealed.

Inside the chest were orderly layers of palm-sized blue crystals that totaled in excess of 100, and they were none other than Starheaven Stones.

With so many Starheaven Stones at his disposal, cultivating the rest of the Great Universe Origin Arts was going to be much easier.

Han Li suppressed the excitement in his heart as he opened all of the remaining wooden chests as well, and he discovered that all of them were also filled with Starheaven Stones, taking the total tally to close to 1,000.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li stowed all of the wooden chests away into the storage bracelet on his wrist, and only after examining the rear hall to ensure that there was nothing else left inside did he exit through the secret doorway.

As he passed by the giant screen, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he stopped in his tracks.

He raised his head to look at the starry night sky depicted on the screen, and a peculiar feeling suddenly welled up in his heart. After a brief moment of contemplation, he pressed a palm against the screen and stowed it away as well.

He then strode past Patriarch Cold Flame without even sparing him a glance before exiting the palace, upon which he was immediately greeted by Lu Yuqing with an anxious look on her face.

"Thank goodness you're finally back," Lu Yuqing hurriedly said in a relieved voice.

"Is something wrong?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Just now, a loud commotion started over on the plaza," Lu Yuqing replied as she pointed in the direction of the white stone plaza.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a resounding boom rang out in that direction, following which a pillar of crimson fire erupted into the sky.

"It looks like Xue Han and the others are already breaking through the array. We have to get out of here," Han Li said.

"We've already completely diverted off our original route, and this area is outside of the map that I have. How are we going to get back?" Lu Yuqing asked in a concerned voice.

Han Li offered no response as he sprang up into the sky, then inspected his surroundings briefly from his new vantage point before descending back onto the ground.

"At this point, we'll just have to take one step at a time and adapt with the circumstances. There are quite a few palaces and pavilions on the mountain behind these three palaces, and I'm sure there are some treasures waiting to be found there," Han Li said.

Lu Yuqing nodded in response.

Right at this moment, Patriarch Cold Flame emerged from within the palace, then asked in a slightly uneasy voice, "Fellow Daoist Han, can I continue to follow you for the rest of the trip?"

"I'm willing to let what you did earlier slide, but don't take my kindness as a sign of weakness. I think it would be best for us to split up and go our separate ways from here onward," Han Li replied in a cold voice.

Right as they were speaking, another resounding boom rang out from the plaza, and two mow pillars of light erupted into the heavens.

Patriarch Cold Flame knew that he was at fault, so he made no attempt to argue as he replied, "Fellow Daoist Han, I no longer harbor any delusions of getting my hands on the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts. All I ask is that you take me with you. If I go off on my own now, even if we set aside whether I'll be able to make it out of this secret area, I'll surely be killed if I run into Xue Han and the others."

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and after a brief silence, he replied, "Alright, but I'll only take you out of this area. Once we're out of here, we go our separate ways."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han," Patriarch Cold Flame said as he extended a respectful bow, but Han Li stepped away to sidestep the bow, then turned and departed with Lu Yuqing in tow.

Patriarch Cold Flame heaved a forlorn sigh as he hurriedly followed along, and the three of them made their way down a mountain path, which was lined with palaces and pavilions of different sizes, but they were far smaller than the previous three.

Han Li knew that the layout of this place was very similar to that of the Vast Glacial Palace, so there was a very good chance that there would be a spirit medicine garden on the rear mountain. He was initially planning to go straight there, but he was feeling a little hesitant after inspecting the nearby buildings with his spiritual sense.

Lu Yuqing could tell that Han Li was rather distracted, and she asked, "What's wrong, Brother Han?"

"Almost all of the buildings here have restrictions set up in them, but the quality of the restrictions vary drastically. Some are extremely crude, while others are quite advanced, indicating that there are treasures sealed inside, so it would be a real pity not to explore these buildings," Han Li mused.

A hint of concern appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes upon hearing this, and she said, "Brother Han, we still have Xue Han and the others hot on our heels, so..."

"It's fine. Even if they've found a way to break the array, it'll still take them some time to break out. On top of that, they'll be sure to be tempted into exploring the three palaces back there, so they won't come after us anytime soon," Han Li said.

A hint of excitement appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes upon hearing this, and she said, "Alright, in that case, I suppose we could explore this area for a while."

Just like everyone else who had entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, Lu Yuqing was also keen to secure some powerful treasures and useful resources for herself, so she was naturally enthused by the prospect of being able to do some exploring.

"Let's split up and search for treasures independently, then meet back up here in an hour. If anything happens during that time, we meet back up early and get out of here," Han Li instructed.

Lu Yuqing gave an affirmative response, then immediately flew away in a certain direction.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame was standing off to the side with an uneasy look on his face, but he didn't dare to say anything.

Han Li took a cold glance at him, then flew away in the opposite direction of Lu Yuqing.

Only after Han Li's departure did Patriarch Cold Flame heave a faint sigh, then flip his hand over to produce a jade slip, upon which a gleeful smile appeared on his face.

This jade slip contained the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts. As it turned out, he had made this replica of the cultivation art in secret while Han Li had been locked in battle against the copper puppet, so he had obtained what he had come here for, after all.

With that in mind, he stowed the jade slip away, then also flew away in a certain direction.

……

Han Li drifted down onto a small bluestone plaza in front of a three-story pavilion.

After landing on the plaza, he examined the pavilion to find that there was a small golden bell hanging from each of the eight corners of its octagonal roof. This pavilion had to have been standing for countless years, yet the bells weren't displaying even the slightest sign of rust or discoloration.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a gentle breeze, which swept over the pavilion, causing all of the 24 bells on the pavilion's three rooves to sway and chime.

The sound was very pleasing to the ears initially, but Han Li quickly noticed that something wasn't quite right.

The chiming of the bells should've gradually subsided over time, but instead, it was only growing louder and louder, until eventually, each strike was as loud as the strike of a gong, striking Han Li with a sense of dizziness and disorientation.

It seems that these 24 bells are a set of spiritually disruptive treasures... How intriguing...

He had already cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique to the fourth level, and even he fell prey to the bells' disruptive effect for a moment, so he could only imagine how susceptible others would be.

In a battle, a moment of disruption was often enough to decide the outcome, and with that in mind, Han Li was tempted to take these bells for himself.

However, as he reached out to draw the bells toward him, he discovered that they were completely immovable.

A puzzled look appeared on his face as he carefully examined the entire pavilion again, and only then did he realize that the entire three-floor pavilion was a part of the set of bell treasures.

Furthermore, he speculated that the bell chime sound was only the tip of the iceberg when it came to the pavilion's full power. There was most likely much worse to come inside the pavilion, and if one were to grow complacent, thinking that they had weathered the storm after withstanding the bell chime restriction, then they would be sure to suffer once they entered the pavilion.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release Daoist Xie.

"Why have you summoned me again so soon? Have you encountered some trouble?" Daoist Xie asked.

"I do have to trouble you for something, Brother Xie," Han Li said in a slightly apologetic voice.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Daoist Xie prompted.

"This pavilion in front of us is a spirit treasure of an extremely high caliber, but it'll take me some time to refine it, so in the meantime, please search the nearby buildings for treasures. Regardless of what you find, I'll compensate you with Immortal Origin Stones," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie hesitated momentarily, then nodded in response.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he flipped a hand over to produce a yellow gourd before handing it to Daoist Xie as he said, "You can send out the Dao Warriors inside to aid you in your search."

"That's a good idea," Daoist Xie said as he accepted the ground from Han Li, then vanished from the spot as a flash of lightning.

Meanwhile, Han Li began to focus on the task at hand, channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique as he strode into the pavilion.

This was clearly no ordinary pavilion, and its core was definitely inside. Hence, in order to refine it, the only way was to enter the pavilion itself.

Chapter 426: Mural

Around 15 minutes later, the door of the three-floor pavilion abruptly sprang open, and Han Li emerged from inside with an elated expression.

He then turned around and made a hand seal, and a vast expanse of golden light suddenly emerged over the entire pavilion.

There were countless runes flashing within the golden light, and all of a sudden, the pavilion shrank down to only the size of a lantern before being stowed away into Han Li's storage bracelet.

This treasure is more than powerful enough to trap a mid-True Immortal cultivator, and it can maybe even trap a late-True Immortal cultivator who hasn't cultivated any spiritual enhancement secret techniques, but it won't work on anyone beyond that. Having said that, I can use it in conjunction with other treasures, so it can still be quite useful.

Right as these thoughts were running through his mind, bursts of rumbling suddenly began to ring out in the distance, and he hurriedly turned to discover that the sound was coming from the three palaces. Clearly, Xue Han and the others had begun invading the palaces.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out in his mind. "Fellow Daoist Han, come here right now."

He immediately responded to the call, springing up into the air, and before long, he had landed in a weed-infested courtyard.

Several Dao Warriors were in the process of searching for treasures in the side room of the residence, but the doors of the main room were wide open, and Daoist Xie could be seen inside.

Han Li made his way into the room to find that Daoist Xie was staring at a wall in the room.

"I didn't find any noteworthy treasures in here, but this mural is quite interesting," Daoist Xie said without even turning around.

Han Li immediately cast his gaze toward the surrounding walls upon hearing this, and he discovered that they were covered in vibrant and colorful murals.

The things drawn in the mural varied drastically, and the scenes depicted were also extremely chaotic, with severely ravaged landscapes that were overrun with lava, ferocious storms of lightning and fire, and it truly painted a doomsday-like scene.

As Han Li continued to observe the mural, he felt as if the depicted scenes were beginning to move. The lava on the ground was flowing, the fireballs in the sky were beginning to descend, and lightning was flashing in the dark clouds up above.

Many figures dressed in all types of attire were also flying through the air, performing all types of different actions, such as making hand seals, raising weapons, swinging fists...

Aside from the battling cultivators, there were also many mountainous beasts depicted on the mural, all of which were extremely fearsome in appearance and possessed various different formidable abilities.

Having dabbled in the 12 Awakening Transformations, Han Li knew many species of powerful ancient beasts, but he wasn't able to identify even a single one of the beasts depicted in the mural.

The mural depicted an immortal battle of an enormous scale, and even though Han Li was only witnessing the battle through the mural, he felt as if he were situated directly in the battle, and a chill instantly ran down his spine.

However, at the same time, he couldn't help but feel a little perplexed.

All of the figures on the mural with clearly visible features seemed to belong to the same camp, yet all of their enemies had blurry facial features, as if they were enshrouded in layers of gray mist.

They appeared to be cultivators, but also somehow different.

"Do you know when the battle depicted on this mural took place, Fellow Daoist Han?" Daoist Xie suddenly asked.

Han Li shook his head in response. "I don't. Do you, Brother Xie?"

He was thinking back to all of the historical records he had seen in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but he couldn't think of any battle that corresponded with this one.

"I don't know, either. I just thought these murals were very strange, so I wanted you to come and take a look," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li had thought that he would be able to get some answers from Daoist Xie, so he was rather disappointed to hear this response, but this wasn't an important matter anyway.

After that, he searched through some more buildings with Daoist Xie and gathered quite a few treasures of different calibers. There weren't many that he could use, but he could certainly sell them for a lot of Immortal Origin Stones once he left the immortal manor.

Once the hour was up, Han Li stowed Daoist Xie and his Dao Warriors away, then returned to the same place as before.

Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame were already waiting there, and the former's eyes were sparkling with excitement, while the latter wore a neutral expression, making it impossible to tell what he was thinking.

After reuniting, the three of them made their way toward the spirit medicine garden on the rear mountain.

Before long, the three of them descended onto a plot of land, right in front of a square garden that was over 10 acres in area.

The garden was surrounded by walls that were roughly 40 to 50 feet tall, constructed from some type of blue crystalline material.

The material was giving off a layer of watery blue light interspersed with specks of starry light that presented a very pleasant sight to behold.

Han Li swept his gaze over the walls, and a hint of surprise immediately appeared on his face.

He had identified this blue crystal to be an extremely rare type of material called the Heavenly Crystal Rock and it could be used to refine spirit treasures. It wasn't particularly difficult to find in the outside world, but such an enormous quantity of it in one place was still a very rare sight, and using it as bricks to construct walls for a garden was a display of extreme opulence.

At each corner of the walls stood a thick stone pillar that was riddled with complex array patterns, and dazzling starlight was radiating from the pillar, forming a thick starry light barrier in the air that encompassed the entire garden.

Countless star designs were flashing over the light barrier as if they were playing out the movements of the celestial bodies in the sky, presenting a profound sight to behold.

From the outside, Han Li could see that there were all types of spirit plants in the garden, and there was a faint pleasant fragrance coming out of the garden that even the starry light barrier wasn't able to contain.

An elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes, but as he took a closer look at the starry light barrier, his brows furrowed slightly in dismay.

This light barrier appeared rather similar to the starry light barrier that had to be bypassed in order to enter the Light Frost Palace, but this one appeared even more profound, so it was most likely going to be even more difficult to break.

"This restriction is most likely going to be very difficult to break through conventional means. Having said that, the Great Five-elemental True Light that you and Fellow Daoist Xiong unleashed earlier should be perfect for breaking this restriction," Han Li said as he turned to Patriarch Cold Flame.

A slightly awkward look appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon hearing this, and he said, "While I do know the mantra for the Great Five-elemental True Light, five extremely pure five-elemental spirit treasures are required to unleash it, and I only have spirit treasures of the fire and earth attributes, so..."

"That's not a problem, I just so happen to have a spirit treasure of each of the remaining three elements, and they should be at a sufficient level of purity for the task," Han Li replied as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a trio of treasures, namely a golden ring, a green wooden sword, and a blue badge.

All three spirit treasures were emanating astonishingly bright spiritual light, and they weren't inferior in the slightest compared with the five spirit treasures that were previously used.

Han Li had slain countless cultivators in the Immortal Realm, most of whom were True Immortals, so he naturally had a large collection of high-caliber spirit treasures.

"You are truly a wealthy man, Fellow Daoist Han. In that case, there won't be any further issues. It's just that the mantra for the Great Five-elemental True Light is a little difficult to grasp, but I'm sure it won't be a problem for someone of your wisdom," Patriarch Cold Flame said.

He flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip as he spoke, then handed it to Han Li, who accepted the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The mantra in the jade slip wasn't very long, but just as Patriarch Cold Flame described, it was quite difficult to comprehend.

Han Li quickly memorized the entire thing, then sat down on the spot and closed his eyes to mull over what he had seen.

"Let's keep a lookout for Brother Han, Senior Cold Flame," Lu Yuqing suggested to Patriarch Cold Flame, to which the latter nodded in response.

Both of them then backed away to give Han Li some space while scouring their surroundings for any potential hazards.

Close to two hours passed by before Han Li abruptly opened his eyes, then rose to his feet.

Both Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame immediately turned to him upon sensing this, while Han Li began to chant an incantation while pointing a finger at the three spirit treasures in front of him.

The three treasures instantly rose up into the sky, with each of them releasing a ball of dazzling light, and as Han Li made a hand seal, the three balls of light began to come together.

Patriarch Cold Flame was astonished to see this.

"Have you already mastered the mantra, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"I once cultivated a five-elemental ability in the past, so I was able to grasp this one a little faster than expected," Han Li explained.

He was naturally referring to the Divine Essencefused Light. Five-elemental secret techniques were notoriously profound and difficult to master due to having to incorporate and balance five elements at once, but the mantra for the Divine Essencefused Light was rather similar to this one, and that was why it hadn't been all that difficult for him to master this mantra.

"You really are full of surprises, Fellow Daoist Han," Patriarch Cold Flame chuckled, seemingly already accustomed to expecting the unexpected when it came to Han Li.

He didn't waste any more time with words as he flipped a hand over to produce the crimson bowl and the yellow seal before also chanting an incantation, and the pair of spirit treasures instantly flew up into the sky while radiating dazzling spiritual light that fused with the spiritual light emanating from Han Li's trio of spirit treasures.

Chapter 427: Medicine Garden

Under the collective efforts of Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame, countless five-colored runes surged out of the spiritual light radiating from the five spirit treasures, and they began to revolve incessantly around the spirit treasures.

The five balls of spiritual light quickly intertwined and fused together to form an enormous ball of five-colored light, within which the five spirit treasures had formed a circle and were rapidly revolving.

With each cycle of revolution, the five-colored ball of light would swell slightly, and it quickly reached over 1,000 feet in size, radiating dazzling five-colored light that illuminated the entire heavens, while Lu Yuqing looked on with a dazed and awestruck expression.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame both raised a hand in unison to cast an incantation seal toward the ball of light, and a pillar of five-colored instantly shot out of the ball of light to strike the starry light barrier.

The two fused together, and the starry light barrier remained completely unaffected, but if one were to gaze upon this scene from afar, it would appear as if there were a five-colored passageway connected to a vast starry sky.

As Han Li and Patriarch Cold Flame continued to chant the incantation for the Great Five-elemental True Light, the pillar of five-colored light instantly became even brighter, and countless five-colored arrows that were each around 10 feet in length took shape within the pillar of light before raining down upon the starry light barrier.

The still surface of the starry light barrier instantly began to tremble violently, and balls of five-colored light appeared over its surface amid a string of resounding booms.

The light radiating from the starry light barrier quickly began to fade, and it was whittled down at a rapid rate, much to Han Li's surprise and suspicion.

The starry light barrier appeared to be extremely profound, so why was it so inept?

Despite his surprise, he continued to make a string of hand seals, and more five-colored arrows came raining down from the pillar of five-colored light.

As time passed, the starry light barrier was whittled down further and further, and after only 15 minutes, only a thin layer of it was left.

Han Li immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and Patriarch Cold Flame did the same thing at almost the exact same time.

The pillar of five-colored instantly brightened as all of the countless arrows within it fused as one wot form a giant arrow that was over 1,000 feet in size, with streaks of five-colored light surging all over its surface.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the giant five-colored arrow came crashing down onto the starry light barrier, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as the starry light barrier finally crumbled into countless pieces.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, and the five spirit treasures in the sky instantly split up, with his three spirit treasures flying back up his sleeve, while Patriarch Cold Flame recovered his two spirit treasures as well.

With the starry light barrier out of the way, a burst of rich spiritual qi and medicinal aroma instantly began to waft through the air.

Han Li immediately flew down, followed closely by Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing.

The three of them landed in the garden in quick succession, and as soon as they did so, balls of starlight abruptly emerged from the stone pillars situated in the four corners of the garden, and they released streaks of spiritual light that began to intertwine in mid-air.

In the span of just a couple of seconds, the starry light barrier had taken shape above the garden once again, except it was only a thin layer this time.

More streaks of starlight were being released out of the stone pillars to support the light barrier, and it was gradually becoming thicker and more resilient.

Han Li took a glance up at the starry light barrier, and his brows furrowed slightly as if he had realized something, but he then shook his head and withdrew his gaze before turning his attention to the medicine garden around him.

The garden had been split up into different sections that were separated by fences crafted from a type of green jade material, and each area was enshrouded in restrictions of different colors, with all manners of different spirit plants growing inside them.

Han Li cast his gaze toward a section of the garden beside him that was several dozen feet in size.

This section was enshrouded under a red restriction with dozens of red spirit plants growing inside. The spirit plants were around two feet tall each, and they had ovular leaves with a bright red palm-sized flower at the top of each one, resembling a ball of scorching fire.

Even through the restriction, Han Li could still detect the formidable fire-attribute spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the plan.

These are Wild Flame Herbs...

This was a type of renowned fire-attribute spirit plant that could be used to refine some top-grade fire-attribute pills and even fire-attribute dao pills, and it was extremely sought after for the fact that upon reaching 100,000 years of age, there was a very high likelihood that a hint of fire-attribute law powers would emerge within the plant.

There were very few spirit plants that could produce law powers on their own, and most of them had to be hundreds of thousands of years of age before reaching that stage, so the Wild Flame Herb was very much an anomaly.

The law powers produced by this plant weren't particularly formidable, but it could be used for dao pill refinement, and the age requirement was also quite low, so it was extremely sought after among all Dao Pill Masters.

Furthermore, judging from the size of these Wild Flame Herbs, they had to have been at least 300,000 to 400,000 years old, so the fire-attribute law powers that they harbored were naturally going to be far more formidable than in 100,000-year-old specimens.

If he could mature them to 500,000 years of age with his Heaven Controlling Vial, then he would have a batch of priceless fire-attribute spirit plants on his hands.

However, instead of scrambling to pick these spirit plants, Han Li turned and made his way toward the other sections of the garden. It appeared that no one had been here for a very long time, so there had to be many spirit plants here more valuable than Wild Flame Herbs.

Meanwhile, Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing had also gone in different directions to search for spirit plants.

A short while later, Han Li stopped beside a section of the garden that contained a series of thin purple spirit plants, each of which was only around half a foot tall, and they resembled wheat.

These spirit plants were giving off a rather peculiar odor that was both fragrant yet also a little rank.

Han Li was staring intently at these purple spirit plants, paying no heed to their peculiar aroma at all.

These were Farsight Weeds, and they were extremely renowned in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Han Li had once read a story about an island by the name of Nightlight Island situated in the northernmost region of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. There was a type of spirit hawk that resided on this island, and they only grew to an upper limit of the Body Integration Stage. Furthermore, there weren't many of them on the island, so they never attracted much attention from anyone.

That was until a True Immortal Stage itinerant cultivator caught a Nightlight Spirit Hawk by chance on the island and kept it as a spirit beast.

The Nightlight Spirit Hawk's cultivation base wasn't anything special, but it possessed extraordinary eyesight, able to see things tens of thousands of kilometers away. The True Immortal cultivator was ecstatic, and he earned himself quite a reputation through this bird.

The story of his exploits was eventually leaked, and many cultivators flocked to the island to capture these Nightlight Spirit Hawks, only to find that their eyesight was quite mediocre and nowhere near as extraordinary as the story proclaimed.

The True Immortal Stage itinerant cultivator was rather surprised to hear this, and he returned to the island to investigate. Only then did he notice that there were several spirit plants growing near the nest of the Nightlight Spirit Hawk that he had captured, and that particular hawk had only attained such exceptional eyesight after consuming this spirit plant.

After word of this spread, the spirit plant in question immediately became vastly renowned and was named the Farsight Weed, becoming extremely sought after for countless cultivators.

However, Farsight Weeds grew very slowly and only in very unique conditions, so they were very rare to begin with, and with so many cultivators going after them, they had been picked to near extinction. No specimen had appeared in the past one million years, and Han Li certainly wasn't expecting to see any here.

Furthermore, these Farsight Herbs had to have been at least 200,000 to 300,000 years old, so they were undoubtedly extremely valuable.

A hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he cast his gaze elsewhere, and there were extremely precious spirit plants everywhere he looked, many of which had already gone extinct in the outside world.

Furthermore, all of the spirit plants in this garden were hundreds of thousands of years old, which meant that they were fit even for refining Golden Immortal Stage pills.

Aside from that, there were also several types of spirit plants in the garden that were completely unfamiliar to Han Li, even with his extensive knowledge in the field.

However, all of them were brimming with spiritual power, and they were clearly extremely valuable spirit plants as well.

Sure enough, the medicine garden hadn't disappointed him.

Right at this moment, a burst of rumbling rang out from nearby, and Han Li turned to discover that Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing had also begun attacking some of the nearby restrictions.

However, these restrictions didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but they were unexpectedly resilient, remaining intact despite the attacks they were being subjected to.

Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, and his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly flew out, then circled around in the air before transforming into an azure sword array that encompassed several restrictions at once.

Immediately thereafter, countless streaks of peerlessly sharp sword qi emerged at Han Li's behest before striking the restrictions, and they were only able to hold themselves together for a few seconds before exploding violently.

With another sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released several hundred dark yellow beans, which transformed into an army of Dao Warriors, and with a third sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released hundreds of jade boxes and other types of containers amid a flash of azure light.

"Collect all of these spirit plants," Han Li instructed.

The Dao Warriors immediately picked up the containers and began to work.

At this point, Patriarch Cold Flame had only just broken through a restriction, and he was collecting the spirit plants inside one by one when he spotted what Han Li was doing, upon which a stunned look appeared on his face.

He had already been astonished by Han Li's power, and it came as another shock to him that Han Li also had an army of Dao Warriors at his disposal, considering how Dao Warriors were notoriously difficult to nurture.

Chapter 428: Split Tree

After issuing an instruction for his Dao Warriors to begin collecting the nearby spirit plants, Han Li remained still on the spot as he made a hand seal, and the azure sword array that he had conjured up immediately flew toward another nearby section of the medicine garden.

Countless streaks of azure sword qi came raining down upon the restriction, breaking through it with ease, and some of the Dao Warriors immediately flocked over to that area to collect all of the spirit plants there.

Right at this moment, all of the destroyed restrictions began to slowly re-emerged, indicating that they were capable of self-regeneration, just like the starry light barrier that encompassed the entire garden.

Han Li was very impressed upon seeing this. The fact that these restrictions were still functional after so many years was already quite astonishing, and the fact that they were capable of self-regeneration indicated that whoever had set up the restrictions had to have been an extraordinary master in arrays.

With that in mind, Han Li was even more curious about who this Infernal Frost Immortal Lord was.

Han Li's trio wasn't holding back in the slightest, and it didn't take them long to clear out the entire outskirts of the medicine garden.

However, Han Li was naturally far more efficient than Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing thanks to his sword array and his army of Dao Warriors, so the majority of the claimed spirit plants had fallen into his possession.

During this time, he had even helped Lu Yuqing break several restrictions, much to the envy and dismay of Patriarch Cold Flame.

As the three of them progressed deeper into the garden, they discovered that the sections here were far larger in area than the ones before, and the restrictions were also brighter, making it impossible to see the spirit plants within from the outside.

Han Li swept his gaze around the area to ensure that there weren't any abnormalities, then immediately unleashed his sword array to attack a glowing red restriction.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing also each chose a restriction of their own to attack, but this time, the sword array formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords wasn't able to inflict much damage onto the red restriction beneath it.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he switched to a different hand seal, upon which the azure sword array abruptly converged toward the center to form a giant azure sword lotus flower.

He then began to chant an incantation, and the sword lotus flower gradually bloomed, while arcs of dazzling lightning flashed over all of its petals as it swooped down toward the red light barrier.

Every single one of the lotus flower's petals latched tightly onto the red light barrier before revolving forcefully to tear into the restriction, and the red light barrier instantly began to warp violently.

This time, it was only able to withstand the assault for a short while before it exploded into countless specks of red light with a resounding boom.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, but his expression then instantly stiffened as he caught sight of a yellowish-brown spirit tree up ahead.

Its trunk was very coarse and riddled with deep cracks, but it was giving off a vibrant sense of vitality, clearly indicating that it was no ordinary tree.

However, the tree had been severed down the middle, and only a section of the trunk still remained. The cut was still quite fresh, and there were droplets of yellow sap leaking oozing out.

Han Li made his way over to the tree trunk with a contemplative look on his face.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing were just about to go to work on some other restrictions, but all of them also stopped what they were doing and approached Han Li upon seeing this.

"It looks like someone got here before us. Judging from how fresh the cut looks, they shouldn't have been here any longer than a day ago," Patriarch Cold Flame surmised.

Han Li nodded in response, then took a glance up at the starry light barrier overhead.

It was no wonder that they had broken the restriction so easily, considering it had already been broken recently once before.

The restriction was capable of self-regeneration, but too little time had passed for it to make a full recovery, and that was the only reason why they had been able to bypass it with so little trouble.

"Who could it be? Xiong Shan?" Lu Yuqing murmured.

"No. Xiong Shan did get to the Light Frost Palace a little earlier than us, but there clearly wasn't enough time for him to get here and break this restriction," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, who could it be?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"I don't know, but that person didn't touch any of the spirit plants prior to this. I don't know if those spirit plants failed to catch their eye, or if they simply didn't have enough time, but given that there are no signs of battle here, I'm assuming it was most likely the former. That leads me to believe that it was most likely a Golden Immortal Stage senior who passed through here before us," Han Li speculated.

There were many Golden Immortals who had entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor on this occasion, and he couldn't tell exactly which one was responsible for this.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing exchanged a glance upon hearing this, then discussed the matter a little longer before parting ways to continue to work on other restrictions.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued to observe the severed tree trunk in front of him, and he gently dipped his finger in some of its yellow sap before taking a sniff, upon which he was immediately struck by a sense of reinvigoration.

His eyes instantly lit up as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, which enveloped the tree trunk before uprooting the entire thing along with the spirit soil around it.

He didn't know what this tree was, but the fact that it had caught a Golden Immortal's eye indicated that it was definitely a very precious spirit tree.

Even though the tree had been chopped down, there was still a chance for Han Li to revive it using his Heaven Controlling Vial.

After doing all of that, Han Li flew over to another section of the medicine garden before making a hand seal, and the sword lotus flower up above instantly swooped down to encompass the bright blue light barrier down below.

The thick petals of the lotus flower then began to slice against the light barrier, causing a massive commotion, and it didn't take long before the blue light barrier was destroyed to reveal what was underneath.

Han Li's expression immediately darkened slightly at the sight that was laid out before him.

The spirit plants in this section had already been taken as well, and this time, not even the roots had been left behind.

Han Li remained still on the spot for a moment before flying over to another section, and around 15 minutes later, yet another restriction was broken under the might of the azure sword lotus flower.

Once again, whatever was in this section had already been taken, and there was a hole that was several feet deep in the ground.

He shook his head as he withdrew his gaze.

At this point, most of the restrictions deep in the medicine garden had already been broken.

Of course, Han Li was the one who had done most of the work, and all of the spirit plants here had already been taken, with no exceptions.

Some of them still had their roots remaining, and Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing had no interest in such things, but Han Li picked up every single root that he encountered.

At this moment, Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing were still each working on a restriction, and Han Li took a glance at the two of them before withdrawing his gaze and turning his attention to the innermost part of the medicine garden.

There was a plot of land there that was over 1,000 feet in size, so it was far more massive than all of the other sections.

The entire section was enshrouded under a thick purple light barrier with arcs of purple lightning flashing over its surface, and it was giving off a formidable aura, almost as if it were a massive purple beast that was laying dormant on the ground.

This section was clearly different from all of the other sections, so the trio decided to leave it for last.

Han Li turned his gaze toward the purple light barrier, and he was just about to call upon his azure sword lotus flower when a resounding boom rang out nearby.

As it turned out, Lu Yuqing had just broken a restriction.

This restriction was more formidable than all of the prior ones, and her complexion was a little pale, indicating that she had severely taxed herself to break it.

She quickly summoned a pill before swallowing it while casting her gaze forward, upon which a disappointed look appeared on her face.

Whatever had been here had already been taken, with even the roots being taken and there were only two huge holes left in the ground.

However, whoever had come here seemed to have passed through in quite a hurry, as evidenced by the fact that there were still some thin pieces of roots left behind.

Lu Yuqing pouted with dismay, and she was just about to turn and depart when Han Li approached her as he said, "These appear to be the roots of some type of spirit bamboo. Bamboo is different from other plants in that it can sprout even from root fragments given the proper care, and the newly grown bamboo should be quite valuable, so it would be a waste for you to leave these roots behind."

An elated look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face upon hearing this, and she asked, "Do you recognize this spirit bamboo, Brother Han?"

Han Li shook his head in response. "I don't, but these silver roots seem quite remarkable, so the spirit bamboo that they belong to must be very precious. Otherwise, they wouldn't have been planted so deep in the medicine garden. If you can find someone who can identify these roots, you should be able to sell them for a good price."

Lu Yuqing nodded eagerly in response as she swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which carefully dug out the silver roots in the two holes before storing them into a pair of jade boxes.

She stowed one of the jade boxes away, then handed the other to Han Li as she said, "Thank you for your guidance, Brother Han. Otherwise, I would've passed up this entirely."

Han Li made no effort to refuse and accepted the jade box as he really was quite interested in these silver spirit bamboo roots.

Meanwhile, a burst of rumbling was coming from another direction, and Patriarch Cold Flame was in the process of attacking a light blue restriction with a set of 12 flying dagger spirit treasures, all of which were spirit treasures of a very high caliber.

However, this was yet another starry light barrier, and it was extremely resilient.

Patriarch Cold Flame had already been attacking the light barrier for quite some time, but it was displaying no signs of breaking at all.

A slightly agitated look appeared on his face as he took a glance at Han Li, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he stopped what he was doing before flying toward Han Li.

Han Li was examining the silver roots in his jade box when he noticed Patriarch Cold Flame coming toward him, and he promptly stowed the jade box away.

"Fellow Daoist Han, that restriction over there is rather difficult to deal with. Would you be able to give me a hand with it?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Of course, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame. Let's go have a look together, Fellow Daoist Lu," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han," Patriarch Cold Flame immediately said with an elated expression.

Before long, the three of them arrived at the starry light barrier, and Han Li began to examine it.

He had actually already noticed this restriction earlier, but he could tell that it was quite a formidable restriction, so he had decided to save it for later. However, it seemed that Patriarch Cold Flame had gotten to it first.

Chapter 429: Withered Vine

Han Li made a hand seal, and his azure sword lotus flower instantly descended upon the starry light barrier while revolving incessantly.

Countless streaks of formidable sword qi were released from the sword lotus flower, raining down upon the restriction, while Patriarch Cold Flame summoned the same set of flying dagger spirit treasures as before.

The 12 flying daggers then instantly swelled to over 1,000 feet in size each at his behest, and they came crashing down upon the restriction with astonishing might.

The starry light barrier was extremely resilient, but it wasn't able to withstand this joint barrage from Han Li's duo for long, and it was only a short while before the light barrier was shattered to reveal what was underneath.

Beneath the light barrier were around a dozen blue spirit plants, each of which was several feet tall.

The stems and leaves of these spirit plants were all glittering and translucent, as if they had been fashioned out of some type of semi-transparent blue jade, and they were also giving off radiant starlight.

Much to Han Li's surprise, these blue spirit plants hadn't been taken by the person who had passed through this place before them.

A surprised look had also appeared on Lu Yuqing's face, while Patriarch Cold Flame's expression remained unchanged, indicating that he seemed to have already anticipated this.

These are Starlight Herbs!

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he identified these blue spirit plants.

This was a type of renowned spirit plant that contained starpower gathered from countless nights of exposure to starlight, resulting in the accumulation of extremely pure starpower, thereby making it an exceptional ingredient for refining starpower-related pills.

Judging from their size, they had to have been at least 500,000 years of age.

If he could get his hands on even just one or two of these Starlight Herbs and refine them into pills, then that would drastically shorten the amount of time it would take for him to cultivate the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts.

Right at this moment, a streak of light suddenly flew past him, then enveloped all of the Starlight Herbs before uprooting them and sending them flying toward Patriarch Cold Flame.

He then immediately stowed all of the Starlight Herbs away without any hesitation, and Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything.

"Thank you for your help, Fellow Daoist Han. If you require my assistance for anything, please feel free to call upon me," Patriarch Cold Flame said with a smile, making no mention of splitting the Starlight Herbs between them.

Han Li turned to look at Patriarch Cold Flame in silence, while Lu Yuqing's brows furrowed slightly as she protested, "Fellow Daoist Cold Flame, you and Brother Han worked together to..."

Han Li raised a hand to cut her off before she could finish her sentence.

"Fellow Daoist Cold Flame was the one who discovered these Starlight Herbs first, so they naturally belong to him. There's no need to dwell on this matter," Han Li said in an indifferent voice, then turned and began to make his way toward the plot of land in the innermost section of the medicine garden.

Lu Yuqing took a cold glance at Patriarch Cold Flame, then departed behind Han Li.

Patriarch Cold Flame also followed along with a gleeful look in his eyes.

Having interacted with Han Li on multiple past occasions, he had developed a decent grasp of Han Li's personality and character. His original plan was for Han Li to bring up the matter of splitting the Starlight Herbs, in which case he would oblige, but in the process make Han Li owe him a favor so that he could continue to leverage Han Li's assistance.

However, to his surprise, Han Li didn't even bother to make such a request, seemingly as he didn't want to lose face.

This was even better as he could continue to exploit this personality trait of Han Li's to keep claiming more things for himself, but of course, he would do so in moderation so that he didn't turn Han Li entirely against himself.

The three of them quickly arrived at the final plot of land in the medicine garden, and Han Li briefly examined the purple restriction in front of him before making a hand seal, upon which a flurry of petals of his azure sword lotus flower flew off on their own one after another, transforming into around a dozen massive translucent swords that came crashing down upon the purple light barrier.

All of the giant swords were giving off extremely fearsome aura fluctuations and immense spiritual pressure that was making the nearby space tremble and quiver.

The giant translucent swords struck the light barrier with immense power, but all of them were repelled one after the other.

Meanwhile, the purple light barrier merely shuddered slightly before falling still again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. The purple restriction was far more resilient than even what he had anticipated.

Lu Yuqing was also eager to help, and she began attacking the restriction with a series of giant azure blades of wind, while Patriarch Cold Flame was also contributing to the effort with his flying daggers.

The collective barrage of attacks from the trio was quite formidable, but the purple restriction remained strong, managing to hold itself intact without much difficulty.

"It looks like we won't be able to break this restriction through conventional means, so let's use the Great Five-elemental True Light again," Han Li said as he summoned the three elemental spirit treasures from before, and Patriarch Cold Flame also summoned his two flying treasures.

Moments later, a thick pillar of five-colored light came crashing down from the heavens, releasing numerous balls of five-colored light that rained down upon the purple light barrier.

A burst of rumbling rang out incessantly, and the entire medicine garden was trembling.

The purple light barrier was extremely resilient, yet even it was no match for the Great Five-elemental True Light, and after one barrage of attacks after another, the light barrier was quickly whittled down to just a thin layer.

A sharp gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the dozen or so giant translucent swords came crashing down upon the purple light barrier at his behest.

Finally, the purple light barrier was unable to hold itself together any longer, and it imploded to reveal what was underneath.

Han Li's trio immediately turned their attention to what had been revealed, and as it turned out, down below was a swamp that was filled with viscous dark purple mud, with the occasional purple bubble appearing on its surface before popping with explosive force to release waves of heat coupled with bursts of purple gas.

A faint layer of purple mist was hanging over the swamp, and countless tiny arcs of lightning could be seen flashing within it, giving off a fearsome aura.

The dark purple mud was rather hideous in appearance, but it was imbued with extremely abundant spiritual power, indicating that it was no ordinary soil.

This is Lightning Aura Soil!

In order to best nurture different types of spirit plants, Han Li had invested a great deal of time into improving his understanding of spirit soils, and at this point, he could be considered to be a master in this field.

The Lightning Aura Soil was a type of extremely precious spirit soil that was ideal for nurturing lightning-attribute spirit plants, but the method to prepare it had already gone missing long ago.

Han Li had tried extensively to search for this soil or its recipe in the past, all to no avail, and he certainly wasn't expecting to see some here.

With a sweep of his sleeve, two Dao Warriors instantly appeared amid a flash of golden lightning.

He then summoned a pair of storage pouches that he tossed at the pair of Dao Warriors as he instructed, "Collect all of this soil."

The two Dao Warriors immediately obliged, beginning to collect the spirit soil in the area, and Patriarch Cold Flame's expression changed slightly upon seeing this as he also swept a sleeve through the air to collect some of the dark purple mud beside him.

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing was looking on with slightly furrowed brows, seemingly rather disgusted by the dark purple mud.

Han Li took a glance at Patriarch Cold Flame, then turned his attention to the center of the plot of land, where there was another hemispherical purple light barrier, this one far smaller than the previous one.

He flew over to the light barrier, followed closely by Lu Yuqing, and Patriarch Cold Flame also hurriedly followed along.

This purple light barrier was identical to the one from before, except it was far smaller and nowhere near as formidable.

Han Li was able to break the light barrier with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords without having to rely on the Great Five-elemental True Light, and a purple stone altar that was around 10 feet tall was revealed.

The altar had been entirely constructed from a type of purple crystal, and there were lightning patterns engraved upon it, seemingly forming some type of profound array.

At the top of the stone altar was yet another purple light barrier that resembled a box that concealed the top of the altar, making it impossible to see what was inside.

"How many layers of restrictions are there?" Lu Yuqing couldn't help but complain.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed that there were two humanoid puppets laying on the ground beside the stone altar.

The puppets were dark golden in color, and they were identical to the copper puppet that Han Li had encountered while securing the Great Universe Origin Arts.

However, one of the puppets had been split in half down the middle lengthwise, while the other had been decapitated, and both of them were laying on the ground in a lifeless fashion.

The wounds on the puppets appeared to be quite fresh, clearly indicating that they had been inflicted not long ago.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

As expected, this place had already been visited as well, so whatever treasure on the stone altar had to have already been taken.

The same thought had clearly also occurred to Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing, and a hint of dismay appeared on both of their faces.

Han Li shook his head with a hint of disappointment in his eyes, then turned his attention back to the pair of copper puppets. In particular, his gaze lingered on the decapitated puppet as a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

In the next instant, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which swept up the pair of puppets before stowing them away.

With these two puppets, particularly the decapitated one, which still had a completely intact core, Daoist Xie would surely be able to scrounge together a complete, functional puppet.

Han Li had witnessed the power of these copper puppets, and they would definitely be of great assistance to him in battle.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly with displeasure upon seeing this, but he quickly reverted back to a neutral expression.

After gathering the puppets, Han Li flicked a finger toward the stone altar, releasing a pair of azure flying swords that swept over the purple light barrier.

The restriction wasn't all that powerful, so it was torn apart with ease, revealing a wooden frame, around which was wound a long vine that still hadn't been taken, much to Han Li's surprise.

However, the vine had withered away, and it seemed to have perished long ago.

Chapter 430: Pursuers

"What kind of vine is this? It has to be something very precious to have been kept here so securely. It's just a pity that it seems to be long dead," Lu Yuqing sighed.

"Regardless, for whatever reason, it seems like the person who came here before us was unable to take this vine," Patriarch Cold Flame said with a hint of schadenfreude in his voice.

All the while, Han Li merely remained silent as his gaze roamed over the withered vine.

All of a sudden, he seemed to have noticed something, and he began to inspect the vine intently with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

"What is it, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing immediately asked.

Instead of answering her question, Han Li flew directly toward the vine, immediately followed by Lu Yuqing and Patriarch Cold Flame.

After landing beside the vine, Han Li lifted up a section of it for closer inspection, and the blue light in his eyes grew even brighter.

After a while, he suddenly heaved a forlorn sigh as he set down the withered vine with a disappointed look on his face.

Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing were both quite perplexed to see this, and they each picked up a section of the vine for themselves for closer inspection.

As it turned out, there were patterns on the vines that were rather similar to beveled silver text or golden seal text, but these patterns were more profound, as if they were the embodiment of the Great Dao itself.

The patterns were very faint, and they would've never been able to notice them had they not been scrutinizing the vine so closely.

"These are Profound Heavenly Patterns!" Patriarch Cold Flame exclaimed.

"There's no mistaking it. These patterns that are imbued with the aura of the Great Dao can only be present on Profound Heavenly Treasures. This was most likely a Profound Heavenly Vine, but the Profound Heavenly Treasure on it has already been taken, and the vine has wilted on its own as a result," Lu Yuqing said with a wry smile.

Han Li pointed at a spot on the vine, and both Patriarch Cold Flame and Lu Yuqing turned their attention to that spot to find that there was a tiny incision, which wasn't very pronounced due to how withered the vine had become, but it was still distinguishable upon closer inspection.

The incision had clearly been formed after something was taken off the vine.

Lu Yuqing heaved a faint sight upon seeing this.

Profound Heavenly Treasures were extremely precious and could be used to refine Essential Immortal Treasure, yet it had slipped through their grasp.

"There's no point in crying over spilled milk. It looks like we're simply not in luck on this occasion," Han Li said.

Right at this moment, the two Dao Warriors arrived on the scene, holding a pair of bulging storage pouches, having stuffed them with virtually all of the nearby Lightning Aura Soil.

Han Li took the pair of storage pouches before stowing the two Dao Warriors away, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, the starry restriction above the medicine garden suddenly began to tremble violently as a resounding boom rang out.

Han Li's trio immediately looked up at the sky with startled expressions.

At this point, the starry light barrier had only recovered a tiny fraction of its power, and it quickly shattered in the face of the formidable attacks being directed at it.

"What a rich medicinal aura! This is definitely the medicine garden!"

A burst of cackling rang out overhead, and the voice belonged to none other than Xue Han.

Patriarch Cold Flame's complexion immediately paled upon hearing this, and he hurriedly made a hand seal while chanting an incantation.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished into the ground beneath his feet.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he also quickly made a hand seal, upon which a faint light barrier enveloped himself and Lu Yuqing's body before the two of them also vanished into thin air.

Meanwhile, the destroyed starry light barrier dissipated into countless specks of light, and not long after Han Li's trio had concealed themselves, Xue Han and the group of Ghost Wail Sect cultivators descended onto the scene.

Upon landing in the medicine garden, Xue Han immediately began to inspect his surroundings, upon which his smile instantly stiffened.

Everyone else was also rooted to the spot.

There was not a single spirit plant left in the entire medicine garden. Not only had everything been completely uprooted, even the spirit soil nurturing the spirit plants that were previously here had also been taken. The entire place had been left in a state of complete chaos, and it would've been impossible to identify this place as a medicine garden had it not been for the rich medicinal aura lingering in the air.

"Someone got here before us!" a yellow-skinned middle-aged man beside Xue Han spat in a vengeful voice.

Xue Han was clearly enraged, and there was a look of burning fury on his face.

Everyone else instantly fell silent at the sight of Xue Han's incensed expression.

After a while, Xue Han exhaled as the fury on his face receded, and he snapped, "Don't just stand there like idiots! Go and see if there's anything left!"

Everyone hurriedly did as they were told, dispersing throughout the medicine garden to conduct a search.

Meanwhile, Xue Han remained still on the spot as he began to inspect the medicine garden with both his eyes and his spiritual sense.

At this moment, there was a faint shadow hovering behind a large rock in a corner of the medicine garden.

Within the shadow stood a pair of blurry figures, and they were none other than Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

There was a solemn look on Han Li's face as he chanted an incantation while flicking his fingers through the air to release a string of incantation seals, which slowly vanished into the space around him.

Xue Han's spiritual sense swept over the two of them without pause, clearly having failed to discover their presence.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, but he still continued to make more hand seals to ensure that they were hidden more securely.

Right at this moment, Xue Han cast his gaze toward the stone altar deep in the medicine garden, and he swept a hand through the air to release a burst of black light, which vanished into the stone altar in a flash before quickly flying back with the withered vine enveloped within it.

None of the other Ghost Wail Sect cultivators were able to find anything, and they all returned to gather around Xue Han upon seeing this.

"This is... a Profound Heavenly Vine!" Xue Han exclaimed with an astonished expression as he carefully inspected the vine.

"Looking at the patterns on the vine, that's definitely a possibility! That means that the Profound Heavenly Treasure on it had to have already been taken by the scoundrel who got here before us!" the yellow-faced man cursed.

"This Profound Heavenly Treasure and all of the other spirit plants here had to have been taken by Cold Flame and the others! Thankfully, this Light Frost Palace isn't a very big place, and they seemed to have only come through here recently, so if we go after them now, we should be able to catch them," a tall and thin daoist priest immediately said.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he eavesdropped on Xue Han and his entourage.

As soon as Xue Han left this place, he and Lu Yuqing would be able to sneak away unnoticed.

He wasn't actually all that fearful of Xue Han. With his current powers, even if he couldn't defeat Xue Han in battle, he would at least be able to ensure self-preservation, but it would be difficult for him to protect himself as well as Lu Yuqing, and he was quite interested in the map in her possession, so he didn't want to lose her.

After hearing what everyone had to say, Xue Han raised his head and slowly swept his gaze over the medicine garden, then suddenly made a hand seal to release a ball of black light.

The ball of black light squirmed around in mid-air like a living creature for a while, then abruptly swelled to form a huge black net that encompassed the entire sky above the medicine garden.

Han Li's expression immediately darkened slightly upon seeing this.

"It's possible that whoever took the spirit plants and the Profound Heavenly Treasure haven't gone far, but it's also possible that they could still be hiding here! We can't afford to pass up any opportunity to claim the Profound Heavenly Treasure!" Xue Han declared as a hint of yearning flashed through his eyes.

If he could obtain an immortal treasure refined using a Profound Heavenly Treasure, then his powers would be significantly enhanced, and that would allow him to leapfrog many figures currently ahead of him in the Ubiquitous Pavilion hierarchy.

"But there's no one here," the yellow-faced man said with furrowed brows.

"Perhaps they used some type of secret technique to conceal themselves, and we've simply been unable to detect them up to this point. Master Xue Han is right, we can't ignore any possibility!" the tall and thin daoist priest said.

"That is indeed possible," the yellow-faced man mused with a contemplative expression.

Xue Han paid no heed to the discussion taking place around him as he began to chant an incantation, and a ball of silver light flew out of his body, containing a pristine white miniature pagoda that was around half a foot tall with a series of profound patterns engraved upon it.

The miniature pagoda quickly swelled to in excess of the height of a grown man, and all of the patterns on its surface had lit up at once.

A series of dazzling white ripples began to proliferate outward from the pagoda, and all of the surrounding world's origin qi instantly began to tremble, as if it were resonating with these white ripples.

The white ripples quickly spread over the entire medicine garden, and Han Li and Lu Yuqing had also become encompassed within them.

The faint light barrier around the two of them instantly began to tremble, and they were slowly being exposed.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he began to chant his incantation and make hand seals with more urgency.

However, his efforts proved to be futile, and it seemed that they were inevitably going to be exposed.

Right at this moment, a burst of faint light emerged from another corner of the medicine garden, then exploded with a dull thump to reveal Patriarch Cold Flame with a panicked look on his face.

"I knew it was you, Cold Flame!" Xue Han said in a cold voice.

Patriarch Cold Flame shuddered as a hint of despair appeared in his eyes, and he began to frantically look around as if he were searching for something.

"Traitors must die! Kill him!" Xue Han declared, and all of the Ghost Wail Sect cultivators instantly pounced at Patriarch Cold Flame, led by none other than the tall and thin daoist priest and the yellow-faced man.

The former swept both sleeves through the air to release balls of azure light that contained arcs of azure lightning, which hurtled directly toward Patriarch Cold Flame, while the latter instantly transformed into a pillar of crimson light.

A massive ghostly projection emerged within the pillar of light before biting down upon Patriarch Cold Flame with ferocious power, while a layer of starlight emerged over Patriarch Cold Flame's body as he fled from the scene as quickly as he could.

"Layman Bone Flame! Daoist Clear Bright! How could you..."

Before he had a chance to finish, he was bombarded by a string of spirit treasures.

Chapter 431: Different Area

All of a sudden, a sharp gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he abruptly did away with his concealment secret technique, instantly exposing himself and Lu Yuqing.

Immediately thereafter, he slung an arm around her waist as arcs of golden lightning began to emerge over his body, then converged above them to form a thick bolt of golden lightning that enveloped both of them and erupted into the air.

Xue Han was quite startled by this, and he hurriedly swiveled around, following which a cold smile appeared on his face.

"I knew you couldn't have gone very far!"

The huge black net above the medicine garden suddenly began to rumble violently while also rapidly becoming around twice as thick as before.

At the same time, a series of black threads shot out of all of the connective points on the net, then sped directly toward the bolt of golden lightning that was rising up into the sky.

The black threads appeared to be moving in a rather languid fashion, but they were astonishingly fast, even more so than the bolt of golden lightning.

The bolt of golden lightning was weaving from side to side to evade the black threads as it approached the black net up above, but it was swarmed by the vast expanse of black threads no more than 100 feet away from the net.

A burst of constrictive law powers erupted out of the black threads, and the bolt of golden lightning instantly faded to reveal Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

The surrounding black threads didn't stop even for a moment as they continued to sweep toward the two, and they were as dense as rain, making them impossible to evade.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, but he remained calm and collected as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which began to revolve rapidly before immediately vanishing back into his body.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of faint golden light emerged over his body, and he transformed into a golden blur as he continued to rush toward the black net overhead.

All of a sudden, he had become extraordinarily fast, allowing him to evade the seemingly unavoidable mass of black threads with ease.

All of this had transpired in the blink of an eye, and before Xue Han had a chance to react, Han Li and Lu Yuqing had already bypassed the storm of black threads and appeared directly underneath the huge black net.

A hint of surprise flashed through Xue Han's eyes upon seeing this, but he wasn't overly alarmed.

Even though Han Li and Lu Yuqing had managed to bypass the storm of black threads, there was no way that they would be able to get through the black net.

Not only was the net imbued with restrictive law powers, it was extremely resilient, which meant that it could trap even a Golden Immortal, let alone a mere True Immortal like Han Li.

With that in mind, Xue Han stowed away the miniature silver pagoda in his hand, then flew up toward Han Li's duo.

Right at this moment, an incredibly powerful Golden Immortal Stage aura surged out of Han Li's body, followed immediately by an eruption of thick and translucent arcs of golden lightning that were far more formidable than the golden lightning from before.

At the same time, a massive crab pincer emerged from Han Li's body with thick arcs of golden lightning flashing around it, and it closed around the huge black net like a giant pair of lightning scissors.

A gash was instantly torn into the net, and it wasn't a very large one, but large enough for two people to pass through.

Xue Han's expression changed drastically upon seeing this.

Han Li immediately flew out of the opening as a faint shadow, then fled into the distance without any hesitation, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Right after Han Li got away, Xue Han immediately arrived outside the black net as well, and he cast his gaze toward the direction that Han Li had fled in as he roared in a furious voice, "After him!"

……

In a dense forest to the left of the mountain summit.

A streak of golden light descended out of the sky, then faded to reveal Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

"Brother Han, why are you flying away from this place?" Lu Yuqing asked with a slightly panicked expression.

"We're being chased by a Golden Immortal. If I were on my own, perhaps I would be able to outrun him, but I can't guarantee the same if you're with me, and if we flee to the sea, there won't be anywhere that we can take cover, so it'll be very difficult to shake them off," Han Li explained while quickly scouring his surroundings.

Lu Yuqing's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she was very thankful that Han Li hadn't abandoned her.

"Having said that, hiding here isn't a permanent solution, either. We have to conceal our auras and hide elsewhere on the island. Do you have an aura concealment spirit treasure on you?" Han Li asked.

"I do, my father gave me one before I came here," Lu Yuqing immediately replied with a nod.

She then flipped a hand over to produce an extremely thin white veil garment that she promptly put on.

A layer of faint white light instantly emerged over the veil garment, and it vanished out of sight, having fused into her clothes in a flash.

At the same time, her aura had also become very subtle and difficult to detect.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over her momentarily, then gave a pleased nod as he said, "That'll do. Once we open up some distance between them and ourselves, we should be able to remain hidden."

At the same time, he was also using his Transient Guild and an aura concealment secret technique to completely stifle his own aura.

After that, the two of them made their way into the dense forest in the opposite direction from the medicine garden.

Not long after their departure, four figures descended out of the sky, landing where they had been standing not long ago.

"Their auras have vanished here," Layman Bone Flame said with tightly furrowed brows.

"They must be hiding like cowards because they're scared of us!" a burly man with a formidable physique chuckled coldly.

"We have to find them. Otherwise, we'll have to face the wrath of Master Xue Han," another Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivator said with a concerned expression.

"No need to panic, I have something here that should be able to help us track them down," Daoist Clear Bright said with a smile.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a miniature golden cauldron, on the lid of which was engraved a peculiar-looking beast with a remarkably long trunk of a nose.

Its eyes were closed, and its trunk was coiled, giving it a rather adorable appearance.

Daoist Clear Bright then summoned a piece of black incense before tossing it into the miniature cauldron after setting alight. After that, he chanted an incantation before laying a finger onto the head of the strange beast on the cauldron's lid, and the beast's eyelids instantly sprang open to reveal a pair of ruby-like eyes.

It began sniffing around the area before turning its trunk in the direction that Han Li's duo had departed in before releasing a cloud of dense white smoke.

"This spirit cauldron can sniff out the magic power, scent, aura, and many other telltale signs left behind by cultivators in the air. In particular, it's very sensitive to the bodily aroma of women. However, it won't work if too much time has passed, so we have to get after them right away," Daoist Clear Bright said.

The other three Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were ecstatic to see this, and they hurriedly set off in the direction that the cloud of smoke was pointing in.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Lu Yuqing had arrived in a dilapidated garden.

All of the pavilions and buildings had already collapsed, and there were layers of slick moss and masses of tangled vines clinging to everything.

The garden wasn't very large, and it had been constructed on the outskirts of the forest, which meant that leaving the garden equated to emerging from the forest.

The exit of the garden was a semi-collapsed circular archway, outside of which was a small winding path that was covered in weeds leading all the way down the mountain.

"Someone's coming after us!" Han Li suddenly said as he stopped in his tracks and turned around.

"How? We've already concealed our auras!" Lu Yuqing exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"We may have concealed our auras, but that doesn't mean that they don't have other ways to track us. If worse comes to worst, we'll have to try and get away..."

Before Han Li finished his sentence, his voice suddenly cut off as a surprised look appeared on his face.

"What is it, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked with a slightly anxious expression.

Han Li offered no response as he hurried over to the semi-collapsed stone archway before carefully examining it.

Lu Yuqing also followed along and began to inspect the archway with tightly furrowed brows, and each of them were using their respective ocular ability.

Moments later, Lu Yuqing withdrew her gaze as she asked in a puzzled manner, "Is there something special about this archway, Brother Han?"

Han Li shook his head in response. "Do you not see anything, either? Looks like it must've been my imagination then. Let's go."

With that, the two of them stepped through the stone archway, but as soon as they did so, the space around them instantly began to warp like a sheet of paper that had suddenly been poked inward, resulting in layers of creases.

Han Li was quite startled to see this, but it was too late for him to backtrack, and he stumbled forward before steadying himself.

Lu Yuqing also tipped forward involuntarily, and she would've fallen on her face had Han Li not reacted sufficiently quickly to catch her.

Upon witnessing the scene that laid out before her, Lu Yuqing immediately exclaimed, "Where are we right now?"

A thin and long mountain range that stretched for hundreds of kilometers had appeared in front of them, and it seemed that the mountain range was connected to the island that they were currently on.

Han Li turned back to discover that the stone archway was still there, but it seemed very out of place in this setting.

"It looks like this archway is the entrance to another area," Han Li mused.

Chapter 432: Realm Traversing Plaque

"That's incredible! Neither of us detected any spatial fluctuations before we stepped through the archway!" Lu Yuqing said with an amazed expression.

"I have a feeling that perhaps this is a one-way passageway, and the triggering mechanism is on this side, so it was previously only possible to go from here to the garden. However, it seems like it's since become a two-way passageway, perhaps due to the damage to the archway," Han Li speculated.

Lu Yuqing immediately began to inspect the archway upon hearing this, and sure enough, there were indeed some faint spatial fluctuations emanating from it.

"Now that we're in this hidden space, it should be very difficult for them to find us," Lu Yuqing said.

"Even so, we can't get complacent. After all, they managed to track us down earlier, did they not?"

Lu Yuqing fell silent upon hearing this.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li suddenly swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of golden light, which transformed into Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Lu Yuqing, then said to Han Li through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Han, while it's true that you're my current owner, haven't you been summoning me a bit too frequently these past few days?"

"My apologies, but we're in a very perilous situation right now, so I have no choice but to call upon you," Han Li replied with a wry smile as he flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch. "Here are some Immortal Origin Stones in case I need to call upon you for battle. Will that be enough?"

Daoist Xie accepted the storage pouch, then inspected its contents briefly before replying, "That should be enough unless I'm required to use certain special secret techniques."

"Good. In that case, you can go back and rest. The next time I summon you will most likely be in the heat of battle," Han Li said with a nod.

Daoist Xie flew back up Han Li's sleeve as a streak of golden light upon hearing this.

Lu Yuqing was watching in silence, and she was rather curious about Daoist Xie's identity, but knew not to ask unnecessary questions.

"Let's try and figure out what this place is before we do anything else," Han Li said as he inspected the mountain range with his eyes and his spiritual sense.

Moments later, he withdrew his spiritual sense, and his brows furrowed slightly as he said, "This place is rather strange. It seems to be an independent space. Whenever I try to release my spiritual sense beyond the boundaries of the mountain range, it hits an invisible wall."

"Then what should we do now? Should we explore the mountain range?" Lu Yuqing asked.

Han Li pondered the question for a moment, then replied, "If this is an isolated area, then there's definitely going to be more than one entrance and exit, so let's go and search the mountain range. Perhaps we'll be able to find a way out."

Lu Yuqing naturally raised no objections to this, and the two of them immediately set off, flying deep into the mountain range as two streaks of light.

Only while in mid-air did Han Li discover that the mountain range wasn't actually in the shape of a straight line. Instead, it split apart down the middle at some point to produce two different branches.

"Which way should we go, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked as she looked at the crossroads down below.

Han Li released his spiritual sense once again to try and detect something, but the results were rather dissatisfactory.

"I can't tell any difference between the two branches at the moment, so we'll just have to explore them one by one and..."

Before Han Li had a chance to finish his sentence, he suddenly discovered that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in his body had become rather restless for no apparent reason, and they were expressing some type of emotion to him through their spiritual connection.

It was a mixture of excitement, surprise, and agitation...

Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to summon one of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords,and it instantly shot forth toward the right branch of the mountain range.

If Han Li hadn't forced it to a halt through their spiritual connection, the sword would have flown away without him.

"For some reason, my bonded flying sword seems to be attracted to that branch of the mountain range," Han Li said as he caught the flying sword in his grasp.

"That must mean that there's something noteworthy there. We don't know which branch to choose anyway, so why don't we let the sword decide for us?" Lu Yuqing suggested with a smile.

Han Li considered this proposal momentarily, then nodded in response.

Thus, the two of them flew toward the right branch of the mountain range, but upon arriving at the point where the two branches intersected, Han Li suddenly stopped in his tracks, then cast his gaze in the direction of the stone archway as he asked, "Can I have a piece of fabric from your dress, Fellow Daoist Lu?"

Lu Yuqing was rather puzzled by this request, but she duly obliged, lifting the skirt of her dress before tearing off a piece and handing it to Han Li.

After accepting the piece of fabric from her, Han Li summoned a pair of giant ape puppets, then tied the strip of fabric around the finger of one of the puppets.

After that, he injected a wisp of his spiritual sense into the body of the other puppet, then instructed them to fly toward the left branch of the mountain range.

Lu Yuqing's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and she praised, "That's so smart of you, Brother Han! Even if you those people manage to track us up to this point, they'll surely be fooled."

"If we're lucky and they really do end up going the wrong way, regardless of whether they trigger any restrictions or engage my puppets in battle, as long as they make some noise, we'll be alerted to their presence in advance," Han Li said.

Lu Yuqing nodded in response, and at the same time, she couldn't help but wonder exactly what Han Li had to have gone through to make him so vigilant and resourceful.

"Alright, let's go," Han Li said, then flew toward the right branch of the mountain range, and Lu Yuqing hurriedly followed along.

The two of them had only just arrived above that branch of the mountain range when the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in Han Li's hand suddenly began to tremble violently, and it flew down with tremendous force, dragging Han Li downward.

At the same time, a burst of azure light suddenly appeared within Han Li's sleeve, and immediately thereafter, his sleeve abruptly burst open as one azure flying sword emerged after another, all of which were desperately trying to fly down as quickly as they could.

Han Li was quite startled by this turn of events, and he hurriedly closed his sleeve to prevent the rest of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords from flying out. At the same time, he tried to summon the dozens of flying swords that had already flown away back to himself, but they refused to heed his call, and it was as if they had gone completely out of his control.

Han Li took a deep breath, then flew down after his flying swords, while Lu Yuqing also followed along without much hesitation.

Upon landing on the ground, Han Li was alarmed to discover that his spiritual connection with the Azure Cloudswarm Bamboo Swords that had already flown away had suddenly been severed, so he was unable to sense them at all.

He forcibly suppressed the agitation that was rising up in his heart as he inspected his surroundings, and he found himself standing in an abandoned garden that was overrun with weeds and shrubs.

There seemed to be a small brick path beneath his feet, but it was barely visible at all underneath all of the soil and dead leaves and branches.

Han Li wore a grim expression as he scoured the surroundings with his spiritual sense, but to no avail.

At the same time, all of his remaining flying swords were still desperately trying to fly out of his sleeve.

Han Li took a glance down at his own bulging sleeve, then suddenly let go, releasing the flying sword in his grasp.

The flying sword instantly flew out of his grasp before hurtling deeper into the garden in a flash.

Han Li immediately focused his gaze intently on the flying sword as he set off in pursuit.

The flying sword flew straight to the deepest part of the garden, then plunged itself completely into a black tombstone that was around half the height of a grown man.

The black tombstone had clearly been weathered by the passage of time, and aside from a layer of dark and slick moss on its surface, there wasn't any text inscribed upon it.

Behind the tombstone was a bulging mound that appeared to be no different from an ordinary grave.

Han Li swept his gaze over the black tombstone with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he was immediately greeted by the sight of a burst of spatial ripples that were invisible to the naked eye.

His brows furrowed slightly as he approached the tombstone, then laid a hand down upon it, and a layer of black light instantly surged over the tombstone, then flashed a few times before fading away.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he pressed down on different parts of the tombstone with the palm of his hand, but it displayed no reaction other than that brief flash of black light.

At this point, Lu Yuqing had also arrived on the scene, and she landed beside Han Li before turning her attention to the tombstone, upon which a hint of recognition flashed through her eyes.

"Do you recognize this thing?" Han Li asked.

"If I'm not mistaken, this should be a Realm Traversing Plaque. We have one in the island master's manor," Lu Yuqing replied.

"Realm Traversing Plaque? What's that?" Han Li asked.

"It's a type of spatial treasure that's similar to a teleportation array, except it only facilitates one-way teleportation," Lu Yuqing explained.

"Do you know of any way to activate this plaque?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

Chapter 433: The Lost Sword Sect

"I can give it a try," Lu Yuqing replied, then strode forward as she flipped a hand over to summon an octagonal black jade pendant, upon which were engraved some very strange spiral patterns that were layered on top of one another in a rather convoluted fashion.

"This is the key for the Realm Traversing Plaque at our island master's manor. Apparently, it was passed down in our clan from generations past along with the Realm Traversing Plaque, but I don't know if this key will actually work on this plaque as well," Lu Yuqing said as she cast an incantation seal onto the jade pendant.

A streak of azure light flew into the pendant, following which the spiral patterns on its surface instantly began to revolve, and it released a streak of black light onto the Realm Traversing Plaque.

A spiral pattern also appeared on the Realm Traversing Plaque, and it warped and twisted momentarily before transforming into a palm-sized black vortex.

The vortex was constantly fluctuating in size, as if there were two conflicting forces trying to expand and contract it in unison.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing suddenly said, "Brother Han, it looks like this key of mine isn't a perfect match with this Realm Traversing Plaque, so I'll need you to inject more immortal spiritual power into it to support me!"

Han Li immediately laid a hand upon Lu Yuqing's jade pendant upon hearing this, and his immense immortal spiritual power surged out of his body before injecting itself into the jade pendant.

The pillar of black light shooting out of the jade pendant instantly became thicker, causing layers upon layers of rippling black light to emerge over the entire plaque.

At the same time, the palm-sized vortex at the center of the plaque seemed to have overcome the mysterious force that was trying to suppress it, and it was steadily expanding.

An elated look appeared in both Lu Yuqing and Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The black vortex on the Realm Traversing Plaque began to revolve faster and faster, and a burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of it, instantly pulling in Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

Han Li felt the entire world spin around him, and his vision abruptly faded before quickly returning again.

However, before he had a chance to steady himself and inspect his surroundings, the remaining flying swords erupted into a frenzy once again.

This time, he didn't even get a chance to stop them before all of them burst out of his sleeve, then shot up into the sky like dozens of rising azure dragons, vanishing into the clouds up above in the blink of an eye.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he took a glance down at his own empty sleeve, then swept his gaze over his surroundings.

Directly in front of him stood an enormous mountain that reached all the way up into the clouds.

The mountain was covered in dense vegetation, and it was thriving with vitality, in stark contrast with the environment from before.

Everything here was completely different from the earlier setting, to the point that Han Li was even beginning to suspect that he had fallen into an illusion.

However, after inspecting the area with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes and his Eye of Truth, he confirmed that this was, in fact, the real world.

Right as he was looking around with a perplexed expression, Lu Yuqing stumbled out of the space beside him.

She was also quite befuddled by what she was seeing, and she couldn't help but ask, "Have already entered the Realm Traversing Plaque, Brother Han?"

"I presume so. This place is a little strange. Right now, all of my bonded flying swords have flown onto that mountain," Han Li replied as he pointed at the mountain summit up ahead.

Han Li was feeling a little agitated from having his spiritual connection with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords severed, but now that he had entered the Realm Traversing Plaque, the spiritual connection had been restored, and he was feeling a lot more reassured.

"Those Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators shouldn't be able to come after us now. If your swords are on that mountain, then let's retrieve them and meet back up with our fellow daoists from the True Flame Sect as soon as possible," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that enveloped both himself and Lu Yuqing before rising up into the sky.

However, he had only risen to an altitude of no more than 1,000 feet when the sky above him suddenly took on a completely different complexion, and a burst of invisible pressure came crashing down without any warning.

Immediately thereafter, the clouds up above descended a little, and a burst of incredibly formidable sword qi surged down from the heavens. Countless streaks of semi-transparent swordlight swooped down from above with unstoppable might, and Lu Yuqing's face instantly turned deathly pale upon seeing this.

Han Li was hovering in mid-air, and specks of blue light emerged over his body as he threw a punch at the vast expanse of swordlight in the sky.

A burst of invisible force erupted out of his fist, hurtling directly upward, and a resounding boom rang out as the entire sky trembled violently, while a string of audible cracks rang out, as if the very space itself had been shattered.

All of the streaks of swordlight were instantly slowed down in their descent, and countless streaks of swordlight were destroyed altogether, exploding into innumerable translucent shards that erupted in all directions to create a huge opening.

Han Li immediately flew toward the opening upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to reach it, the clouds up above descended even further, and a layer of shiny swordlight emerged to fill the hole that Han Li was trying to exploit.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this as a thrust a palm upward, and a burst of black light instantly shot out of his hand, then transformed into his Heavy Water True Axis before hurtling directly upward.

With the infusion of second level heavy water, the Heavy Water True Axis had become incredibly formidable, and the Water Dao Runes on its surface were radiating dazzling black light, making it resemble a black sun.

At the same time, it was revolving rapidly like a giant black millstone, pulverizing all of the streaks of swordlight that were descending upon it.

However, as more layers of swordlight were destroyed, the clouds up above descended further and further. The swordlight in the sky was becoming denser and denser as a result, and the pressure in the air had become so severe that Han Li felt as if the surrounding space had become slightly warped.

At this point, Han Li had arrived at the conclusion that if he were to go all-out and resist the swordlight descending from the heavens without any regard for consequences, then perhaps he would be able to force his way through thanks to his treasures and his Profound Immortal Physique, but doing so while avoiding injury was far from a sure thing.

There were potentially many more perilous situations that he was going to have to face in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, so he wasn't willing to take the risk.

Thus, he descended back down to the ground as he said to Lu Yuqing, "The sword qi here is too vast for me to oppose, so we have no choice but to scale the mountain by foot."

"That's fine. At our speed, it shouldn't take us long to get to the top even on foot," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

With that, the two of them set off toward the foot of the mountain along the stone path beneath their feet.

After Han Li returned to the ground, the clouds that were bearing down from above slowly returned to their original altitude, and Han Li and Lu Yuqing didn't encounter any further obstructions as they continued their journey on foot.

Upon arriving at the foot of the mountain, the two of them were greeted by the sight of a tall stone archway, upon which was a massive plaque that bore some golden seal text characters.

"Boundless Sword Sect"

The strokes of the characters were strong and forceful, but also full of casual flair. They were as sharp as a sword, yet also wild and unrestrained, unlike the straight edge of a blade.

As soon as Han Li's gaze fell upon the plaque, he was immediately struck by a burst of tremendous sword intent, and he reflexively stumbled back a few steps with a surprised look on his face.

The Boundless Sword Sect had always been shrouded in mystery, and it had suddenly disappeared over a million years ago. Never had Han Li anticipated that he would discover it here.

As these thoughts were running through his mind, he took a glance at Lu Yuqing, only to find that she wasn't displaying any special reaction. Perhaps it was because she was unable to sense the sword intent imbued within the plaque due to her lack of affinity for the way of the sword.

Could there be some kind of sword restraining array that drew in my Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li strode through the stone archway with Lu Yuqing, and they continued their way up the mountain.

The ancient mountain path snaked up the mountain in circles like a spiraling staircase, and as Han Li and Lu Yuqing scaled the mountain, they encountered many mountains that were concealed within the undergrowth.

Upon closer inspection, they discovered that all of them were ordinary buildings that weren't being protected by any arrays or restrictions, and most of them had already become extremely dilapidated with age.

The closer they drew to the mountain summit, the more peaceful the surrounding environment became, and there was a forbidding atmosphere in the air, a notion that certainly wasn't helped by the complete lack of birds and beasts in the forest.

As they were passing through a green bamboo forest, Han Li suddenly stopped in his tracks as he spotted a dark green bamboo cabin deep within the forest.

After a brief moment of hesitation, he diverged from the stone path and made his way into the bamboo forest.

Lu Yuqing was rather curious about why Han Li had suddenly changed directions, but she remained silent and trailed along behind him.

Not long after making his way into the forest, he noticed some strange signs. For example, there were many sword marks on the bamboo trees that he was passing by, and the marks were all quite dark, clearly indicating that they had been inflicted many years ago.

Moments later, he stopped in his tracks, then grabbed onto a thick bamboo tree beside him before tightening his grip around it.

The bamboo tree immediately began to creak and groan, but it didn't shatter right away.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and he tightened his grip even further.

Finally, the bamboo tree exploded, sending countless pieces of shrapnel that were as hard as steel flying in all directions.

Chapter 434: Sword Resolution

"What kind of bamboo is this? It's so resilient!" Lu Yuqing asked with a surprised expression.

"It should be a type of Purple Essence Bamboo, one of the hardest types of trees in existence," Han Li replied.

He continued onward while speaking, making his way up the steps in front of the bamboo cabin before stepping through the entrance.

The cabin was barely furnished, with only a woven bamboo eight immortals table coupled with four long benches in the outer room, and seven bamboo beds in the inner room.

"These beds are so small and narrow... It feels like they're meant for children," Lu Yuqing mused with slightly furrowed brows.

"It's said that the Boundless Sword Sect was extremely strict in its recruitment of disciples. There was never any large intake of disciples. Instead, existing disciples were sent out to search for children with supreme swordsmanship attitude, and these children were nurtured from a young age. This is most likely some of those disciples stayed in their youth," Han Li speculated.

"I see. I've read some records about this sect by chance in an ancient scripture, and I recall that the sect had extremely few members, all of whom very rarely left the sect, so it was a very mysterious entity, but I don't know any more beyond that," Lu Yuqing said.

"If disciples of this sect wanted to leave as sect disciples, then they had to reach the Golden Immortal Stage first. Otherwise, they would have to stay in the sect until the day they died. During its heyday, there was once a story about the sect having seven Golden Immortals traveling the world together, but not many people know of this story nowadays," Han Li said.

"How do you know about this, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked with a curious expression.

"Technically, I'm a swordsman myself, so I keep an eye out for things like this in my reading. There are many more legends surrounding the Boundless Sword Sect, and the most renowned one pertains to the Boundless Sword Sea in its inner sect," Han Li continued.

"What's that?" Lu Yuqing asked with an intrigued expression.

Han Li began to make his way out of the bamboo cabin as he explained, "It's said that the founder of the Boundless Sword Sect, the Boundless Daoist, had a hobby of collecting swords. Regardless of whether it's a battle of life and death or just a casual spar, he would always take the flying swords of the opponents that he defeated to be kept in the sect's sword pond.

“All of the disciples that he took under his wing adopted the same tradition as well, and whenever they left the sect to explore the world, they would search for swords to bring back to the sect, and over time, the Boundless Sword Pond turned into the Boundless Sword Sea."

After emerging from the bamboo forest, the two of them continued up the winding mountain path, arriving at a stone staircase that extended all the way up into the clouds halfway up the mountain.

To the left of the stone staircase stood a giant black rock, upon which were inscribed the words "Sword Resolution Stone" in antiquated characters.

Han Li strode over to the giant rock, and upon close inspection, he discovered that there were two small lines of white text beneath the words "Sword Resolution Stone".

"True Immortals shall not take flight here, all swords of this world must bow their heads"

Every single character was giving off an indescribable aura of sharpness, as if each and every stroke was comprised of a streak of sword qi. It was clear that the inscription had been made by the same person as the one who had made the "Boundless Sword Sect" inscription on the plaque at the entrance.

"I can understand the first line alluding to how even True Immortals are unable to fly here, but what does the second line mean?" Lu Yuqing murmured to herself.

"The Boundless Sword Sea of the Boundless Sword Sect contains countless swords, and there's no larger collection of swords in this world. That's most likely what it means for all swords to have to bow their heads. However, what I'm struggling to understand is what this Sword Resolution Stone is supposed to be," Han Li mused.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out from the cloud above, and a burst of golden light emerged before spreading in all directions.

Han Li immediately looked to see what was happening overhead, while Lu Yuqing hurriedly asked, "What's happening, Brother Han?"

"Some type of restrictions seems to have been activated above the clouds. My spiritual connection with my bonded flying swords have been severed again," Han Li replied with tightly furrowed brows.

Immediately thereafter, he turned and strode onto the first stone step before launching himself diagonally upward, scaling several hundred steps with just a single leap.

Lu Yuqing immediately followed along in the same fashion, and the closer they drew to the mountain summit, the more humid the air became.

By the time they had reached an altitude of several thousand feet, they found themselves enshrouded in a cloud of misty water vapor.

As they traversed through the sea of mist, their visibility was severely hampered, and their spiritual sense was also significantly restricted.

"Something's not right with this mist... I can't see through it with my spirit eye ability, so be careful," Han Li cautioned as he conjured up a layer of protective spiritual light over his body and accelerated up the staircase.

Lu Yuqing was following along close on his heels with her ocular ability activated, and all of a sudden, she yelled, "Look out, Brother Han!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, two streaks of golden sword light came flying out of the dense mist above Han Li's head before hurtling down with one crossed over the other.

Han Li looked up to find that the two streaks of swordlight had been unleashed by a pair of tall wooden puppets with long and slender limbs.

Instead of retreating in the face of the attack, Han Li lunged forward instead, flying straight under the two streaks of swordlight.

As soon as he steadied himself, he instantly swiveled around, and a layer of azure light surfaced over his palm as he swung it toward the puppets in a chopping motion.

The two puppets remained completely still, but their heads suddenly swiveled around 180 degrees to face Han Li in a rather unsettling fashion.

At the same time, the joints of their sword-wielding hands also swiveled around, and one of the puppets parried Han Li's palm attack with its sword, while the other pierced its sword straight at Han Li's chest.

Han Li hurriedly sprang back in retreat to evade the attack, and he was feeling quite surprised.

The two puppets weren't giving off any aura at all, making it impossible to gauge their power level, but the swords that they were wielding were extremely formidable, as evidenced by the fact that it was able to slice through the azure light around his hand with ease.

Immediately thereafter, several more streaks of swordlight appeared above his head, then intertwined to form a golden sword net that swooped down upon him.

Han Li raised a fist before throwing a punch upward, releasing an azure fist projection, which was instantly sliced apart upon contact with the golden sword net.

Han Li swept a palm through the air once again, and this time, his Heavy Water True Axis flew out of his sleeve before rising upward like a revolving millstone.

The golden sword net appeared to be quite formidable, but upon coming into contact with the black light emanating from the Heavy Water True Axis, it instantly melted away like snow tossed into a fire.

Right at this moment, five more streaks of swordlight flashed through the air, and five additional wooden puppets appeared around Han Li without any warning.

As soon as these five puppets appeared, they were joined by the previous two puppets, which were charging at Han Li from behind with their swords aimed at the back of his chest.

However, before they had a chance to stride, two gusts of fierce azure wind rose up from down below, enveloping the pair of puppets before dragging them downward.

Han Li looked down to find Lu Yuqing wielding an azure feather fan that was radiating dazzling spiritual light, and with each wave, it was generating gusts of azure wind that trapped the wooden puppets inside.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, then thrust it forward, and the Heavy Water True Axis above his head instantly hurtled directly toward the puppet directly in front of him.

The puppet reacted quite quickly, making a hand seal with one hand while thrusting its longsword downward with the other.

A burst of golden light appeared on the tip of the longsword, and a massive golden sword projection erupted forth, crashing heavily into the Heavy Water True Axis.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and the golden sword projection was instantly vanquished, while the sword-wielding puppet's body was also inundated and pulverized by the black light surging out of the Heavy Water True Axis.

After absorbing so much second level heavy water, the Heavy Water True Axis had become far more formidable than before.

The other four sword-wielding puppets swiveled their heads around to lock their eyes on Han Li, and at the same time, a peculiar rune on each of their glabellas began to radiate golden light as they thrust the tips of their swords toward the heavens.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze upward, and a sense of foreboding instantly welled up in his heart.

Sure enough, the faint glimmers of light began to appear above the mist that enshrouded the entire area, and the sky quickly began to rumble as if a thunderstorm were approaching.

"Come to me, Fellow Daoist Lu!" he hurriedly yelled.

Lu Yuqing immediately swept her fan through the air without any hesitation, releasing two fierce gusts of wind that blew the pair of puppets aside, then flew over to Han Li's side in a flash.

She had only just gotten under the Heavy Water True Axis when a burst of deafening rumbling began to ring out overhead, and a vast expanse of golden radiance descended from the heavens.

It was a mass of countless streaks of golden swordlight identical to the ones that Han Li had to contend with while attempting to fly to the mountain summit.

Those streaks of swordlight had only been present to prevent people from taking flight, whereas this golden sword array was purely designed to kill its target, so the swordlight within it was far more formidable than before.

Not only that, but the descending streaks of swordlight were also imbued with faint hints of metal law fluctuations, and that was why Han Li had called Lu Yuqing to his side so urgently.

Chapter 435: Sea of Swords

A resounding boom rang out as the vast expanse of golden swordlight passed through the surrounding mist, then came crashing down upon the Heavy Water True Axis like a waterfall.

A string of loud clangs rang out in rapid succession overhead, and Han Li immediately made a hand seal, upon which a vast expanse of black light erupted out of the axis alongside several dozen bursts of heavy water, which intertwined in mid-air to form an enormous heavy water vortex.

Upon falling into the vortex, all of the golden swordlight was shredded into pieces without being able to put up any resistance.

All of a sudden, the Heavy Water True Axis shrank down to the size of a normal shield at Han Li's behest, then flew through the air as a long streak of black light, hurtling directly toward one of the wooden puppets.

The puppet remained still on the spot as it raised its sword to defend itself against the Heavy Water True Axis, and right as the two were about to clash, Han Li suddenly curled a finger upward, upon which the Heavy Water True Axis circled around in mid-air, avoiding the puppet's sword before striking it on the head.

A loud thump rang out as the puppet's head exploded amid an eruption of black light, and its headless body instantly fell away to the side as if it had been sapped of all of its strength.

Meanwhile, the golden longsword in its hand flew toward the mountain summit as a bright streak of light as if it had been summoned.

The other puppets paid no heed to this at all as they continued to come after Han Li and Lu Yuqing with their swords raised.

We can't afford to waste any more time here!

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he made a beckoning motion, and the Heavy Water True Axis instantly flew back to him before hovering above the palm of his hand, where it revolved incessantly.

At the same time, the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body began to revolve in reverse, and he abruptly shot through the air as a blurry shadow.

A string of afterimages suddenly flashed over the stone staircase, then abruptly drew to a halt.

Immediately thereafter, a string of explosions rang out as four of the six remaining puppets fell to the ground, having been decapitated.

Their longswords also flew toward the mountain summit as if they had been sucked away by some type of invisible force.

Meanwhile, Han Li took a moment to steady himself, and his complexion was looking a little pale. His breathing was also a little labored, and his Heavy Water True Axis was gradually slowing down in its revolution.

Simultaneously using the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Heavy Water True Axis was extremely taxing on his immortal spiritual power, and at his current cultivation base, he couldn't keep this up for long.

Lu Yuqing was still locked in battle against a pair of puppets, and she was rather taken aback to see both of them being decapitated in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out from the mountain summit, and the entire mountain began to tremble violently.

Han Li's expression changed slightly as he cast his gaze upward.

"There's no time to waste, Brother Han. Leave me here and go retrieve your flying swords, I'll be able to look after myself," Lu Yuqing suddenly said.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "Alright, make sure to be careful."

After that, he sprang up the ladder once again, and it didn't take long before he vanished into the dense mist up above.

In the wake of Han Li's departure, the two remaining puppets immediately tried to give chase, only for Lu Yuqing to appear in front of them in a flash.

At this moment, there was a rather peculiar look on her face, one that she had never adopted before. She appeared a little cold and distant, but also rather confused and disoriented, while a hint of moisture had appeared in her eyes.

With a flick of her wrist, she stowed the azure feather fan away, and it was replaced by a silver longsword that was clearly a treasure of a far inferior caliber to the azure fan.

She looked down at the longsword in her hand as she murmured to herself, "Why does it suddenly feel like using a sword isn't so bad?"

This wasn't said in a joking manner. Instead, she seemed to be genuinely confused, as if she didn't know herself why she suddenly wanted to use the sword.

……

After emerging from the area enshrouded within the dense mist, everything in front of Han Li immediately cleared up, and only then did he discover that he was still situated halfway up the mountain. There was still no end in sight to the stone staircase, but as Han Li continued to scale the staircase, he encountered no further obstructions.

Upon reaching the top, Han Li made his way along a bluestone mountain path toward the center of the mountain summit, and he spotted what appeared to be a daoist temple from afar, concealed behind a green bamboo forest.

The daoist temple wasn't very large, and there were all types of designs engraved onto its white walls and black tiled roof, giving it a rather intricate appearance.

Han Li naturally had no time to appreciate the scenery right now, and after verifying that there weren't any restrictions in the daoist temple, he pushed its black gate open before making his way directly inside.

The daoist temple was barely furnished at all. The first two of its three courtyards was comprised of around a dozen halls, most of which were empty, while the rest only had some unidentifiable deity statues inside.

There were also two halls that appeared to be pill refinement chambers with pill cauldrons placed inside, while the shelves on the walls were lined with containers of different sizes.

Han Li had no time to verify whether the contents of the containers could still be used, so he simply stowed everything away with a sweep of his sleeve.

The final courtyard of the daoist temple was quite far away from the first two, and down the center was a wide path paved with white stone slabs.

Han Li made his way down the path before arriving in front of a large hall.

There were seven or eight wooden puppets that were identical to the ones that he had encountered earlier strewn over the ground outside the hall's entrance.

Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings, and he quickly noticed that the wooden frames of the hall's doors and windows were all engraved with complex runes, clearly indicating that there was a formidable defensive restriction set up here.

However, the restriction had already been severely damaged, and there were wisps of residual sword qi present in many of the important points on the array, indicating that the damage had been inflicted not long ago.

There was a huge black plaque hanging directly above the center of the hall's entrance, upon which was inscribed the words "Ancestral Hall" in flowing golden characters.

Despite the shared name, the ancestral halls of cultivating sects and those of the mortal world were actually very different.

The ancestral halls of the mortal world were generally used to worship the memorial tablets of deceased ancestors. However, cultivators of the Immortal Realm led extremely long lives, so aside from a select few memorial tablets, the ancestral halls of the cultivating sects mostly contained treasures left behind by ancestors and founders.

These treasures weren't necessarily extremely powerful. Instead, most of them were personal treasures that these ancestors and founders liked to keep with them during their cultivation journeys.

These treasures had the closest ties with the sect, and as a result, it gradually turned into a tradition for treasures of this nature to be kept in the ancestral halls.

An ancestral hall was the heart of a sect's lineage, and it was often the center of a sect's fortune. There were many stories of treasures being kept in ancestral halls that became nurtured by the fortune of a sect over time, thereby attaining sentience on their own.

A very fortunate sect disciple could be chosen by one such sentient treasure while engaging in worship at the ancestral hall, and that would often be the beginning of a meteoric rise.

The furnishings in the Boundless Sword Sect's ancestral hall were very simplistic. There were two rows of eternal flame lamps in the hall, the flames in which had, ironically, already burned out. Down the center of the hall between the two rows of lamps were four worship tables standing on platforms of ascending heights.

If we take each tier as one generation, that means that the Boundless Sword Sect's heritage only lasted four generations...

Han Li was initially rather surprised by this observation, but it then quickly made sense to him considering the sect's method of disciple recruitment.

Han Li swept his gaze over the hall to find that aside from worship tables on the second and third tiers, which had several memorial tablets placed on them in a haphazard fashion, the remaining two tables only held some sandalwood platters, all of which were completely empty.

Han Li's gaze lingered momentarily on the worship table on the highest tier to find that there was no memorial tablet for the Boundless Daoist there.

It looks like the Boundless Daoist was still alive when the Boundless Sword Sect fell...

Right as Han Li was inspecting his surroundings, a crisp and pleasant chime suddenly rang out from the rear of the ancestral hall.

The sound wasn't very loud, but it was remarkably penetrative, traveling all the way here, and Han Li was able to hear it clearly even though he hadn't been listening out for it.

He immediately left the ancestral hall, then made his way toward the mountain behind the hall along a small bluestone path.

After walking for a few minutes, Han Li arrived on a downward-sloping hill.

Standing before him was a black rock that was only half the height of a grown man. It was a rather unremarkable structure, and it bore the words "Sword Sea" inscribed in antiquated text.

Han Li stood on the edge of the hill as he cast his gaze downward, and he spotted a glimmer of light in a meadow down below. He took a closer look, and a stunned look instantly appeared on his face.

As it turned out, there were countless flying swords plunged into the vibrant meadow down below. All of the swords had their tips pointing up at the sky, and they were swaying gently like blades of grass in the light breeze, gently tapping against each other to produce the pleasant chiming sound that Han Li had heard earlier.

Among these flying swords were tiny ones that were as thin as sewing needles, enormous ones that were as wide as city gates, squiggly ones that resembled winding snakes, straight ones with parallel edges... Every type of longsword that one could think of could be found here.

They had been in this sword sea for countless years, yet not a single one of them was displaying any signs of damage or rust, and all of them were radiating dazzling spiritual light.

Han Li's gaze roamed over the sea of swords for a moment before his eyes finally settled on a spot in the meadow, where he spotted his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords arranged in a uniform line, swaying gently alongside all of the other flying swords.

When he tried to summon them back to his side, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately began to sway in a more urgent and erratic fashion, as if they were trying to heed his call, but were also locked into place by some type of suppressive force.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li raised a hand, and a section of his sleeve flew off on its own, enveloped in a layer of gentle azure light.

The piece of sleeve drifted past the black rock and entered the sword sea, upon which barely visible streaks of light instantly flashed through the air around it.

In the blink of an eye, that sliver of sleeve was shredded into dust in complete silence.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Chapter 436: Lost

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out in the sky.

Han Li looked up to find a single white cloud with a golden lining in the air above the sea of swords.

Atop the cloud sat a massive white stone altar that was octagonal in shape with eight giant golden pillars around it, each of which was several hundred feet tall. There were extremely life-like coiling golden dragons engraved onto the pillars, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

Han Li was just about to fly up to the cloud for a closer inspection when another burst of rumbling suddenly rang out from the altar, following which a flash of red light shot out of the cloud.

Immediately thereafter, a ball of crimson flames abruptly surged out of the center of the cloud, and the entire cloud instantly took on a bright crimson hue, as if it had been set alight.

At the same time, a sea of crimson flames had also appeared beneath the white stone altar, illuminating the entire sky a bright red color.

With the cloud scattered, Han Li spotted a thin and stocky middle-aged man standing on the floating altar, and it was none other than Xiong Shan.

At this moment, there was a solemn look on his face, and his arms were raised to heavens as he chanted an incantation.

Hovering above his head was a large black metal plate that had a slight bulge in the center that was identical in appearance to the beveled metal scriptures awarded to officials in mortal empires, [1] and upon it was inscribed the words "Uniting All Swords".

As Xiong Shan continued to chant his incantation, the flames beneath the altar began to burn brighter and brighter, and waves of heat that were visible even to the naked eye began to surge through the air, causing the surrounding space to warp and shimmer.

All of the countless flying swords in the meadow were also beginning to sway much more violently, clanging against one another much more forcefully than before.

Han Li was initially a little perplexed upon seeing this, but he then quickly realized what was happening.

The so-called Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array that Xiong Shan had painstakingly created back in the Blaze Dragon Dao had most likely been an array that he had learned from the Boundless Sword Sect, and this was sea of swords had to have been the true spirit gathering sword array.

The sea of swords served as the foundation, the hovering altar was the cauldron, and the metal scripture filled the role of the catalyst, allowing Xiong Shan to draw upon the spirit of all of the countless flying swords here.

It was truly an extremely ambitious endeavor.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from the altar up above, causing the entire area to rumble incessantly.

All of a sudden, the entire mountain had begun trembling, and all of the sword qi in the meadow erupted into the heavens.

From Han Li's perspective, it appeared as if a gust of gentle wind had blown through the sea of swords, and all of the lush grass in the meadow was instantly severed before being shredded into countless pieces by the sword qi in the air.

At the same time, all of the swaying flying swords had become completely still, standing straight like soldiers ready for battle with their tips pointed up at the heavens.

On the altar, Xiong Shan took a deep breath, then suddenly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a golden flying sword that circled around momentarily in mid-air before hovering beneath the metal scripture.

Xiong Shan then joined the index and middle fingers of his right hand together, and a burst of golden light emerged over his fingertips as he swept them through the air, creating a golden rune that was around 10 feet in size.

The giant rune fell upon the metal scripture in a flash, and the latter immediately let loose an exultant ringing sound.

Immediately thereafter, a series of thin lines began to appear over the entire metal scripture, and they connected together before radiating dazzling golden light.

An incredibly thick pillar of golden light erupted out of the metal scripture straight up into the heavens, then exploded high up in the sky like a firework, forming a dazzling golden light barrier with countless projections surging over its surface.

There was a giant deity clad in golden armor wielding a massive blade capable of splitting mountains. There was a wraith-like masked assassin wielding a sword as thin as sewing needles, plucking out the heart of an enemy general. There was a gorgeous celestial maiden wielding a sword as elegant and free-flowing as her dress. There was a thin elderly man with a long beard directing the vast expanse of sword qi around him...

All types of sword-wielding figures were depicted in these projections, and Han Li was staring at the unfolding scene with his brows tightly furrowed in concentration.

Specks of golden light began to appear in his pupils, and in the next instant, he felt as if had become completely immersed in what he was witnessing.

He felt as if he had become another figure on the golden light barrier, wielding his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords to conjure up one sword lotus flower after another.

At the same time, a change suddenly began to take place in the sea of fire beneath the floating altar. The surging flames twisted around to form a massive fiery vortex, while then began to release bursts of formidable suction force.

All of the flying swords in the meadow down below immediately began to tremble and sway, then rose up into the air as if they had been summoned, hurtling toward the fiery vortex as a wave of flying swords.

The sky above the meadow instantly became extremely chaotic as a result, with swordlight of all colors shooting in all directions, slicing the entire space to ribbons. The invisible sword qi in the air was also no longer restricted to the meadow, beginning to spread in all directions instead.

The sound of tearing fabric rang out as Han Li's robes were brushed by some of the spreading sword qi, and a pair of extremely long gashes had been torn into the fabric.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he remained still and looked up at the sky.

In the heavens above, over 1,000 flying swords had surged into the fiery vortex, and they were instantly scorched a bright red color while giving off a miserable wailing sound.

Balls of light of all types of different colors began to fly out of the swords, and those were none other than their sword essence.

The flying swords that were stripped of their sword essence quickly dimmed before being refined into puddles of molten liquid that quickly vanished into the flames.

The capacity of the fiery vortex was limited, only able to take in fewer than 2,000 swords at a time. Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were situated closer to the back, so it was going to take some time before they were drawn into the vortex, but it wasn't going to be a very long time.

On the floating altar, Xiong Shan's brows were tightly furrowed as he murmured to himself, "I'll deal with you once I'm done refining my sword..."

He had already noticed Han Li's arrival, but he had been too busy working the array to do anything about it.

There was a hollow area on the floating platform in front of him, and at this moment, balls of sword essence were emerging from that area before hovering in mid-air.

Xiong Shan was ecstatic to see this, and made a peculiar hand seal with both hands before pointing a finger at the metal scripture.

The golden patterns on the metal scripture instantly flashed before releasing a vast expanse of golden light to envelop the golden longsword down below, forming a golden vortex upon it.

As soon as the vortex took shape, all of the sword essence hovering above the altar was instantly drawn to it before surging into Xiong Shan's bonded flying sword in a frenzy.

The golden longsword began to tremble and ring while radiating halos of golden light.

While the sword essence was being absorbed on the altar, the fiery vortex down below was constantly drawing in more flying swords, and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords was getting closer and closer to the vortex.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly shuddered, and the golden light in his eyes gradually faded, replaced by a layer of blue light.

"What a formidable array!" Han Li exclaimed to himself as a hint of elation appeared on his face.

The scenes depicted on the golden light barrier were very similar in nature to the Myriad Sword Artwork that he had obtained in the past, but this array was clearly far more profound, and it could even be said that the Myriad Sword Scroll was most likely a replica of this array.

While viewing the array, Han Li had actually intentionally opened himself up so that he would become immersed in it. Otherwise, given his current level of spiritual sense, there was no way that he would've completely lost himself just now.

Thanks to the complete immersion that he had opened himself up to, not only had he gained a deeper understanding of all sword arrays, he had also identified the key points in this array and the way that it operated.

On the altar, Xiong Shan's expression changed drastically at the sight of Han Li suddenly snapping back to his senses, and he exclaimed, "Impossible!"

It was no wonder that he was so shocked. Back when he first witnessed this array, he had been completely immersed in it for seven days and seven nights, and it was only through a stroke of luck that he was able to awaken.

He had managed to learn the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array from that experience, but his spiritual sense had been severely damaged, so he had no choice but to leave this area, and only after so many years had passed did he get another opportunity to come here.

Xiong Shan gritted his teeth in fury as he thrust both palms forward, pushing the balls of sword essence with his immortal spiritual power so that they would surge into his bonded flying sword at an even faster rate.

All of the flying swords in the sky twisted together before flowing incessantly into the fiery vortex, and at this point, Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were no more than 1,000 feet away from the fire.

He immediately stomped a foot down onto the ground upon seeing this, and the entire mountain shuddered violently beneath his feet as he launched himself up into the sky.

However, he had only just risen up into the air when a burst of asphyxiating pressure crashed down upon him from all directions, forcing him back down onto the ground.

At the same time, gusts of ferocious wind were sweeping through the air all around him, interspersed with countless streaks of sword qi that tore a series of gashes into his robes.

Han Li let loose a defiant roar as all of his profound acupoints lit up with blue light, and his True Extreme Film emerged over his body to keep all of the sword qi at bay.

The pressure weighing down upon him had slammed his body so heavily back down onto the ground that his legs had sunk deep into the earth.

Han Li looked up into the sky to find that Xiong Shan was standing on the edge of the altar, controlling the metal scripture with one hand while reaching out toward the sea of swords down below with his other hand.

At the same time, he was glowering intently at Han Li with fury and resentment in his eyes.

Only now had he realized that Li Feiyu was the one who had foiled his sword array all those years ago, the so-called "number one sword cultivator of Heavenly South".

[1]. For an idea of what this looks like, Google Image search "丹书铁券".

[Back]

Chapter 437: Vendetta

"This is the work of karma! You took my sword essence and spoiled my sword array, but looks what's happened now! Everything is still mine in the end!" Xiong Shan chortled with glee, and his voice rumbled across the sky like thunder.

He had made many enemies in order to gather so many spirit swords for his Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array, yet all of his efforts had been for nought thanks to Han Li.

He had been made the laughingstock of the entire Blaze Dragon Dao for years over this matter, so how could he not be ecstatic to exact his vengeance now?

"If you hadn't tried to refine my bonded flying swords, I wouldn't have foiled your sword array. You and I are both from the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Transient Guild, and we've worked together multiple times in the past, so how about we let bygones be bygones, and you let me recover my bonded flying swords?" Han Li proposed.

His voice wasn't very loud, but it was able to pierce through all of the layers of obstruction like a sharp sword to travel into Xiong Shan's ears.

"Shut your mouth! You've treated me like a fool this entire time! While it's true that I gradually came to realize your involvement in foiling my plans, there was no good opportunity to strike, so I continued to bide my time, but now that you've presented yourself to me on a silver platter, I'm going to refine both you and your bonded flying swords into my unmatched immortal sword!" Xiong Shan harrumphed coldly.

"If you're not willing to resolve this matter peacefully, then don't blame me for taking you down by force!" Han Li said in a cold voice.

"What a joke! Your death is imminent, yet you're still spouting nonsense!" Xiong Shan scoffed, but for some reason, he couldn't help but shudder internally in the face of Han Li's threat.

All of a sudden, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar, and his body rapidly swelled to over 1,000 feet tall while tufts of golden fur appeared over his skin as he took on his Giant Mountain Ape form.

He then stomped down viciously onto the ground, launching himself up into the sky in the face of the layers of sword qi above.

As it drew close to the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, the giant golden ape reached out with a thick and muscular arm, and a layer of golden scales appeared over its fur as it lashed out at the stream of swords flowing toward the fiery vortex.

A resounding boom rang out, and the entire stream of swords curved outward amid a chorus of chaotic clangs.

All of a sudden, all of the flying swords that were hurtling toward the fiery vortex were knocked off their original trajectory, and that included the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Immediately thereafter, the giant golden ape reverted back to its human form, and a pair of translucent wings abruptly appeared on Han Li's back as he twisted around, changing direction in mid-air to fly directly toward his bonded flying swords.

However, before he had a chance to get close, a burst of invisible force erupted out of the entire sword array, gathering all of the flying swords and dragging them back on course to flow into the fiery vortex.

"I'm not letting you get your way a second time!" Xiong Shan declared in a cold voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he made a string of hand seals before pointing a finger at the metal scripture that was hovering in the air before him.

A drop of blood essence that was glowing with golden light flew out of his fingertip before falling upon the metal scripture, and the golden patterns on its surface instantly shuddered, following which a burst of faint red mist rose up and surged into the golden light barrier up above.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden light barrier in the sky exploded violently, but all of the projections on it lingered, falling into the sword array like a storm of golden rain.

With each projection that flew into the array, a sword would diverge from the stream of sword before falling into the grasp of the golden projection and flying toward Han Li.

Han Li was just about to try something else to forcibly recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords when he suddenly felt a shadow loom over him. He immediately flapped his Thunderstorm Wings, flying back several dozen feet through the surrounding sword qi with great difficulty.

A giant sword that was as wide as a city gate came crashing down from above, just barely glancing past Han Li as it slashed down with tremendous power.

Han Li immediately raised a fist before giving the broad side of the sword's blade a vicious punch, and a giant azure fist projection instantly erupted upon the massive sword, causing it to tremble violently.

The golden giant that was holding the sword also shuddered violently from the immense force that was transferred through the sword, and it disintegrated into countless specks of golden light.

However, before Han Li had a chance to withdraw his fist, another golden figure wielding an extremely long sword charged directly at him.

Behind this golden figure were countless more, including a gorgeous woman, a burly man clad in a suit of golden armor, an elderly man with a long beard, a small child... Waves upon waves of sword-wielding figures were converging toward him once.

Han Li remained calm and collected as he took a stride forward, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of radiant golden light.

All of the projections and flying swords that entered the range of the ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly came to a standstill, and Han Li was able to casually make his way past them as if he were taking a stroll in the park.

All of the swords that were pierced toward him had become his stepping stones, allowing him to progress steadily toward the altar.

It had already become clear to him that if he didn't defeat Xiong Shan, then he would continue to use the power of the sword array to prevent him from retrieving his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords. Once enough time elapsed, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords would inevitably be destroyed.

Xiong Shan was astonished to see this from the altar, and he looked on in shock as Han Li approached the altar from afar.

However, he then quickly composed himself and gritted his teeth tightly as he made his way back to the center of the array, where he cast a series of incantation seals into the hollow area before him.

Immediately thereafter, he spread a hand open, and five longan-sized golden beads dropped into the hollow area at once to fall into the sea of fire down below.

All of the flames below instantly began to sway violently, as if a fierce gust of wind were blowing through them, and the fire was spread in all directions.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the flames to see five balls of golden light emerge within it, drawing in all of the surrounding fire to form five menacing draconic heads, all of which were turned to face him.

As soon as the draconic heads took shape, a thin jet of fire instantly shot out of each of their nostrils, and their eyes also lit up with radiant golden light, making it appear as if they were actual living creatures.

In the next instant, an animalistic roar rang out from within the sea of fire, and five fiery dragons that were as thick as water vats flew out, twisting around in mid-air before pouncing at Han Li with tremendous power.

Waves of scorching heat erupted forth in all directions, causing the entire space to warp and shimmer, to the point that even the golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis had begun to warp, thereby significantly shrinking their effective area.

In the face of the oncoming fiery dragons, Han Li raised a hand before sweeping it through the air, and his Heavy Water True Axis flew out of his sleeve, then swelled to the size of a millstone while revolving rapidly as it positioned itself in front of him.

At the same time, the Water Dao Runes on its surface began to glow radiantly as it released bursts of heavy water, which converged to form a huge heavy water vortex that surged toward the five fiery dragons.

The five fiery dragons opened their cavernous mouths, and there was molten lava bubbling inside while releasing plumes of black smoke, making them resemble five volcanoes that were on the verge of eruption.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as vast torrents of lava and fiery rocks came pouring out of the five dragons' mouths down upon the Heavy Water True Axis.

A string of deafening booms rang out as the entire sky was illuminated bright red.

As the ferocious storm of fire crashed down onto the Heavy Water True Axis, enormous black waves were instantly raised, and even though the axis was able to hold its own, it was clearly struggling under the formidable barrage.

Han Li's arms were raised aloft, and his entire body was trembling uncontrollably, indicating that he was clearly also struggling to keep the assault at bay.

All of a sudden, he let loose a thunderous roar, and instead of retreating, he thrust his palms forcefully against his Heavy Water True Axis, which instantly released an enormous wave of black heavy water that swept toward the five fiery dragons in retaliation.

The fiery dragons also swooped down from above, and a clash of tremendous power took place as fire and water intertwined with one another, causing a cloud of white mist to rise up into the sky.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly declared, "All-encompassing black wave!"

An earth-shattering boom instantly rang out in the sky above the floating altar, and a bolt of white lightning flashed past, tearing an enormous black gash into the heavens.

What seemed like an infinite volume of heavy water surged out of the black rift, forming a gargantuan black waterfall that came crashing down from above.

Xiong Shan could only stare up at the heavens with his eyes wide with despair and incredulity.

How was it possible that a True Immortal could be capable of wielding such incredible power?

However, at this point, it was already far too late to try and call a truce.

With that in mind, he could only grit his teeth as he swept his sleeves through the air, releasing one incantation seal after another into the metal scripture.

The golden light radiating from the metal scripture immediately began to flash while releasing a string of golden runes, which fell upon the eight golden pillars around the array.

The golden pillars instantly began to glow radiantly, and the eight golden dragons coiled around the pillars raised their heads as beams of crimson light shot out of their eyes, then converged directly above the altar to form a crimson light barrier that was riddled with draconic patterns, just in time to oppose the vast torrent of heavy water that was crashing down from above.

Chapter 438: Sword Battle

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out incessantly as the crimson light barrier trembled violently, quivering under the weight of the black waterfall.

Situated directly under the enormous torrent of heavy water, Xiong Shan could see the black waterfall crashing down onto the crimson light barrier, and he could also clearly sense the tremendous pressure that was weighing down the light barrier from above.

A series of massive indentations had appeared all over the crimson light barrier in the face of the heavy water torrent's immeasurable weight, and the golden draconic patterns on it were also flashing incessantly, indicating that the light barrier wasn't going to be able to withstand the assault for much longer.

Xiong Shan's brows were tightly furrowed as he took a glance at the metal scripture that was hovering in mid-air, and he made a beckoning motion to draw it back into his grasp.

He then extended his index finger, and a burst of golden light flashed over his fingertip, resulting in a tiny bleeding gash.

Using his finger as a brush and his blood as ink, he began to quickly inscribe a peculiar dark red rune onto the metal scripture.

As soon as the rune took shape, the golden patterns on the metal scripture began to take on a bright red hue, resembling a system of blood vessels and meridians.

Xiong Shan held the metal scripture in both hands as a determined look appeared on his face, and he brought the metal scripture to his own chest like a breastplate.

Red and black light flashed over his chest, and the metal scripture vanished into his body in a flash, fusing as one with him.

The metal scripture was serving as the core of the entire array, and with its disappearance, the array instantly ceased to operate.

The sea of fire beneath the floating altar subsided, gradually reverting back into a scorching fiery cloud, while the crimson light barrier up above also disintegrated into a vast expanse of translucent red light.

All of the golden projections up above also vanished, but the flying swords that had been drawn toward the array didn't descend back down onto the meadow. Instead, they continued to hover in mid-air, remaining locked into place by a burst of invisible force.

The black waterfall in the sky was nothing more than an illusion conjured up by Han Li's Mantra Domain, and it had also faded away, restoring heaven and earth to their original state.

Without the obstruction posed by the golden projections and the fiery dragons, Han Li was able to ascend into the heavens at a rapid speed, and in the blink of an eye, he had already fallen upon the floating altar.

He cast his gaze toward Xiong Shan to find that the latter's entire body had been encased in a suit of black scale armor, and there was also a layer of crimson light around him.

The layer of crimson light was formed by countless wisps of extremely pure sword qi that were so incredibly sharp that even the space around them had been completely shredded, and even the golden ripples released by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis were unable to infiltrate them.

"To think that you would use such a precious treasure in such a suboptimal fashion. Don't you think this is a massive waste?" Han Li asked with a forlorn shake of his head.

"It's fine. I'm only using up some of the sword qi within it. As long as I can kill you, it'll all be worth it," Xiong Shan replied as he strode over to the center of the altar, where he grabbed onto the hilt of his golden longsword.

As soon as his hand closed around his longsword, the dark red patterns on his suit of black armor instantly lit up, and the layer of crimson light around his body surged forth to encompass his bonded flying sword as well.

His aura remained at the late-True Immortal Stage, but it had become indescribably sharp, as if he had transformed into a peerlessly sharp immortal sword.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, but he remained unfazed.

Instead of immediately lashing out at Han Li, Xiong Shan said in an unhurried manner, "There's something that I've never been able to wrap my head around: how were you able to control my Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array back then? Could it be that you're the heir to some side branch of the Boundless Sword Sect?"

"Didn't the Boundless Sword Sect disappear over a million years ago? How could I be a side branch heir of the sect?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"So you're not a member of the sect... No matter, you've shown yourself to be worthy of facing me," Xiong Shan said as a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes, following which he launched himself directly at Han Li with his longsword pointed forward.

Han Li immediately drifted up into the air, and even after retreating all the way to the edge of the altar, he still showed no sign of stopping as he continued to fly back in retreat.

A burst of dark red light flashed over Xiong Shan's longsword, and a streak of crimson swordlight erupted out of its tip, instantly covering a distance of over 1,000 feet.

Only upon reaching within several feet of Han Li's chest was the streak of crimson swordlight finally slowed down by the golden ripples released by his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li took advantage of this opportunity to retreat several dozen feet further before stopping again.

The streak of crimson swordlight then slowly disintegrated as he looked on with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes. If he hadn't retreated in a timely fashion just now, that sword strike would've definitely been fast enough to counteract the Mantra Treasured Axis's time-slow effect and pierce straight through his chest.

If only all of the Time Dao Runes were recovered...

As this thought flashed through Han Li's mind, he swooped down toward all of the flying swords that were hovering mid-air.

However, before he was able to reach his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, he felt a burst of formidable sword qi sweeping toward him from behind, and a chill immediately ran down his spine.

He hurriedly reversed his Mantra Treasured Axis before dodging to the right, thereby allowing him to evade the attack.

A streak of crimson light flew past him in a flash before piercing straight into the vast array of flying swords up ahead, and a string of sharp clangs rang out as several dozen flying swords were shattered by the streak of swordlight.

Finally, Han Li was able to pounce on this opportunity to arrive beside his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

He reached out to grab onto one of them before tugging on it with all his might, only to find that it remained completely unmoved, seemingly locked into place by some type of tremendous force.

Before he had a chance to do anything, Xiong Shan arrived on the scene, then slashed his longsword viciously through the air.

However, Han Li paid no heed to the attack as he continued to hold tightly onto the hilt of his flying sword while injecting a wisp of his spiritual sense into it.

The sword in his grasp abruptly shuddered before letting loose a crisp ringing sound, as if it were elated to have had its spiritual connection with Han Li restored.

At the same time, a longsword that was enveloped in a layer of crimson light swept through the air toward the back of his neck.

The dozen or so active Time Dao Runes on Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis lit up in unison, and the golden ripples radiating from the axis took on a slightly more substantial form.

However, the oncoming longsword was able to largely ignore the Mantra Treasured Axis's time-slowing effect thanks to the formidable sword qi that it was enshrouded within, and the sword wasn't slowed down to a sufficient degree for Han Li to evade the attack.

In this dire situation, Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis flew onto the scene as a streak of black light, positioning itself in the path of Xiong Shan's sword like a giant black shield.

A sharp clang rang out as Xiong Shan's longsword pierced straight through the black light around the Heavy Water True Axis before striking the axis itself.

The Heavy Water True Axis shuddered violently as a large section of the black light radiating from it was shredded by the sword qi erupting out of Xiong Shan's sword, inflicting a deep sword mark onto its surface.

Han Li could sense the power of that sword strike through his spiritual connection with his Heavy Water True Axis, and he was greatly alarmed.

He immediately pulled out the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that he had grabbed onto, and at the same time, blue light flashed within his eyes as he released 71 wisps of spiritual sense at once, with each one entering one of the remaining 71 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

At this point, Xiong Shan had already made his way around the Heavy Water True Axis and was slashing his sword at Han Li from his right.

This time, Han Li didn't take any evasive measures. Instead, he met Xiong Shan directly retaliating with his own Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

The two swords clashed, and a layer of dark red swordlight erupted out of Xiong Shan's bonded flying sword, immediately following which a burst of golden lightning erupted out of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword as well.

The dark red swordlight glanced over Han Li's sword-wielding arm, instantly slicing through his sleeve, but thankfully, his True Extreme Film remained resolute, so he didn't sustain any injuries.

However, the sword qi imbued within the swordlight was extremely penetrative, and it felt as if it were slicing over the bones in his arm, causing him to wince in pain.

He ignored the pain as he made a beckoning motion with his other hand, and the Heavy Water True Axis behind him immediately shrank down to the size of a normal shield before hurtling directly toward Xiong Shan.

The armor on Xiong Shan's arm flashed with black light, scattering the Divine Devilbane Lightning released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, following which the blade of the sword made direct contact with the armor itself.

At the same time, the Heavy Water True Axis crashed into Xiong Shan's longsword, and the impact sent him flying back over 100 feet.

Right at this moment, Han Li made a hand seal before pointing a finger forward, and all of the remaining 71 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out in unison alongside the sword in Han Li's grasp, hurtling directly toward Xiong Shan as a wave of azure light.

As the flying swords raced through the air, countless streaks of azure swordlight intertwined and converged in the same spot to form a massive ball of azure light.

As it approached Xiong Shan, a thunderous draconic roar suddenly erupted out of the ball of azure light, ringing out across the entire sky.

Immediately thereafter, the giant ball of light exploded violently, and an azure coiled dragon sprang out from within with tremendous force before swallowing Xiong Shan whole.

At the same time, Han Li reversed his Mantra Treasured Axis while simultaneously summoning his Heavy Water True Axis back to him as he sprang forward in pursuit.

He was flying through the air far faster than the azure dragon sword array, and upon catching up to the head of the dragon, he focused his gaze downward, upon which a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

As it turned out, Xiong Shan was standing in the dragon's maw in a relaxed and composed manner, and there were hundreds of streaks of swordlight attempting to pierce into his body, but his suit of black armor was keeping him completely unscathed.

Chapter 439: Pushed to the Limits

Han Li gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and he sped directly toward the azure coiled dragon, leaving a string of afterimages in his wake.

His Heavy Water True Axis was revolving rapidly over the palm of his hand as it swept toward Xiong Shan, who let loose a thunderous roar as a burst of dard red swordlight erupted out of his suit of black armor, instantly destroying the azure coiled dragon around him.

He then raised an arm and swung his longsword heavily down onto the Heavy Water True Axis, and a sharp clang rang out as the azure dragon sword array reverted back into 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that were scattered in all directions, while Xiong Shan flew back over 1,000 feet before steadying himself.

"Are you trying to compete with me to see who has more swords?" he scoffed with a mocking sneer.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he tossed the longsword in his hand forward, then made a peculiar hand seal and chanted an incantation before sweeping his sleeves through the air.

All of the dark red patterns on his suit of black armor lit up once again, and an antiquated rune appeared on his breastplate.

As soon as that rune emerged, a vast and primordial aura instantly began to emanate out of Xiong Shan's body.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he hurriedly contacted Daoist Xie with his spiritual sense, telling it to prepare to intervene when necessary.

All of a sudden, the entire sky had become deathly silent, and even the sound of the wind had been stifled.

However, a burst of metallic screeching then suddenly rang out, breaking the silence in a very abrupt and disruptive fashion.

Han Li looked down to find that all of the swords on the meadow down below had begun moving again, and every single sword was enveloped in a layer of dark red swordlight, coming together to form what resembled a giant primordial beast that was only just beginning to awaken.

"Let's see you deal with all these swords at once!" Xiong Shan roared with a furious expression, and all of the swords instantly surged through the air at his behest like a swarm of all-encompassing locusts.

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this. Such a vast barrage of swords coupled with such formidable swordlight was a combination that was clearly too powerful for either his Mantra Treasured Axis or Heavy Water True Axis to oppose.

With that in mind, the only feasible course of action for him was to run.

His sole objective for coming here was just to recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and now that he objective had been achieved, there was no point in continuing this battle.

Xiong Shan was most definitely going to become a sworn enemy of his after this encounter, but that was something for him to worry about another time.

After making up his mind, Han Li immediately withdrew all of his treasures before making a hand seal, and a golden lightning array quickly took shape around him.

In order to conjure up the lightning array as quickly as possible, he had directly used his Divine Devilbane Lightning rather than drawing upon the power of the Lightning Bird, but even so, he was still too slow.

A streak of dark red swordlight came slashing down from above, and the golden lightning array had only just taken shape before it was destroyed.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li was instantly inundated by countless flying swords of all types of descriptions.

His expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but he remained calm and composed as a streak of silver light flew out of his sleeve, transforming into a silver bell that rose up into the air above him while swaying incessantly from side to side.

A series of dense silver halos spread through the air in all directions, proliferating outward to encompass an area that was several hundred feet in size.

At the same time, he opened his mouth to release the Seven Bright Star Rings, which connected together with one another in a flash to form an even larger ring above his head.

Radiant starlight erupted out of the Seven Bright Star Rings, forming a starlight barrier with countless star designs flashing on its surface, protecting him alongside the waves of silver ripples.

He had only just managed to summon these two treasures when the torrential wave of swords was already upon him, and in the blink of an eye, he was enveloped by swords from all directions.

The silver bell was chiming incessantly, yet the silver ripples that it was releasing continued to be worn down little by little, reducing the size of the safe area around Han Li.

The starlight barrier released by the Seven Bright Star Rings was also screeching incessantly as one speck of starlight was snuffed out after another.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he swept both sleeves through the air, and his Heavy Water True Axis and Mantra Treasured Axis emerged on either side of him in unison.

He then made a hand seal before thrusting a palm into his Heavy Water True Axis, and the black light on its surface shuddered while a vast torrent of heavy water erupted out of its Water Dao Runes, forming a black water dragon that surged into the wave of countless swords.

The heavy water dragon was enormous, and it resembled a vast river flowing through the sky, quickly blasting an opening into the vast expanse of swords. Han Li immediately flew toward that opening, while Xiong Shan looked on with a cold sneer on his face.

"What's the point? Your struggles are futile!"

Immediately thereafter, he wiped a hand over his own face, and the palm of his hand was instantly stained red.

There was a price that had to be paid for forcibly drawing upon the power of the metal scripture, and he was already beginning to bleed out of all of his orifices, but in his eyes, it would all be worth it if he could kill Han Li and recover those 72 swords.

All of a sudden, Xiong Shan let loose a thunderous roar, and all of the swords on either side of the opening that Han Li had created instantly converged at his behest, closing in around Han Li like a pair of impregnable walls.

The dark red light on the two walls of swords was becoming denser and denser, and Han Li wasn't even able to fly 1,000 feet before the sword array up ahead had already come together again, and the heavy water dragon was also destroyed under the immense pressure, disintegrating into droplets of heavy water that flowed back into the Heavy Water True Axis.

This was an even more dire situation than before, and his silver bell and Seven Bright Star Rings weren't going to be able to afford him much more protection.

It wasn't going to be long before these two treasures would also crumble under the pressure.

A string of faint cracks rang out from above Han Li's head, and a layer of hairline cracks had already appeared on the starlight barrier above, clearly indicating that it wasn't going to be able to hold itself together for much longer.

Han Li made a beckoning motion upon seeing this, and the starry light barrier faded, while the Seven Bright Star Rings flew back to him.

At the same time, the silver bell also shuddered slightly before circling around in mid-air and flying back to him as well.

In the next instant, purplish-golden light erupted out of his entire body alongside a layer of purplish-golden scales, and two additional sets of heads and arms emerged from his body.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li drew his Heavy Water True Axis back to himself, grabbing onto it with one hand like a shield while also clasping each of his other five hands around an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

He was also channeling the Xuanwu bloodline that he hadn't used in a very long time, forming a suit of dark green armor with antiquated runes all over its surface to protect his midsection.

Han Li's physical prowess had always been his forte, and in his current form, his physical constitution was no less resilient than many defensive spirit treasures.

His Mantra Treasured Axis flew back into his body, then immediately began to spin in reverse, and instead of continuing to adopt passive defense, Han Li went on the attack, flying straight into the torrent of swords.

He was moving as fast as lightning, traversing through the sea of swords while leaving a string of blurry afterimages in his wake, and he was constantly swinging his five Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords with tremendous power, releasing formidable bolts of golden lightning with every single swing to scatter the nearby flying swords.

Despite the vast number of swords in the array, it was unable to strike Han Li down.

However, Han Li knew that he wouldn't be able to keep this up for long. Maintaining this form over any extended period of time was simply far too taxing, and the instant that he ran out of immortal spiritual power would be the instant that spelled his demise.

He wasn't flying headfirst into the oncoming torrent of swords as he had lost all sense of rationality and was charging forward out of desperation. Instead, he had done this to buy Daoist Xie some time to recover.

Back when he was conjuring up the lightning teleportation array earlier, he had already tried to call upon Daoist Xie to buy him some time, only to discover that Daoist Xie's puppet body was still recovering from the attack that it had unleashed to vanquish that copper puppet, thereby rendering it unable to help.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li was clearly beginning to slow down. The suit of azure armor around his body was already riddled with sword marks, and his six arms were also lined with gashes.

Even with his incredibly formidable physical body, it was clear that he was nearing his limits.

"Are you still not ready, Brother Xie?" Han Li yelled internally in an urgent manner.

"I'm going to need a few more minutes," Daoist Xie replied through their spiritual connection.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this, but in this situation, all he could do was grit his teeth and persevere.

However, Xiong Shan wasn't willing to drag this out any longer, not because he had seen through Han Li's intentions, but instead because he was also not going to be able to last much longer.

At this point, blood was practically gushing out of his orifices, and he was beginning to feel a little faint from the blood loss.

He shook his head vigorously to clear the foggy sensation in his head, and his facial features became slightly twisted as he roared, "Die!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he launched himself forward as a streak of crimson light, fusing as one with his bonded flying sword to transform into a giant streak of crimson swordlight that hurtled directly toward Han Li at an astonishing speed.

The streak of crimson swordlight was extraordinarily fast, and all of the swords in its path quickly parted, forming a passageway that led straight to Han Li.

Chapter 440: Sword Refinement

Han Li's vision had been obstructed by the vast expanse of swords before him, and by the time he spotted the streak of crimson swordlight, it was already too late for him to take evasive measures.

In this dire situation, he quickly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique before unleashing his Spirit Stun Thorn. [1]

All of a sudden, Xiong Shan felt a cold harrumph ring out in his mind, and a burst of sharp pain speared through the head, resulting in a split second of disorientation.

The streak of oncoming crimson swordlight abruptly shuddered and drew to a halt around 10 feet away from Han Li, and this minuscule delay was enough to turn the tide of the entire battle!

The Mantra Treasured Axis in Han Li's body spun rapidly in reverse as he flapped his Thunderstorm Wings vigorously while also drawing upon his Azure Luan Bird bloodline, allowing him to reach an astonishing speed as he flew to one side of the streak of crimson swordlight before piercing all five of his swords toward a single spot.

A resounding boom rang out as the streak of crimson swordlight exploded, and violent shockwaves erupted in all directions, causing Han Li to throw up a mouthful of blood as he flew back several thousand feet into the vast torrent of swords behind him.

At the same time, scraps of black metal flew out of the streak of crimson swordlight that had just imploded, and they converged in mid-air to reform the black metal scripture.

A figure then stumbled out of thin air, looking deathly pale, and it was none other than Xiong Shan.

A huge hole had been torn through his chest, and his heart had already been completely destroyed. The dark red patterns on his body appeared to be intact, but in reality, they had already been severed into countless pieces.

There was a deranged look on his face as he used his longsword as a crutch while stumbling toward the metal scripture, but with each step that he took, a chunk of flesh would fall off his body, and by the time he reached the metal scripture, only a bare skeleton of his remained.

Immediately thereafter, the golden longsword in his hand also shattered into countless pieces that flew away in all directions.

A streak of golden light flew out of the top of the skeleton's skull, forming a golden nascent soul with a weary look on its face. The nascent soul turned to look at Han Li, who had only just steadied himself several thousand feet away, and it murmured to itself, "Is this the design of fate..."

As soon as its voice trailed off, the nascent soul also disintegrated into golden light, while Han Li looked on with mixed emotions.

He didn't harbor much enmity toward Xinog Shan, and they had been comrades several times in the past. If it weren't for Xiong Shan's insistence on hunting him down, he would've avoided this battle entirely.

With Xiong Shan's demise, the sword array in the sky instantly fell apart, and all of the flying swords suspended in the air came raining back down into the Boundless Sword Sea.

Han Li flew up into the air before drawing Xiong Shan's storage bracelet into his grasp, then reached out to grab the metal scripture as well before descending onto the floating altar in the sky.

He examined the metal scripture in his hand to discover that it bore the appearance of a piece of shattered chinaware. Its surface was riddled with extremely deep cracks, and it looked as if it could crumble away at any moment.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he scrutinized the metal scripture.

Having gleaned the secrets of the golden light barrier from earlier, he had learned how to use this sword refinement array, but he didn't know if the metal scripture could support the sword refinement process in its current terrible condition.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he sat down with his legs crossed and set the metal scripture aside, then swallowed a pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

A short while later, he rose to his feet and picked up the metal scripture again, then cast his gaze toward a certain direction as he murmured to himself, "I have to give it a try. I suppose it could be considered as completing your dying wish in your stead."

With that, he tossed the metal scripture forward, and it immediately lit up as it flew back onto the altar.

After that, Han Li began to chant an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, and the cloud beneath the altar was reignited, transforming into a sea of crimson flames once again.

……

Meanwhile, elsewhere in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

A green jade flying carriage that was around 100 feet in length was racing through the sky.

At the front of the carriage stood a tall man with a disk treasure held in his hands. A layer of white mist was hovering above the treasure, and there was a speck of red light that was flashing incessantly at its center.

"Could those maggots from the Reincarnation Palace be responsible for this?" the man murmured to himself with a perplexed expression.

There was a pair of golden armored puppets standing behind him with halberds held in their hands, and they displayed no reaction.

……

Halfway up the Boundless Sword Sect mountain, Lu Yuqing was standing with her silver longsword clasped behind her as she looked up at the mountain summit.

Her vision was still obstructed by the dense mist up above, and there had been quite a loud commotion ringing out a little earlier, but it had since subsided.

It seemed that whatever was taking place up there had concluded, and peace and quiet were restored.

As for the wooden puppets that she had been battling, they had already been reduced to a pile of wood scraps strewn all over the ground around her.

After a long hesitation, Lu Yuqing finally made up her mind, setting foot onto the stone staircase to make her way up toward the mountain summit.

……

On the floating altar, Han Li was sweating profusely as azure light surged all around him.

His 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were currently suspended above the hollow section at the center of the altar, and they seemed to have been arranged into some type of special formation with arcs of golden lightning surging between them.

Meanwhile, balls of glowing sword essence of different colors were constantly rising up and surging into the swords from the scorching flames down below.

As time passed, fewer and fewer swords remained in the Boundless Sword Sea, while the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords absorbed more and more sword essence, and the collective aura that they were releasing became more and more formidable.

Han Li was observing the process intently with bated breath.

As the final batch of sword essence flowed into the 72 flying swords, a faint crack suddenly rang out up above, and Han Li's heart immediately sank slightly upon hearing this sound.

Immediately thereafter, radiant golden light erupted out of the cracks on the metal scripture, and it looked as if it were about to explode.

With the example set by Xiong Shan earlier, Han Li was well aware of the consequences that would ensue if the metal scripture were to be destroyed, so he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, trying to pull the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords away from the altar before getting away.

However, as soon as his immortal spiritual power came into contact with the flying swords, a burst of lightning that was interspersed with tremendous sword qi instantly erupted out of the swords to pulverize his sleeve.

Immediately thereafter, a numb sensation spread through his entire body, rendering him temporarily immobilized.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light suddenly flashed over his storage bracelet, following which a peculiar palm-sized jade badge flew out from within before drifting directly toward the metal scripture.

Han Li was quickly able to identify the jade badge as something that had been given to him by Elder Qi Heng of the Holy Puppet Sect.

During their battle all those years ago, Qi Heng had once unleashed the Seven Deaths Sword Array of the Boundless Sword Sect, and it seemed that this strange jade badge was something from the Boundless Sword Sect as well.

Before Han Li had a chance to ponder this matter any further, the jade badge suddenly began to glow radiantly while becoming completely transparent, and a series of threads of golden light emerged within it to form a string of antiquated characters that read "Boundless Sword Core".

Following the emergence of the golden characters, the white jade badge gradually fused as one with the light radiating from the metal scripture,

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and a dense dark cloud suddenly appeared out of nowhere above the altar. Azure and purple light was flashing incessantly within the dark cloud amid bursts of rumbling thunderclaps, and golden light abruptly flashed within the eyes of the golden dragons coiled around the eight surrounding pillars, as if they had suddenly sprung to life.

At the same time, they were giving off vast auras, and it seemed that they could fly out of the pillars at any moment.

Immediately thereafter, the eight dragons opened their mouths at once to blast forth streams of crimson flames toward the center of the altar, and the flames converged in mid-air to form a raging sea of fire.

As soon as Han Li's bodily functions returned to him, he immediately flew through the air to situate himself outside the altar.

Immediately thereafter, the sea of flames came surging down from the heavens, inundating the entire altar in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, a resounding thunderclap rang out in the sky, and a waterfall of azure and purple lightning came crashing down, plunging straight into the scorching flames.

It was impossible to see the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords through the lightning and fire, and even Han Li's spiritual sense was unable to make any inroads.

Only now did the sword refinement truly begin.

Han Li wore a complex expression as he sat down in mid-air and observed from afar.

Three days passed by in the blink of an eye, and the mouths of the eight dragons coiled around the pillars surrounding the altars.

The sea of fire that engulfed the altar had expanded even further compared with three days ago, and bolts of azure and purple lightning continued to rain down from the heavens into the scorching flames below.

Han Li was standing near the sea of fire, and it seemed that he had already recovered from the injuries that he had sustained from the prior battle, but there was a slightly anxious look in his eyes.

The sword refinement process had gone on far longer than he had anticipated, and it was completely out of his control, so all he could do was stand and wait. Fortunately, Xue Han and the others hadn't entered this place up to this point.

Inside the daoist temple down below was Lu Yuqing, who had arrived on the mountain summit some time ago.

At this moment, she was casually strolling through the daoist temple, stopping in front of a dilapidated pavilion one moment, then crouching down in front of a moss-covered well the next.

She was constantly inspecting her surroundings with a slightly lost look in her eyes, and it seemed as if she were struggling to recollect something.

[1]. For more information on the Spirit Stun Thorn, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1046: Devil Slaying.

[Back]

Chapter 441: A Sword to Split the Heavens

Finally, Lu Yuqing drew to a halt in front of the ancestral hall at the center of the daoist temple.

Her brows furrowed slightly as her gaze roamed over the memorial tablets before her, and she was looking a little dazed.

Right at this moment, a thunderous boom rang out in the sky, and she shuddered as she instantly snapped back to her senses, then hurriedly made her way out of the daoist temple to look up into the sky.

A streak of dazzling azure light was in the process of rising up from the sea of flames up above, and it transformed into a pillar of azure light that erupted straight into the heavens.

Tremendous sword qi was emanating from the pillar of azure light, stirring the sea of fire up into a frenzy, and the lightning that was crashing down from above was also thrown into a state of disarray.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, another resounding boom rang out as yet another pillar of azure light rose up from the sea of flames while releasing aextremely formidable sword qi.

One pillar of azure light rose up after another in rapid succession, and a total of 72 pillars of light had emerged in the blink of an eye, all of which were giving off terrifying sword qi fluctuations.

The sea of fire was snuffed out with ease by this burst of collective sword qi, revealing the white stone altar inside.

The dark clouds up above were also completely scattered by the enormous sword qi in the air, while gusts of ferocious wind swept forth in all directions.

Han Li wore a calm expression as he made a hand seal, conjuring up his True Extreme Film to protect him.

As soon as the film took shape, a wave of scorching heat instantly surged over him, causing the True Extreme Film to crackle and flash incessantly.

However, Han Li remained as still as an immovable mountain within the formidable shockwaves, and his gaze remained focused intently on the altar in an unblinking fashion.

The shockwaves were so powerful that all of the greenery on the mountain summit down below was reduced to powder, and a thick layer of earth was also scraped up from the ground, producing an extremely flat area.

The daoist temple was also swept up in the shockwaves, and the restrictions around it had already been broken by Xiong Shan, so it wasn't going to take long before the temple was also razed to the ground.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing summoned her azure feather fan before waving it vigorously through the air, releasing a gust of fierce azure wind that formed an azure tornado to encompass the entire daoist temple.

After traveling over such a long distance, the power of the shockwaves was already significantly diminished, but the azure tornado was still trembling incessantly.

Lu Yuqing's face paled slightly as she bit through the tip of her tongue, then expelled a mouthful of blood onto the azure feather fan in her hand.

The fan immediately began to radiate bright spiritual light, and all of its feathers spread open like the train of a peacock before detaching themselves from the handle of the fan and vanishing into the azure tornado in a flash.

The tornado instantly swelled drastically in size while radiating bright azure light, and it became far more stable than before.

The shockwaves quickly subsided, but the entire mountain continued to sway violently as countless rocks of different sizes came tumbling down in a catastrophic avalanche.

Moments later, the azure tornado around the daoist temple faded, and the temple remained completely unscathed.

Lu Yuqing was panting slightly, but her expression was quite calm, and she quickly swallowed a pill before looking up into the sky.

At this point, the sea of fire and cascade of lightning up above had already disappeared, and all that remained in the sky was the white altar.

Above the altar was a radiant ball of azure light that was several hundred feet in size, and it resembled an azure sun.

An ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he unconsciously took a step forward.

Right at this moment, the azure sun exploded violently, sending rays of blinding azure light erupting in all directions.

Every single ray of azure light was a peerlessly sharp streak of sword qi that howled through the air, and the white altar was instantly punched full of holes before shattering into countless pieces.

The surrounding eight pillars suffered the same fate, reduced to countless pieces of scrap metal.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he flew back in retreat while sweeping a sleeve through the air, and his Heavy Water True Axis instantly emerged before him, then released a thick heavy water barrier to shield him.

He was retreating very quickly, but he was still unable to outrun these rapid streaks of sword qi, and he was only able to get a small distance away before the streaks of sword qi struck his Heavy Water True Axis.

The axis instantly began to tremble violently as a string of metallic clangs rang out in rapid succession, and the black water barrier that it had released was quickly being worn down.

A rumbling thunderclap erupted out of Han Li's body as he accelerated drastically in his retreat, flying back to several dozen kilometers away in the blink of an eye.

As for the azure sword qi, all of it abruptly dissipated after reaching a certain distance away from the altar, much to Han Li's relief.

After waiting for a moment to ensure that there would be no more sword qi coming after him, he swept a sleeve through the air to stow his Heavy Water True Axis away.

Meanwhile, the azure sun in the distance flashed a few times, and the azure light that it was radiating rapidly dimmed before fading away altogether, revealing the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hovering in mid-air in a circle.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he flew over to the circle of azure swords.

Following this latest refinement, the outward appearance of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hadn't changed much. They had become more translucent, and bursts of azure energy were just barely visible flowing inside.

Enormous spiritual power fluctuations were emanating out of the flying swords, causing the nearby world's origin qi to shudder and tremble, and a massive spiritual power vortex had taken shape around them.

Upon sensing Han Li's arrival, the 72 flying swords suddenly flew through the air in a blur, transforming into 72 streaks of azure light before vanishing into his dantian in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was quite startled by this, but he could sense that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were merely hovering in his dantian in a still manner.

With the flying swords inside his dantian, he was able to get an even clearer sense of the changes that had taken place within them.

After absorbing such an immeasurable amount of sword essence, it was no exaggeration to say that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been reborn anew.

In their current form, just a single one of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords contained far more spiritual power than any of his other immortal treasures, including even the Heavy Water True Axis that he had painstakingly refined.

However, due to the fact that this spiritual power came from the sword essence of countless different swords, it was a little chaotic and erratic.

This was something that had happened once before after the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had absorbed the sword essence from the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array last time, so Han Li wasn't concerned.

Looking at the 72 swords in his dantian, he locked onto one of them with his spiritual sense before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and only after a few flashes of azure light did the flying sword appear before him.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this. It seemed that the flying swords had become more difficult to control, and they also felt heavier and more cumbersome.

However, this was only to be expected, considering how much more powerful they had become, and it should be possible to resolve these issues following another bout of refinement.

With that in mind, Han Li made a hand seal before pointing a finger forward, and a layer of azure light instantly appeared over the flying sword's surface.

The sword then moved a few times before falling still again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the flying sword in a flash.

The azure light radiating from the flying sword became even brighter, and once again, it moved a little before falling still.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he channeled all of the immortal spiritual power in his body, releasing two bursts of dense azure light out of the palms of his hands, both of which surged into the flying sword.

At the same time, his spiritual sense also flooded into the flying sword, and the azure light radiating from the sword's surface instantly brightened even further.

All of a sudden, the flying sword twisted around before shooting through the air like an azure spirit snake while expanding drastically in size, swelling to over 1,000 feet in length as it radiated blinding azure swordlight.

The entire surrounding space began to tremble in the wake of the tremendous sword intent emanating from the giant sword, and all of the nearby world's origin qi instantly converged toward it.

The light radiating from the huge sword continued to grow brighter and brighter as it pierced back and forth through the clouds like an enormous azure dragon.

The cloud in the sky surged and churned violently before rapidly dissipating to reveal the clear, blue sky up above.

Only then did a hint of relief appear on Han Li's face, and a look of elation surfaced in his eyes at the sight of the giant sword.

The sword had become far more formidable than he anticipated, and it wasn't inferior in the slightest compared with the combined power of the entire set of 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in their previous form.

All of a sudden, he made a hand seal, and arcs of thick and radiant golden lightning instantly emerged over the giant azure sword.

The arcs of lightning were flashing over the blade of the sword like a flight of prowling dragons, giving off a violent and primordial aura.

In the blink of an eye, the giant azure sword had transformed into a golden lightning sword and was giving off a devastating aura of destruction.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this.

The comparison between these arcs of golden lightning and his Divine Devilbane Lightning from before was no different from that between night and day. Not only had the lightning become at least several times more powerful, there also seemed to be some type of new, unidentifiable property about them.

Han Li hesitated momentarily before making another hand seal, and the giant lightning sword in the sky instantly stopped in its tracks before becoming even brighter.

Immediately thereafter, it swept through the air as if it were being swung by an enormous invisible hand.

A streak of gargantuan azure sword qi swept forth, and it was several kilometers wide with arcs of golden lightning surging over its surface, presenting an astonishing sight to behold.

The azure sword qi erupted in all directions, tearing through the very space itself to create countless black spatial rifts while also causing the surrounding space to warp and tremble violently.

The streak of giant sword qi vanished into space in the blink of an eye, but the disturbance continued to rage on, and the entire secret area was beginning to tremble and sway.

Only after a long time had passed were peace and quiet restored.

Chapter 442: Collapse

There were some mixed emotions in Han Li's eyes as he looked on in silence.

After unleashing that slash, all of the golden lightning around the giant sword dissipated as if it had exhausted all of its power.

That power of that slash was approaching the level of an all-out attack unleashed by Han Li's Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword in the past, and this was only the power of a single sword, so it was difficult to imagine just how powerful all 72 swords combined would be.

With that in mind, a surge of excitement welled up in Han Li's heart.

However, the problem was that it was taking virtually all of his immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense to control this single flying sword, rendering him unable to do much else.

With that in mind, much of Han Li's enthusiasm was instantly dampened.

A thought then suddenly sprang into his mind, and he raised an eyebrow as he thought back to how the flying swords had just flown into his dantian on their own.

Perhaps the situation wasn't what he imagined it to be.

With that in mind, Han Li enveloped the 71 flying swords in his dantian with his spiritual sense before attempting to draw upon them, but the only response that he received was a faint flash of azure light.

He then channeled all of his immortal spiritual power before attempting the same thing, but all of the flying swords remained completely still and unmoved.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh upon seeing this.

In their current form, the flying swords in his dantian had become incredibly heavy, and attempting to move them with his current level of immortal spiritual power was no different from an ant attempting to move a mountain.

Thankfully, his spiritual connection with the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords still remained, so he should be able to use them once he attained sufficient power.

After heaving another faint sigh, he made no further attempt to summon all of the remaining flying swords at once, instead focusing his spiritual sense on summoning just a single additional sword.

A second azure flying sword emerged in front of him at his behest, and Han Li took a deep breath before channeling all of his immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense before making a hand seal.

Bright azure light flashed over the surface of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword a few times, but it remained completely still.

Meanwhile, Han Li was feeling a little dizzy from overexertion of immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense, and he hurriedly stopped what he was doing.

After that, he stowed the flying sword away as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

It seemed that at his current level of power, controlling a single Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword was already his limit.

The giant azure sword slowly flew through the air, and even though all of the formidable arcs of golden lightning on its surface had already faded, it was still giving off mountainous pressure.

Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the giant azure sword flew down while rapidly shrinking before vanishing up his sleeve as a miniature azure sword, following which he drifted back down onto the ground, where he was greeted by Lu Yuqing.

"Congratulations, Brother Han. I can see that your flying swords have become far more formidable," Lu Yuqing congratulated with a beaming smile.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he asked, "The fact that you're here must mean that all of the puppets from before have been taken care of, right?"

Lu Yuqing nodded in response.

At this point, the phenomena in the sky had completely faded, and the entire secret area was restored to its original state, while the clouds that had been scattered by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword were also slowly recovering.

"It doesn't look like there are any other treasures in here, and we've already been here for a very long time. The entrance of this secret area is quite difficult to access, but there's no guarantee that Xue Han and the others won't be able to follow us into this place, so it's best for us to leave as quickly as possible," Han Li said.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this, and a slightly hesitant look appeared on her face.

"Is there something else that you have to do here?" Han Li asked upon noticing her expression.

"No. You're right, Brother Han, it's best for us to leave this place as quickly as possible, but before that, please wait for me for a moment," Lu Yuqing said, then flew toward the ancestral hall of the daoist temple in the distance, where she swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that swept up all of the memorial tablets inside before stowing them away.

After that, she flew back to Han Li's side and said, "I'm ready to go."

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, but he didn't ask any questions, and he began to fly down the mountain, followed closely by Lu Yuqing.

Perhaps it was due to the destruction of the white altar in the sky or the disappearance of all of the flying swords on the meadow. In any case, the boundless sword qi in the air had completely faded, allowing them to fly without any obstruction.

The two of them had only just risen up into the air when a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out, following which the entire secret area began to tremble violently.

"What's going on?"

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly as he stopped in his tracks.

All of a sudden, a pillar of white light had erupted into the heavens in the distance behind him.

The pillar of white light was incredibly thick, with a diameter of at least several hundred feet, and it was giving off tremendous spiritual power fluctuations that were quite alarming even to Han Li.

Lu Yuqing was also staring at the pillar of white light in the distance with an astonished look on her face, and right at this moment, another rumbling boom rang out in another direction as the entire secret area shuddered violently once again.

A second pillar of white light had appeared there, and it was also extending directly up into the sky.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing were even more alarmed upon seeing this.

The two pillars of light seemed to be resonating with one another, and the trembling of the entire secret area was becoming more and more violent, presenting a doomsday-like scene to behold.

"This secret area is about to collapse! We have to get out of here!" Han Li exclaimed in an urgent voice as he flew down the mountain as a streak of azure light, and Lu Yuqing hurriedly followed along.

As he was flying down the mountain, Han Li's mind was racing as he tried to pinpoint a reason for the collapse of the secret area.

Could it be that the destruction of the white altar had triggered the secret area's demise, or could it be that the sword strike that he had just unleashed had damaged some important point in the secret area?

However, he then quickly shook his head to rid himself of that thought. There was no point in pondering this matter, and his top priority now was to get out of this place as quickly as possible.

With that in mind, he accelerated even further, and the two of them arrived at the foot of the mountain in the blink of an eye, returning to the place where they had first entered the secret area.

Meanwhile, a third pillar of white light had risen up elsewhere in the secret area, and the tremors running through the entire secret area had become even more severe.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense through the nearby area, upon which his expression instantly darkened slightly.

The space here was extremely stable with no spatial passageways or teleportation arrays to facilitate their escape.

He had always thought that this place served as both the entrance and the exit of the secret area, but it seemed that he was incorrect in that assumption.

Lu Yuqing had sensed the exact same thing, and a grim look had appeared on her face as well.

"Fellow Daoist Lu, I noticed that you've been exploring this secret area over the course of the past three days. Have you discovered any exits or any abnormal places?" Han Li asked as he turned to Lu Yuqing.

"I'm afraid not. The entire secret area seems to have already been ransacked by Xiong Shan, and all I stumbled upon were some damaged buildings and destroyed restrictions," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li cast his gaze forward once again upon hearing this.

At his current level of power, it was not very feasible for him to forcibly tear open a spatial passageway.

After all, the space in the Immortal Realm was far more stable than that of lower realms like the Spirit Domain Realm.

Furthermore, even if he could tear open the space here, there was no guarantee that the resulting spatial passageway would lead to anywhere safe, and there was a very good chance that he would be swept up by the boundless spatial currents and killed.

Right at this moment, a fourth pillar of white light emerged in the secret area with another resounding boom, and the entire secret area was swaying extremely violently at this point.

A string of loud cracks rang out overhead as a series of white rifts appeared up above, and they quickly spread in all directions like cracks on the surface of a mirror.

Lu Yuqing's face instantly turned deathly pale upon seeing this.

"There's no time to waste, let's split up and try to search for an exit," Han Li said in an urgent voice, then immediately flew away in a certain direction.

Lu Yuqing nodded in response before flying away in another direction, but she had only flown a short distance away when she suddenly stopped in her tracks, and a slightly befuddled look appeared on her face as she cast her gaze toward a spot halfway up the mountain.

After a brief moment of hesitation, she flew in that direction as a streak of azure light.

Meanwhile, Han Li was flying back up toward the mountain summit while scouring his surroundings with all his might using his spiritual sense and his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, as well as his Eye of Truth.

At his speed, he was quickly able to scour the majority of the entire mountain, and right at this moment, he suddenly stopped cold in his tracks.

All of the greenery further up the mountain had already been completely uprooted to reveal the bare mountain face, and he could see that there was nothing up there.

No additional pillars of white light had appeared after the fourth one, but the spatial rifts in the sky were rapidly spreading and expanding.

The tremors running through the entire secret area were becoming more and more violent, and an agitated look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he hurriedly flew away in another direction.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Brother Han, come to me! Hurry!"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then cast his gaze in a certain direction before flying away as a streak of azure light.

At this moment, Lu Yuqing was standing somewhere halfway up the mountain, scrutinizing a section of the mountain face with black light shimmering in her eyes.

Han Li arrived by her side amid a flash of azure light, then cast his gaze toward the same spot with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but failed to discover anything.

"Have you found something, Fellow Daoist Lu?"

He summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis as he spoke, then began to observe the mountain face through his Eye of Truth, upon which an elated look instantly appeared on his face.

He flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of azure sword qi that struck the mountain face, and the streak of sword qi instantly vanished in a flash, while the mountain face rippled slightly before returning to its original state.

Chapter 443: Now or Never

"There really is a restriction here! Looks like your spirit eyes are sharper than mine," Han Li said as his eyes lit up.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this, then forced a smile onto her own face as she replied, "Not at all, I was simply lucky to have stumbled upon this place. I wonder what's behind the restriction."

Han Li noticed that Lu Yuqing's expression was a little unnatural, but there was no time for him to ponder such matters as he replied, "There's only one way to find out."

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a giant azure sword that was radiating dazzling azure swordlight.

Arcs of thick golden lightning sprang forth from the surface of the giant sword, instantly transforming it into a golden lightning sword that was giving off a terrifying destructive aura.

Han Li made a hand seal, and the golden lightning sword crashed heavily into the mountain face with tremendous force.

The restriction on the mountain face immediately began to radiate dazzling white light, forming a thick white light barrier to protect itself, and balls of white spiritual light were dancing around within it like living creatures to oppose the giant sword.

The white light barrier appeared quite profound, but it was torn apart with ease by the golden lightning sword, dissipating into countless specks of white spiritual light to reveal a small valley.

A large azure hall was situated within the valley, and above the entrance of the hall was a plaque that read "Flying Immortal Pavilion".

The gate of the hall was slightly ajar with several dim specks of white light visible through it, interspersed with faint spatial fluctuations.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing were both ecstatic to detect these spatial fluctuations, and they immediately flew through the entrance of the hall to arrive inside.

Despite its large size, the interior of the hall was actually very empty, with only a stone platform inside that was around three feet tall and over 100 feet in diameter.

On the stone platform was a white array that was giving off faint white light, and Han Li immediately flew onto the platform in a flash, then quickly inspected the white array momentarily before giving a contemplative nod.

This was indeed a teleportation array, and it was most likely the exit of this secret area.

There was an Immortal Origin Stones embedded into each of the nodes on the array, amounting to a total of over 200 Immortal Origin Stones.

However, only a small proportion of these Immortal Origin Stones still had immortal spiritual power left within them, while the rest had already become completely transparent.

Right at this moment, a string of resounding booms rang out overhead, and the four pillars of white light dissipated in a flash.

The entire secret area was finally beginning to truly collapse, and a spatial rift had just extended over the mountain.

The mountain summit exploded violently, sending countless giant rocks tumbling down from above, and the valley was also at risk of being crushed under the avalanche.

"Hurry!" Han Li yelled as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the Seven Bright Star Rings shot out in a flash, then connected together with one another to form a larger ring.

Radiant starlight erupted out of the Seven Bright Star Rings, forming a starry light barrier with countless star designs flashing on its surface to oppose the avalanche that was tumbling down from above.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Lu Yuqing immediately sprang into action, plucking out all of the spent Immortal Origin Stones before replacing them with new ones.

With a set of new Immortal Origin Stones installed, the white light radiating from the teleportation array instantly became several times brighter.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he was just about to step into the array when his brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward a corner of the array.

At this moment, the entire array was radiating resplendent white light with the exception of that corner, and the flow of immortal spiritual power through that area was also rather labored.

Lu Yuqing had also noticed this, and an anxious look appeared on her face as she asked, "Is the teleportation array damaged?"

Han Li offered no response as he cast a series of incantation seals into the dim corner of the array, and the corner immediately lit up slightly, but then turned dark once again.

Han Li hurriedly stopped what he was doing upon seeing this, and he said, "It looks like the teleportation array is about to lose its effectiveness due to prolonged lack of maintenance."

"What do we do then, Brother Han? Do you have a way to repair it?" Lu Yuqing asked in an urgent voice.

At this point, the tremors running through the entire secret area were becoming more and more violent, and a series of giant cracks had also appeared on the mountain.

"This array is too complex for me to repair, and even if I could, we don't have enough time. Having said that, there's no need to be concerned. The array is still just barely functional, and it should be able to work one more time," Han Li replied, then immediately stepped into the array.

Lu Yuqing's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and she immediately stepped into the array as well.

Han Li chanted an incantation before casting an incantation seal, and the teleportation array instantly lit up with radiant white light that erupted straight into the heavens.

Meanwhile, Xue Han and the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators had only just emerged at the entrance of the secret area at the foot of the mountain amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

There was an enraged look on Xue Han's face, and he seemed to be in the process of scolding the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators. "You're all a bunch of useless fools! You can't do anything without me! How has it taken you three whole days just to find an entrance..."

Before he had a chance to finish, his voice abruptly cut off at the sight of the collapsing secret area before him, and everyone else was also instantly rooted to the spot.

"Get back! This space is about to collapse!" Xue Han roared as he immediately turned back the same way he had come from.

However, the spatial fluctuations at the entrance had already subsided, and the space was completely stable, meaning that there was no way back.

A layer of cold sweat instantly appeared on Xue Han's forehead.

He was well aware of just how terrifying a collapsing space could be, and even he wouldn't be able to survive such a disaster.

"Look over there, Master Xue Han!" Layman Bone Flame yelled as he pointed at a burst of dazzling white light that had appeared halfway up the mountain.

Xue Han immediately released his spiritual sense in that direction seeing this, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he yelled, "It's them! They're trying to leave using the teleportation array!"

He then immediately set off in that direction as a streak of black light, and everyone else hurriedly followed along.

Inside the hall, the teleportation array was glowing brighter and brighter, but Han Li didn't dare to speed up the process too much for fear of exacerbating the existing damage in the array.

As time passed, the entire array glowed brighter and brighter, with the exception of the one damaged corner, which was only dimming with each passing second.

Droplets of cold sweat were beginning to bead up on Han Li's forehead, and Lu Yuqing was also staring intently at that corner of the array with a tense expression.

All of a sudden, she turned toward the foot of the mountain with an alarmed expression, where several streaks of light were rapidly approaching.

"Brother Han, Xue Han and the others are here!" she immediately yelled in an urgent voice.

Han Li's attention was entirely focused on the array, so he wasn't keeping tabs on what was happening around him, and he immediately raised his head upon hearing this.

At this point, the streak of black light that contained Xue Han had already arrived outside the hall, and it was rapidly approaching.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly made a hand seal, upon which the starlight barrier above the valley abruptly disappeared.

The Seven Bright Star Rings emerged out of thin air, then vanished from the spot in the blink of an eye, and in the next instant, they reappeared in front of the hall before flying into the streak of black light formed by Xue Han.

A furious roar rang out as Xue Han was stopped cold in his tracks, and a ring had appeared around each of his four limbs, his chest, his lower abdomen, and his neck, digging deep into his skin.

"What the hell is this!" he roared in a furious voice as he struggled with all his might, while black light surged over his body.

The black light quickly spread over the Seven Bright Star Rings like ink, overpowering the starlight radiating from them, but they remained resolute around Xue Han's body.

Meanwhile, Han Li opened his mouth to release a ball of azure light into the array, and the white light radiating from the array brightened even further, seemingly having reached a certain threshold.

Bursts of spatial power surged out of the array to envelop Han Li and Lu Yuqing, and in the next instant, both of them vanished into thin air.

At the same time, the damaged corner of the teleportation array also reached its limits, and a series of cracks appeared over its surface.

The white light radiating from the array flashed one final time before fading away as well, and Xue Han was still immobilized outside the hall.

At this moment, there was radiant black light erupting out of his body, and the Seven Bright Star Rings were finally unable to hold on any longer, shattering into countless pieces that flew away in all directions.

Xue Han immediately stormed into the hall, and an extremely grim look appeared on his face at the sight of the damaged teleportation array.

At this point, Layman Bone Flame and the others also arrived on the scene, and their hearts immediately sank at the sight that they were greeted by.

Right at this moment, the secret area finally completely collapsed, and powerful bursts of spatial turbulence erupted out of the spatial rifts.

The entire mountain collapsed violently, sending countless giant rocks crashing down to inundate the small valley.

……

In a certain dim space, there was a boundless black desert down below, and the ground was riddled with black rocks of different sizes. Vegetation was extremely sparse here, and the entire area looked extremely bleak and desolate.

The sky was a dark yellow color, and all of a sudden, a rumbling thunderclap rang out.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of black light emerged before forming a ball of black light that was several dozen feet in size, and arcs of black light were flashing incessantly over its surface.

The ball of black light warped and twisted before suddenly elongating to form a spatial rift that was several dozen feet in length, and a pair of figures, one male and one female, stumbled out from within.

The two were none other than Han Li and Lu Yuqing, who had arrived here through the teleportation array, and at this moment, both of them were looking rather worse for wear. In particular, Lu Yuqing was as pale as a sheet, and there was a thin trail of blood running down from the corner of her lips.

Chapter 444: Completely Empty

After steadying themselves, both Han Li and Lu Yuqing heaved a collective sigh of relief.

The teleportation array seemed to have transported them out of the secret area earlier, but it had actually suddenly collapsed at a crucial juncture, casting them into an area of spatial turbulence, and it had taken them a great deal of effort to escape.

The spatial rift flashed a few times before abruptly vanishing, and Han Li inspected his surroundings briefly while releasing his spiritual sense throughout the nearby area.

Lu Yuqing's expression eased slightly at the sight of the surrounding environment, and she quickly swallowed a pill, upon which her complexion immediately began to improve.

"Where are we right now? Have we been teleported out of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor?" she asked in a slightly uneasy manner.

Even a slight deviation in a teleportation array could result in a vast difference in the destination, and the fact that they had been cast into a spatial storm certainly wasn't going to help the matter.

"I don't think so. I can still detect the profound glacial qi that's unique to the Light Frost Region here, so we should still be in the immortal manor," Han Li replied.

"Good," Lu Yuqing said with a relieved expression.

"That teleportation array has already been destroyed, so Xue Han and the others will most likely fall to their demise along with that secret area. We should be able to take some time to rest and recuperate here," Han Li continued.

Lu Yuqing had sustained some rather severe injuries, and even though he was uninjured, he had virtually used up all of his immortal spiritual power in the process of escaping from the spatial turbulence.

This place appeared to be quite bleak and desolate, but at the very least, it seemed to be safe.

Lu Yuqing was in desperate need of some rest, and she immediately nodded in agreement.

Hence, the two of them descended onto the desert, then set up a few restrictions around themselves before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Han Li summoned a pair of Immortal Origin Stones to help himself replenish his immortal spiritual power, and close to a day later, he had made a full recovery.

After withstanding a string of ordeals in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, his cultivation base had advanced a little further, but that final immortal acupoint still showed no sign of budging.

A resigned look appeared on his face as diverted his attention away from the stubborn immortal acupoint, then turned to the side to find that Lu Yuqing was still meditating with a spherical azure light barrier around her.

Han Li withdrew his gaze, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon a gray stone slab, the very same one that contained the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts.

He had been too busy earlier to take a close look at the cultivation art, and he was eager to take advantage of this window of respite.

Blue light flashed within his eyes as he inspected the stone slab closely, and around two hours later, the blue light in his eyes faded as he withdrew his gaze.

He had already completely memorized the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts, and just like the first half of the cultivation, the second half also laid out the method required to open 18 profound acupoints.

He was confident that if he could master the second half of the cultivation art and open this second set of 18 profound acupoints, then he would be able to break through his final immortal acupoint with no issues.

Just like the first half, the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts also involved guiding starpower into the body to open up profound acupoints.

However, the second half of the cultivation art was far more complex than the first half, and not only was an enormous amount of starpower required to open the second set of 18 profound acupoints, a considerably long time had to be spent on bodily refinement as well, making the process far more rigorous than what had been laid out in the first half of the cultivation art.

He wanted nothing more than to drop everything and immediately find a place to go into seclusion, but this was clearly not a suitable place for seclusion. On top of that, he still had to help Daoist Hu Yan secure whatever treasure he was searching for in the limited time left so that he could obtain the second part of the Mantra Treasured Axis, so he would have to save the Great Universe Origin Arts for later.

With that in mind, stowed the gray stone slab away again, then cast his gaze forward with a contemplative look in his eyes.

He didn't know where Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were at this moment, and he also had no idea what the treasure Daoist Hu Yan had been referring to was.

The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor was far more complex a place than he had imagined. It was an enormous place that rivaled a small continent, and he had no idea where to find Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, and right as he was about to close his eyes, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as if a thought had occurred to him.

He then raised a hand, and Xiong Shan's storage bracelet appeared in his grasp.

He still hadn't had a chance to examine the storage bracelet yet. Considering he had been quite a formidable swordsman with unknown ties to the Boundless Sword Sect, surely his storage bracelet had to have been a precious treasure trove.

With that in mind, Han Li was feeling a little excited, but his smile instantly stiffened as soon as he injected his spiritual sense into the storage bracelet.

To his surprise, Xiong Shan's storage bracelet was completely empty!

That wasn't entirely the truth as there were some items piled up in a corner of the storage bracelet's internal space, but none of those things were very valuable.

The only things that were even slightly appealing to Han Li were several vials of recovery pills and a few scriptures, and there were barely even any Immortal Origin Stones.

Han Li was initially quite perplexed to see this, but he quickly came to understand why this was the case.

Xiong Shan had already exhausted all of his resources for the sake of his previous sword refinement attempt, and only several centuries had passed since then, so it was only to be expected that he had to empty his pockets again for this second sword refinement.

Furthermore, as soon as he entered the Light Frost Palace, he had immediately traveled straight to the Boundless Sword Sect, so he didn't have any time to collect any treasures along the way, and that was why his storage bracelet was so barren and desolate.

Han Li was slightly disappointed to see this, but he then quickly reminded himself that he had already reaped many rewards in the Light Frost Palace, and asking for any more would only be a sign of excessive greed, which was certainly not a good thing.

With that in mind, the disappointment in his heart quickly faded away, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release all of the storage bracelet's contents, then briefly sorted through them splitting them up into different categories before stowing them away.

Before long, all that remained in front of him was a silver jade box, within which were three jade slips.

He was quite interested in the cultivation arts that Xiong Shan had been using prior to his death, and he picked up one of the three jade slips before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

This jade slip contained a cultivation art by the name of the Great Destruction Yang Sword Arts. The cultivation art could support one's cultivation to the Golden Immortal Stage, and it had most likely been Xiong Shan's primary cultivation art.

According to the description of the Great Destruction Yang Sword Arts, the cultivation art granted one mastery over the laws of metal, and it was rather similar in nature to the laws of destruction.

Han Li hadn't dabbled in metal-attribute cultivation arts in the past, and he had no intention of beginning now, so this cultivation art wasn't very useful to him.

However, there were some sword-related secret techniques and insights recorded at the very end of the cultivation art that could be useful for reference purposes.

He read through the entire cultivation art from beginning to end, then placed it back into the jade box before picking out another jade slip and injecting his spiritual sense into it.

This jade slip contained a body refinement cultivation art by the name of the Golden Arhat Arts, and it appeared to be the secret technique that Xiong Shan had unleashed while climbing the stairs outside of the Light Frost Palace.

This was quite a remarkable body refinement art that granted one tremendous physical prowess, but a mastery over the laws of metal were required to cultivate it.

Han Li immediately lost interest in the cultivation art upon seeing this prerequisite, and he only briefly read through its contents before setting it down again and picking up the final jade slip.

This jade slip contained some pill recipes, most of which were for earthy metal-attribute pills, which would be quite helpful for True Immortals using metal-attribute cultivation arts.

Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip as a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes.

None of the jade slips had contained any records of the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array. Could it be that Xiong Shan had destroyed those records?

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he pondered this matter, and he was just about to stow the jade box away when he suddenly seemed to have noticed something.

He fiddled with the jade box briefly, and it suddenly split apart down the middle with a faint crack. As it turned out, there was a hidden compartment with what appeared to be a piece of gray cloth inside.

What's this?

Han Li picked up the gray cloth to find that it was roughly square in shape, and it resembled a dirty rag, but upon closer inspection, he noticed some faint patterns on the cloth.

These patterns were very strange in appearance, and even with Han Li's vast wealth of knowledge and experience, he was at a complete loss as to what they were.

However, there was something profound about these patterns that convinced him that they definitely weren't just haphazard designs casually drawn onto a cloth.

The gray cloth was very smooth and slightly cool to the touch, and it was unclear what type of material it had been fashioned out of.

Han Li inspected the cloth back and forth for a long while, even using his Brightsight Spirit Eyes and Eye of Truth in the process, but was unable to find anything worthy of note.

The gray cloth wasn't giving off any spiritual power fluctuations, and if it weren't for those profound patterns, it would've appeared no different from a normal rag.

However, the fact that Xiong Shan had stored it away so carefully clearly indicated that it was no ordinary object.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he absentmindedly rubbed the cloth between his fingers, upon which a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

With his physical strength, that casual rubbing motion would've been enough to tear a steel slab apart, yet the gray cloth remained completely unscathed.

Han Li grabbed onto the cloth with both hands and attempted to pull it apart, but it refused to budge.

He raised an eyebrow as he exerted even more force through his hands, but the gray cloth was able to easily hold itself together.

An intrigued look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he switched tactics, attempting to tear the cloth apart down the middle this time, but still to no avail.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

He had exerted sufficient force to tear apart even an ordinary spirit treasure just now, yet this gray cloth remained completely unscathed, so there had to be something special about it.

Chapter 445: Boundless Sand Sea

Han Li wanted to test the limits of the gray cloth's resilience, and he continued to exert more and more force until he was going all-out, but he was still unable to tear the cloth apart.

A curious look appeared on his face as he began to inspect the gray cloth again.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a ball of crimson flames that enveloped the entire cloth, subjecting it to scorching heat, but it remained completely unscathed.

With a wave of his sleeve, Han Li snuffed out the flame, then released a ball of heavy water to envelop the gray cloth, and once again, it was completely unaffected.

Around an hour later, Han Li was staring at the gray cloth in his hand with a defeated expression.

During the past hour, he had tried everything that he could think of to get any type of reaction out of the gray cloth, but his attempts had ended in complete failure.

After staring at the gray cloth for a while longer, Han Li stowed it away with a resigned smile, deciding that he would look into it another time.

Right at this moment, the spherical azure light barrier around Lu Yuqing flashed a few times before fading away, and as she opened her eyes, her complexion was looking much better.

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Brother Han," she said as she rose to her feet.

"It's fine. Take a look and see if you can identify roughly where we are right now," Han Li said as he gestured at their surroundings.

"According to my knowledge, the Light Frost Region is a very complex place, and there's more than one desert of this description in the region, so I can't tell where we are based only on what I can see right now," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

"In that case, let's do some exploring. This place looks quite barren and desolate, but we shouldn't underestimate it," Han Li said as he summoned his azure flying boat before stepping onto it.

Lu Yuqing naturally raised no objections and descended onto the flying boat as well.

Immediately thereafter, the flying boat sped away in a certain direction at Han Li's behest.

Just like the ice field from before, there was a type of invisible force in this area that severely restricted one's spiritual sense, and even Han Li's spiritual sensory range had been reduced to only several hundred kilometers in radius, so he decided to proceed at a moderate speed as a safety precaution.

Moments later, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he turned in a certain direction, and the azure flying boat also faltered slightly.

"Have you found something, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"I have, but it's not worth very much. So be it, let's go and take a look," Han Li said as the flying boat diverged slightly from its original path, quickly covering a distance of close to 200 kilometers to the left.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing then drifted down onto the ground from the flying boat.

A large patch of dark purple mushrooms were growing over the ground down below, and every single mushroom was around 10 feet tall. The mushrooms were covered in dark purple spots, while their edges were a bright red color, giving them an extremely vibrant appearance.

This cluster of mushrooms took up an area of around an acre, and they resembled a vibrant sea of flowers growing on this barren desert, seemingly completely out of place.

"These are Mull Cloud Mushrooms!" Lu Yuqing exclaimed as her eyes lit up.

"Could it be that you've managed to ascertain our current location thanks to these mushrooms?" Han Li asked.

He had seen some records pertaining to Mull Cloud Mushrooms before, and he knew that they were extremely poisonous and could be used to refine certain poisons or poison-attribute treasures. However, their poison was only effective against cultivators below the True Immortal stage, while those who had attained immortal bodies were impervious to its effects.

"That's right," Lu Yuqing replied with an excited expression.

She flipped a hand over to produce a green jade pendant as she spoke, then cast a streak of azure light into it, and a burst of green light surged out of the pendant, projecting a green light screen.

The light screen was a map that was comprised of around a dozen components of different colors, and it appeared to be only half of a full map.

"Is this the map of the Light Frost Region that you mentioned previously?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. According to the information that our Black Wind Island was able to gather, the Light Frost Region consists of close to 100 different environments. Unfortunately, this map only contains around a dozen of those areas," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, and his gaze began to roam over the map.

The map was extremely detailed and life-like, presenting many details that would've been absent in the average map.

However, it didn't contain the ice field, the black mountain range, and the black sea that they had passed through previously.

"None of the three areas that we passed through prior to this were on my map. Otherwise, we wouldn't have been so lost," Lu Yuqing said.

"So where are we right now?" Han Li asked.

Only now was he beginning to develop a rough idea of the Light Frost Region's layout.

"We're here. This place is called the Black Rock Desert, and according to my sources, there are three or four deserts in the Light Frost Region, but this is the only one where Mull Cloud Mushrooms can be found," Lu Yuqing replied as she pionted at a black area on the upper part of the map.

"It's good that we've finally managed to ascertain our location. Stumbling around in the Immortal Palace without any idea of where we are is far too dangerous," Han Li said.

"The Black Rock Desert is actually one of the safer areas on my map. There are no frost beasts here, nor any large-scale hazards like glacial storms," Lu Yuqing said.

"We're quite lucky not to have been teleported to a more dangerous area," Han Li said in an ambiguous fashion.

"Indeed, we're extremely lucky, Brother Han," Lu Yuqing replied with a meaningful smile.

"Oh? Is there something I'm missing, Fellow Daoist Lu?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Do you see this place here, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked as she pointed at the upper region of the Black Rock Desert.

"Is there something special about that area?" Han Li asked.

"That place is called the Boundless Sand Sea, and it's the northernmost point of the Light Frost Region," Lu Yuqing replied.

"So what? Are there some precious treasures in this Boundless Sand Sea?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know about that, but as you're already aware, there are other unexplored regions in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor aside from the Light Frost Region, and it's said that the one must go through the Boundless Sand Sea to access those other regions," Lu Yuqing replied.

"Really?"

Han Li was very intrigued to hear this.

"Of course! The Light Frost Region has already been mostly explored by cultivators who had previously entered the immortal manor, and I've been meaning to go to the other regions to see what I can find there, but I haven't been able to find the Boundless Sand Sea. Who could've predicted that we would end up so close to the Boundless Sand Sea after that mishap?" Lu Yuqing said with an excited expression.

"In that case, we really are extremely fortunate. Time is of the essence, so let's set off right away," Han Li said as he returned to his azure flying boat.

The Light Frost Region had already been scoured countless times, yet even so, he was still able to reap many significant rewards. If he were to go to an unexplored region of the immortal manor, who knew what would be waiting for him there?

Lu Yuqing stowed her azure jade pendant away before also flying back onto the azure spirit boat, following which the flying boat sped away into the distance at Han Li's behest.

Three days later.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing appeared in front of a vast yellow desert.

The sand in the desert was a light yellow color and rather translucent in appearance, reflecting the light of the sun in a blinding fashion.

At the same time, waves of heat were surging through the air, and it was as if this entire place were a massive lit furnace.

"This is the place, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right, this is the Boundless Sand Sea," Lu Yuqing replied with excitement shimmering in her eyes.

Instead of immediately venturing into the area, Han Li asked, "This doesn't look like a very safe place. Do you know if there are any hazards present here?"

"You have a very sharp eye, Brother Han. There are indeed quite a few hazards in this area. For example, this desert is filled with fire poison, and anyone who sets foot into it will slowly be poisoned. Even Golden Immortals will be affected given enough time," Lu Yuqing replied.

"Fire poison? I'm assuming this is no ordinary fire poison," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Indeed. The poison can't be treated with any ordinary pills, and the only cure is to find a water spirit area in the desert and use the special water spiritual qi there to gradually neutralize the fire poison. If one is unable to find a water spirit area and has become too severely poisoned, then even a Golden Immortal could die in this desert," Lu Yuqing said with a serious expression.

"What other hazards are there?" Han Li asked.

"Aside from the fire poison, it's said that one could fall prey to extremely confounding mirages in the desert that could make one lose their way and become trapped in the desert forever. This desert is extremely notorious for these two hazards, and very few people who enter the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor set foot in this place," Lu Yuqing replied.

"This does sound like an extremely perilous place. You're saying that there's a pathway to another region somewhere in this desert?" Han Li asked.

"The pathway is deep within the Boundless Sand Sea, but there's no need to be concerned, Brother Han. I have a map of the Boundless Sand Sea, so as long we proceed with caution and follow the map, we should be able to find the pathway just fine," Lu Yuqing replied as she summoned a jade slip before offering it to Han Li.

Chapter 446: Tribulation of Life and Death

Han Li accepted the jade slip from Lu Yuqing before pressing it against his own forehead, and a short while later, he withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip before handing it back to Lu Yuqing as he remarked, "This is quite a detailed map. May I ask where you got it from? Was it from that stone plaque?"

"That's right. It's exactly because I have this map that I wanted to come to the Boundless Sand Sea, but even with this map in my possession, I'll be counting on you to get us through the Boundless Sand Sea, Brother Han," Lu Yuqing replied.

"I'll do my best," Han Li said in an ambiguous fashion, following which the azure flying boat beneath his feet flew into the desert at his behest.

Upon entering the Boundless Sand Sea, the two of them instantly felt the air temperature rise dramatically, making them feel as if they had entered a steamer.

"Let's try and determine our current location before we do anything else, Fellow Daoist Lu," Han Li suggested.

"That's a good idea. I don't know exactly where we are right now, but I should be able to determine our location once we encounter two or three of the places recorded on the map," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

......

At the same time.

There was a certain mountain range in the Immortal Realm that was extremely majestic, filled with steep, breathtaking peaks that resembled swords aimed straight up at the heavens.

Deep within the mountain range was an imposing, antiquated fortress.

The fortress had been constructed in a very unique style that incorporated all types of sword designs into every aspect of its construction, including its roof and all of its walls.

Large swords, small swords, short swords, long swords... Countless swords of all descriptions filled every single corner of the ancient fortress.

The fortress was brightly lit, and there were many people walking or flying back and forth through it.

All of these people were dressed in golden robes with a "Xiong" character embroidered onto the sleeve, and it appeared to be quite a formidable cultivating clan.

Inside a dim secret chamber deep within the fortress was a black stone platform that was around 10 feet in size, upon which laid a young man.

The man's eyes were tightly shut, and he was completely still and lifeless.

On the stone platform around the body were engraved a circle of profound spirit patterns, while a dark azure oil lamp had been placed above the man's head.

However, at this moment, the flame in the lamp was very feeble, and it was constantly flickering, looking as if it could be snuffed out at any moment.

Adhered to the front of the man's chest was a black talisman with a series of profound runes inscribed upon it, and it was giving off a burst of special aura fluctuations.

All of a sudden, the door of the secret chamber creaked open to punctuate the silence, and two figures made their way into the room one after another.

The first figure was an elderly man with a head of white hair, but his face was extremely supple and completely devoid of wrinkles, presenting a rather jarring contrast to behold.

Behind the elderly man was a strange-looking middle-aged man with a dark green complexion and a pair of eyes with tiny black pupils.

The two of them made their way over to the stone platform before turning their attention to the black talisman.

"Today's the day?" the white-haired elderly man suddenly asked.

"It is. My divination tells me that it's today," the green-faced man replied as he pulled out an azure abacus-like object, and the beads on it were occasionally sliding back and forth on their own.

"Shan'er possesses the best aptitude out of everyone of his generation in our clan, but unfortunately, he's had a rough upbringing as he hails from a side branch of our clan, resulting in a very cold and arrogant personality. He's refused to accept any assistance from our clan and insists on forging his own path. Hopefully, following this ordeal, he can set aside all of his stubborn nature and realize what's truly important," the white-haired elderly man sighed.

The green-faced man nodded in response, and he was just about to say something when he suddenly raised an eyebrow and exclaimed, "It's coming!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the black talisman on the young man's chest suddenly ignited on its own, erupting into a ball of black flames.

All of the patterns on the stone platform around the body also began to glow with radiant black light, forming a black halo that encompassed the entire body.

The white-haired elderly man immediately flicked a finger through the air upon seeing this, releasing a streak of black light that vanished into the black flame in front of the body.

The flame instantly reared up, then split up into five parts, immediately following which several streaks of black light flew out of the five balls of fire, then connected together with one another to form a pentagram array.

Fierce gusts of yin wind instantly began to sweep through the secret chamber, and the air temperature plummeted, but the white-haired elderly man and the green-faced man paid no heed to this as they stared intently at the pentagram array.

The space at the center of the array suddenly began to warp, and a black shadow appeared, squirming and writhing as if it were a living creature.

The shadow squirmed around for a while, then abruptly split open to reveal a spatial rift.

In the next instant, a ball of golden light flew out of the spatial rift, then vanished into the young man's body in a flash.

Some time later, the body began to radiate dazzling golden light.

The white-haired elderly man's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light that enveloped the young man's body.

The complexion of the young man's pale and lifeless face quickly reverted back to normal, and his heart also began to beat again as the vitality was restored to his body.

The azure lamp above the young man's head had also suddenly become several times brighter, and its flame had become extremely stable.

Some more time passed, and the young man's eyelids fluttered slightly before slowly peeling back to reveal a pair of dazed and disoriented eyes.

It took a long while for those glazed over eyes to focus, and the young man began to look around in bewilderment, upon which he quickly spotted the two people beside him.

"Uncle, Clan Leader!"

His expression instantly changed drastically as he tried to sit up, only for the white-haired elderly man to press a hand down onto his shoulder as he said, "Lay still, Shan'er. The soul transference technique has only just been completed, so you can't move yet."

The young man opened his mouth to say something, but ultimately remained silent and laid back down.

"What's going on, Clan Leader? I should already be dead by now, why have I returned to the clan?" the young man asked.

"You have your uncle here to thank. A long time ago, he gleaned through divination that you were going to face a tribulation of life and death at some point, but he couldn't determine when this tribulation was going to befall you.

“Hence, when you decided to leave the clan, he secretly planted a soul transference secret technique onto your nascent soul, which ensured that if your nascent soul were to ever sustain lethal damage, it would automatically be teleported back to our clan so that you can possess another body," the white-haired elderly man explained.

The young man was silent for a moment, then turned to the green-faced man as he said, "I see. Thank you, Uncle. If it wasn't for you, I would already be dead by now."

"There's no need to thank me. Don't forget that you and I are related by blood," the green-faced man replied with a dismissive wave of his hand.

A complex look flashed through the young man's eyes as he said, "Uncle, every time you use your divination technique, you lose at least 10,000 years of your cultivation base. In order to glean my fate, you had to have lost at least 100,000 years of cultivation base. How can I repay you?"

"A mere 100,000-years-worth of cultivation base is nothing. I'm just glad you're back safe and sound," the green-faced man said with a smile.

The young man lowered his gaze and remained silent.

"What kind of enemy did you encounter in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, Shan'er? There's no way any ordinary cultivator could've struck you down," the white-haired elderly man suddenly asked.

A cold gleam flashed through the young man's eyes upon hearing this, but he refrained from answering the question.

"Forget it. If you don't want to tell me, then I won't pry any further. You can take care of this matter on your own," the white-haired elderly man said with a shake of his head.

"Thank you, Clan Leader," the young man replied with a nod.

"Now that you're back, stay here for now. We'll help you recover your cultivation base as quickly as possible, and the Immortal Palace has already sent us several summons, so you should go and accept your post there. As for everything else, we can discuss all of that some other time," the white-haired elderly man said.

The young man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he was silent for a moment before nodding in response.

The white-haired elderly man and the green-faced man exchanged a glance upon seeing this, and both of them could see their own elation mirrored in one another's eyes.

......

In the sky above a red plain, two balls of radiant light, one red and one golden, were engaged in a ferocious battle.

The two balls of light were clashing violently amid a string of earth-shattering booms, causing the surrounding space to tremble as gusts of fierce wind swept through the air in all directions.

Occasionally, a streak of light or two would spill down from above, smash giant craters into the ground while also sending vast clouds of red dust erupting into the air.

One of the combatants in the battle was none other than the silver-robed woman by the name of Qu Ling, and she was standing atop the back of the mountainous golden beetle, which was radiating dazzling golden light.

She was facing a group of seven or eight figures, all of whom were dressed in red robes with extremely life-like fire raven designs embroidered onto them. These were none other than the True Flame Sect cultivators, but Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were nowhere to be seen among them.

All of the True Flame Sect cultivators were looking rather worse for wear. In particular, the three Golden Immortals among them seemed to all be carrying injuries.

The trio was led by Xu Yangzi, and they had instructed all of the True Flame Sect cultivators to form a flame-shaped array. Hovering above each of them was a large red flag with scorching flames burning upon them, and bursts of fire were erupting out of the eight flags toward Qu Ling and the golden beetle.

The fire was giving off scorching heat that caused the very space in its wake to tremble and warp, but Qu Ling wasn't taking this battle seriously at all.

Instead, she was casually standing on the golden beetle's back while fiddling with a green gourd in her hand, paying no heed to the ongoing battle at all.

Meanwhile, the golden beetle swept its two front legs through the air, releasing streaks of translucent light, each of which was around 10 feet in length.

The streaks of light came as thick and fast as rain to clash against the crimson flames, and a violent explosion rang out as the streaks of light and scorching flames dissipated in unison, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

"Qu Ling, there's no bad blood between you and our True Flame Sect, so why have you suddenly attacked us?" Xu Yangzi roared in a furious voice.

"All of us have ventured into the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor in order to search for treasures, but as you can see, I'm all on my own, and there's only so much that I can do by myself. Hence, prior to entering the immortal manor, I planted some marks on all of you in secret.

“That way, all I have to do is let you go off on your own for a while, then hunt you all down, and all of the treasures that you've found will be mine. Isn't that a much better strategy than going around searching for treasures on my own?" Qu Ling replied with a wide smile.

Chapter 447: Profound Heavenly Gourd

Xu Yangzi and the others were even more enraged to hear this, but at the same time, they were also extremely alarmed as they hurriedly inspected themselves with their spiritual sense.

A mocking sneer appeared on Qu Ling's face as she swept a sleeve through the air, and an enormous azure silkworm that was several hundred feet in length emerged on one side of her, while a pristine white python of a similar stature appeared on the other side.

Both of the massive creatures immediately pounced at Xu Yangzi and the others as soon as they appeared.

The azure silkworm had quite a bloated appearance, but it was quite a bit faster than the giant white python, and it reached the True Flame Sect cultivators in the blink of an eye before opening its mouth to release a dense mass of azure silk, forming a massive net as it swooped through the air.

These azure silk threads were glittering and translucent, and they were also giving off faint law power fluctuations.

Xu Yangzi and the others were all quite alarmed to see this, and Xu Yangzi hurriedly yelled, "Adopt the Golden Crow Formation!"

Immediately thereafter, he began to make a rapid string of hand seals while opening his mouth to expel a ball of blood essence into the large flag above his head.

The spirit patterns on the surface of the flag instantly began to glow radiantly while turning a golden color, and a pillar of golden fire erupted forth from within.

Everyone else immediately did the same thing, and the flags above their heads also took on a golden hue while releasing pillars of golden flames.

The eight fiery pillars fused as one in the sky above, transforming into a golden brid that was over 1,000 feet in size. The bird had a phoenix comb on its head and a set of long and fiery tail feathers. What was most remarkable about it was that it had three legs, and it spread its enormous wings before swooping toward the oncoming azure net.

As soon as the azure net came into contact with the golden bird, the former instantly erupted into flames and was quickly incinerated into ashes.

Qu Ling raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, the giant white python had also arrived near the True Flame Sect cultivators, and it opened its mouth up wide before releasing a thick pillar of translucent white light.

As soon as the pillar of white light emerged, it instantly shattered in silence into a cloud of white mist that was interspersed with white ice spikes that swept toward the True Flame Sect cultivators from all directions.

The cloud of white mist was giving off bone-chilling glacial qi, and it seemed that even the nearby space had been frozen solid.

Meanwhile, the giant azure silkworm screeched in annoyance at having its attack foiled, and it opened its mouth once again to release a stream of countless silk threads that flew through the air like a volley of arrows.

At the same time, Qu Ling's golden beetle steed was also contributing to the attack, and it swept its two front legs viciously through the air to release two streaks of translucent light, each of which was over 1,000 feet in length.

In the blink of an eye, the two streaks of translucent light appeared in front of the True Flame Sect cultivators before sweeping toward them in a crisscross arrangement.

The collective power of these three beasts was extremely formidable, and an alarmed look flashed through Xu Yangzi's eyes as he hurriedly made a rapid string of hand seals, while everyone else was also looking on with grim expressions.

As the eight flags began to glow more and more radiantly, the flame around the golden bird's body also became brighter and brighter.

......

In the Boundless Sand Sea, the azure flying boat continued onward at a steady pace.

After flying for close to half a day, Han Li and Lu Yuqing had already traveled a considerable distance into the Boundless Sand Sea, and at this point, both of them were looking a little flushed.

Han Li was clearly faring much better, but Lu Yuqing's cheeks were bright red, and she was giving off an unnatural aura of heat.

Han Li was standing at the bow of the boat, using his spirit eyes to scour the surroundings when he suddenly turned to the left.

There on the horizon was a faint spot of green, and it seemed that there was an oasis over there.

"That must be one of the mirages that this place holds," Lu Yuqing said.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

"These mirages are very difficult to deal with, but we'll have to go there if we want to ascertain our current location. However, I'm not very well-versed when it comes to dispelling illusions, so I'll be counting on you, Brother Han," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li nodded in response in an ambiguous fashion, and the azure flying boat beneath his feet accelerated significantly at his behest as it sped toward the oasis.

......

The battle was continuing to rage on above the red plain.

A string of earth-shattering booms was ringing out incessantly, causing the nearby space and the ground down below to tremble violently.

All of the True Flame Sect cultivators were frantically making hand seals, and aside from the three Golden Immortals among them, all of the other cultivators were looking very pale.

The flags hovering above their heads had already taken on a bright golden hue, and the runes on their surfaces were surging incessantly. The golden crow was nowhere to be seen, and it had been replaced by a sea of golden fire that was several thousand feet in size.

The sea of golden flames was keeping all of the attacks from the three formidable beasts at bay, and an impasse had ensued.

"Looks like I underestimated all of you. Then again, you must have some tricks up your sleeve if you're going to enter the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. In any case, this is a perfect opportunity to test out the power of this thing," Qu Ling said with a smile, then tossed the green gourd in her hand forward.

At the same time, a burst of silver light surged out of her mouth, then vanished into the gourd in a flash.

The gourd instantly shuddered before radiating dazzling green light, and it also swelled drastically in size to over 100 feet in length. The entire gourd looked as if it had been fashioned out of exquisite green jade, and its surface was riddled with profound patterns.

All of a sudden, the gourd began to tremble, and countless tadpole-like spirit runes emerged on its surface, radiating blinding silver light.

At the same time, a burst of tremendous law fluctuations surged out of the gourd in all directions, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

"That's an Essential Immortal Treasure!"

The hearts of all of the True Flame Sect cultivators instantly sank upon seeing this.

At the moment, they were completely tied down by the attacks being unleashed by the trio of formidable beasts, and there was simply nothing more that they could do.

A serious look appeared on Qu Ling's face for the first time in the battle, and she made a rapid string of hands seals while releasing several balls of silver light out of her mouth in succession, all of which vanished into the giant green gourd in a flash.

The green light radiating from the gourd instantly became even brighter, while the silver spirit runes on its surface began to writhe and squirm incessantly as if they were living creatures.

All of a sudden, a burst of green light erupted out of the opening of the gourd, then swept directly toward Xu Yangzi and the others.

A green ring then emerged within the stream of green light, giving off a burst of indescribable law fluctuations.

The nearby space instantly collapsed, while all of the world's origin qi within a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers was swept up into a frenzy. Countless balls of five-colored light emerged in the air, then converged toward the green ring before vanishing into it, causing it to swell further in size while the law power fluctuations it was giving off became even more immense.

The stream of green light struck the sea of golden fire in a flash, then pierced straight through it with ease before arriving directly above the heads of the True Flame Sect cultivators.

In the blink of an eye, the streak of green light swallowed up the eight flags suspended above the heads of the True Flame Sect cultivators, and the green ring within it abruptly expanded to encompass the eight flags.

The golden flames burning over the eight flags were instantly snuffed out, following which the flags rapidly shrank down significantly in size.

The expressions of all of the True Flame Sect cultivators instantly changed drastically upon seeing this. Just now, their spiritual connection with the eight flags had suddenly been severed.

A pleased look appeared on Qu Ling's face upon seeing this, and she cast an incantation seal into the air, upon which the streak of green light surged back into the giant green gourd, bringing the eight flags along with it.

Xu Yangzi and the others were completely flabbergasted to see this. Without the support of the eight flags, the sea of golden fire in front of them exploded violently into a vast expanse of fire before quickly fading away, and with that, there was no longer anything standing in the way of the attacks of the three formidable beasts.

Countless azure silken threads swept through the air, ensnaring all of the True Flame Sect cultivators before they had a chance to react.

Immediately thereafter, two thick streaks of translucent light emerged from the nearby space before sweeping toward them like lightning, instantly slicing the bodies of all of the ensnared True Flame Sect cultivators in half.

At the same time, a cloud of glacial mist containing countless ice spikes arrived, releasing such formidable glacial qi that a white mountain of ice that was several kilometers in diameter appeared out of thin air, encapsulating all of the True Flame Sect cultivators within it.

All of the True Flame Sect cultivators had already perished at this point with the exception of the three Golden Immortals, but even they were completely immobilized and only just barely clinging to life.

Qu Ling gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, following which her brows suddenly furrowed slightly as her complexion paled noticeably.

The green gourd was extremely powerful, but she still hadn't refined it yet, so she had to expend an enormous amount of immortal spiritual power to use it.

She took a deep breath, and her complexion quickly returned to normal as she swept a sleeve toward the giant green gourd above her head.

In the blink of an eye, the gourd reverted back to its original size before returning to her grasp.

After that, she turned to the True Flame Sect cultivators encased in the mountain of ice with a cold expression, yet before she had a chance to do anything, a layer of crimson flames suddenly emerged over the bodies of the three Golden Immortals.

The three bursts of crimson fire quickly joined together to release a burst of astonishing power, and the giant mountain of ice shuddered as a large crack appeared on its surface.

The giant white python let loose a furious roar upon seeing this, but it was already too late for it to do anything.

All of a sudden, three streaks of crimson light shot out of the crack like lightning before racing away into the distance, and three nascent souls could be seen within the streaks of light.

A large plume of azure silken threads shot forth, sweeping toward the three nascent souls at an astonishing speed, but they were clearly still too slow to catch the nascent souls.

Chapter 448: Brewing Storm

"Why are you running all of a sudden?" Qu Ling chuckled as she casually flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of silver light that shot forth like lightning before vanishing into thin air.

In the next instant, it reappeared directly above the three nascent souls, revealing itself to be a small silver vial.

A burst of silver light surged out of the opening of the vial, instantly enveloping the three nascent souls, and the nearby space instantly became extremely heavy.

It was as if the three nascent souls had flown into a swamp, and they were barely able to move at all.

A vicious look appeared on the face of Xu Yangzi's nascent soul as it opened its mouth to release a tiny crimson dagger, which came slashing down upon its own head like lightning.

The nascent soul was instantly sliced into two, and one half of it was instantly set alight, transforming into a tiny fiery figure with countless crimson runes dancing within it.

The fiery figure reached out with both hands to grab onto the surrounding silver light, then brought its hands apart violently, tearing a gash into the silver light.

The other half of Xu Yangzi's nascent soul immediately flew out through the opening, following which the tiny red blade shattered, disintegrating into a ball of crimson light that enveloped this half of its nascent.

As a result, the nascent soul's speed was instantly increased by severalfold, and it vanished into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

A hint of surprise flashed through Qu Ling's eyes upon seeing this, and it was already too late for her to try and intervene.

However, she paid no heed to this as she pointed a finger at the small silver vial, and it instantly sucked in the other two nascent souls.

Meanwhile, the mountain of ice shattered, and the giant white python carried the storage tools of all of the True Flame Sect cultivators to Qu Ling on its head.

Qu Ling inspected the contents of the storage tools briefly with his spiritual sense, then gave a pleased nod before stowing them away, following which she patted the giant python on the head as she praised, "Well done today."

A fawning look instantly appeared in the giant python's eyes as it bobbed its head at Qu Ling, then transformed into a streak of white light that flew into a small white pouch strapped to her waist.

The huge azure silkworm also flew over to her before vanishing into another pouch that she was carrying as a streak of azure light.

In the next instant, Qu Ling flew onto the back of the golden beetle, and it asked her in a rather tender voice, "Should we keep going?"

"You are the fastest of the three, yet both of the other two intervened to intercept the escaping nascent souls, so why didn't you do anything?" Qu Ling asked as a cold look flashed through her eyes.

"With your powers, if you really wanted to intercept those nascent souls, you could've done so with ease without my help," the golden beetle scoffed in response.

"Don't think that you can just keep getting away with blatant disobedience like this! I'm only pampering you because you have decent potential, but don't mistake my kindness for weakness!" Qu Ling scolded in a cold voice.

The golden beetle merely buzzed in response, paying no heed to her thinly veiled threat.

A hint of anger flashed through Qu Ling's eyes, but she was unexpectedly tolerant of the golden beetle, and she quickly suppressed her anger as she instructed, "Keep going."

The golden beetle didn't say anything else, either, and it continued onward as a streak of golden light.

Qu Ling sat down onto its back, then cast her gaze toward the green gourd in her hand.

A burst of azure light flashed from the opening of the gourd at her behest, and the eight crimson flags flew out before landing in her grasp, upon which a hint of excitement appeared on her face.

"What's the big deal? It's just some crappy gourd," the golden beetle scoffed.

"This is no ordinary gourd! All Profound Heavenly Treasures are born from heaven and earth and contain unmatched power. They are true Essential Immortal Treasures, and this gourd has already been growing here for countless years. The law powers nurtured within it are the most fundamental secret of this realm, and it's certainly going to be even more formidable than the average Profound Heavenly Treasure!

“I still haven't even refined it yet, and it's already displaying such immense power. Once I have a chance to refine and examine it further, it'll be sure to serve me even better."

Qu Ling's voice sounded quite calm and collected, but there was definitely an underlying hint of excitement.

"I didn't know this gourd was that impressive. How remarkable!" the golden beetle chuckled.

"In any case, I really made the right decision to come here. With this Profound Heavenly Treasure in my possession, the High Zenith Pill will surely be mine! Once I reach the High Zenith Stage and master this treasure, there's a chance I could even ascend to the Great Encompassment Stage in the future! As long as you pledge your absolute loyalty to me, I'll be sure to treat you well," Qu Ling said in an excited voice.

"I'll be thanking you in advance then," the golden beetle replied in an indifferent manner, seemingly unimpressed.

Qu Ling's brows furrowed slightly with displeasure, and she harrumphed coldly, "What an ungrateful little rascal you are!"

She then paid no further heed to the golden beetle as she continued to examine the green gourd in her hand.

All of a sudden, her expression changed slightly as her gaze fell upon the opening of the gourd.

The gourd was entirely green in color as if it had been carved out of a chunk of jade, but the coloration around the gourd's opening was clearly a little light, indicating that it hadn't completely matured yet.

Looks like I harvested it too early, and it's still quite some years away from reaching full maturity. In any case, once I leave this place, I can find some suitable spirit soil and spirit liquid to nurture it, and a million years should be enough for it to mature.

She had found this green gourd in a medicine garden, and she had been ecstatic to stumble upon it. She knew that it hadn't completely matured, but after some consideration, she still decided to harvest it right away.

She knew that harvesting the gourd prior to full maturity was definitely going to have some type of negative impact upon it, but she certainly wasn't going to wait for the next emergence of the immortal manor. Who knew if the gourd would still be there waiting for her next time?

......

In the sky above a crimson mountain, the Vast Flow Palace cultivators were flying through the air.

They were arranged in a line, collectively forming a long streak of blue light that resembled a giant dragon as they raced through the air.

The crimson mountain down below was filled with lush vegetation, among which there was no lack of spirit plants that were giving immense spiritual power fluctuations.

Some of the True Immortal cultivators of the Vast Flow Palace were clearly tempted to make a detour to scoop up some of the spirit plants below, but Luo Qinghai showed no intention of stopping as he continued onward without pause.

As a result, no one else could stop to search for treasures, and the fair-skinned scholar beside Luo Qinghai said, "I don't think we need to be in such a hurry, Palace Master. Some of the spirit plants down below are quite useful, even to the likes of ourselves."

"Trust me, Junior Martial Brother, I have my reasons for doing this," Luo Qinghai replied.

The fair-skinned scholar faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response before falling silent.

......

Meanwhile, the cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace were currently standing in front of a blue palace.

The palace was shimmering with spiritual light, and there were clearly many precious treasures inside.

All of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators were looking at the palace with intense longing in their eyes, while Xiao Jinhan had his hands clasped behind his back as he declared in an indifferent voice, "You can go in, but you only have 15 minutes. Once the 15 minutes are up, we set off right away."

All of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators immediately gave affirmative responses before flying inside, while Xiao Jinhan remained at the entrance of the palace, looking into the distance with a contemplative look in his eyes.

......

Within a gray cloud, a gray flying boat was racing through the air.

Bursts of black light were flashing within the gray cloud like arcs of black lightning, but all of it was kept at bay by a light barrier around the flying boat.

The Dawn Fall Sect cultivators were seated in the cabin of the boat, with Feng Tiandu situated at the center, while everyone else was arranged around him in a circular formation.

Hints of gray light were emanating from their bodies, and it seemed that they were using some type of secret technique.

A long while later, Feng Tiandu's eyes suddenly sprang open, while his brows furrowed tightly.

"How could this be? I can't detect the auras of those two Origin Separation Law Chains at all now... Where could he have gone?" he murmured to himself with a contemplative look on his face.

......

Elsewhere in the immortal manor, a ball of crimson light was flying through a vast sea of clouds in the sky at an extraordinary speed.

The ball of light contained none other than Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and both of them wore serious expressions as they flew along in silence.

......

In the sky above a swamp, the group of Southern Dawn beings had been surrounded by a flock of strange yellow birds.

These birds were around 40 to 50 feet in length with green fleshy lumps on their heads and extremely sharp beaks and talons.

Individually, they weren't particularly powerful, but there were hundreds of them, and they were as fast as lightning.

The Southern Dawn beings were far more powerful than these birds, but they were still trapped here, unable to make any progress.

......

At this point, everyone had already been in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor for quite some time, and many people had already reaped significant rewards or fallen to their demise.

In the Boundless Sand Sea, the azure flying boat continued to race through the air, while Han Li stood at the bow of the boat, scouring his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Lu Yuqing was standing beside him, holding the jade slip that contained the map of the area.

Their unhealthy red complexions had already faded, and it was clear that they had already found a water spirit area that had allowed them to alleviate their fire poisoning.

Even though they would be slowly poisoned again after leaving the water spirit area, as long as they planned out a good route that would allow them to make regular stops at water spirit areas along the way, there shouldn't be any problems.

Hence, the fire poison that the Boundless Sand Sea was extremely notorious for didn't actually pose much of a threat to them.

At this point, the two of them had already ventured quite deep into the Boundless Sand Sea, and they weren't far away from the pathway leading to the other region.

All of a sudden, Han Li's attention was drawn to his right, where there seemed to be another oasis on the distant horizon.

Chapter 449: Relentless Mirages

Lu Yuqing had also noticed the oasis up ahead, and she said, "This is already the 83rd mirage, Brother Han. From this point, we have to begin traveling in the northeastern direction."

Han Li immediately summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis upon hearing this, the Eye of Truth appeared at the center of the axis at his behest.

Faint golden light was radiating from the eye as it cast its gaze forward, and immediately thereafter, the azure flying boat changed directions slightly, flying in the northeastern direction of the oasis.

Even though Han Li had changed directions, the oasis still appeared directly up ahead, and it began to expand on the horizon as the flying boat continued onward.

Han Li made no attempt to try and avoid the oasis, instead flying the spirit boat straight into it.

The surrounding scene suddenly changed as the barren and desolate desert gave way to a lush oasis that was filled with dense greenery and lakes.

The air had also become very moist, while the heat completely faded, and it was as if they had arrived in a cool and refreshing world, one that was in stark contrast with the environment that they had just been in.

However, the surrounding oasis was constantly spinning, making one feel very dizzy and disoriented.

Han Li's expression remained calm and collected, and it seemed that he was already accustomed to this. He continued to make a string of hand seals as he inspected his surroundings through his Eye of Truth, while Lu Yuqing had already closed her eyes and sat down with her legs crossed, channeling her cultivation arts to protect her mind.

The azure flying boat continued onward in a very stable fashion, completely unaffected by the changes in the surrounding environment.

After flying for around 15 minutes, the surrounding oasis suddenly fell away layer upon layer like a series of popped bubbles, and the environment reverted back to that of the parched desert.

Han Li displayed no reaction to this whatsoever, and he continued to look straight ahead while guiding the azure flying boat onward.

"I didn't think that these mirages would be so unavoidable. Thank heavens you're here, Brother Han. Otherwise, even if I had the map and knew the correct route, it would've been impossible for me to get to the destination," Lu Yuqing said with a smile as she slowly opened her eyes.

Han Li merely gave a faint smile upon hearing this.

"We're already not far away from that passageway, but according to what I've heard, the passageway is guarded by a Golden Immortal Stage demon beast, so it won't be easy to bypass," Lu Yuqing continued.

"Do you know what type of demon beast it is?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"No. All I've heard is that it's quite formidable, and that it's already been guarding that passageway for countless years," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head.

"I see. In that case, I suppose we'll just have to adapt according to the situation," Han Li said with a contemplative nod.

Han Li's calm and confident demeanor instilled within Lu Yuqing a great deal of reassurance.

Close to a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and they encountered several more mirages during that time, all of which were smoothly negotiated by Han Li using his Eye of Truth.

According to Lu Yuqing's map, the passageway wasn't very far up ahead.

At this moment, the flying boat was still flying onward, but Han Li's brows had become slightly furrowed.

He was no longer concerned about the mirages in the Boundless Sand Sea, and the only thing that was weighing on his mind was the demon beast that was guarding the passageway.

If the demon beast really had already been guarding the passageway for countless years as Lu Yuqing proclaimed, then who knew if it had managed to develop some special abilities during that time?

Right at this moment, another oasis appeared up ahead, and Han Li hurriedly rid himself of his train of thought so he could focus on the task at hand.

Lu Yuqing examined her map momentarily, then said, "This is the final mirage before the entrance of the passageway. There's no need to change directions, just fly straight ahead."

Han Li nodded in response, and he summoned his Eye of Truth once again as the azure flying boat continued directly forward.

Right as it was about to fly into the oasis up ahead, four more oases suddenly appeared consecutively up ahead.

The five oases formed a pentagon, with each one resonating with one another, and all of them began to glow bright in unison, transforming into an enormous ball of green light in the blink of an eye.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing were both quite taken aback to see this, but at this point, it was already too late to try and stop the flying boat.

The azure flying boat vanished into the ball of green light in a flash, and the surrounding desert vanished once again.

However, on this occasion, instead of appearing in an oasis, Han Li and Lu Yuqing found themselves in a chaotic space with countless glowing green shadows flashing, pulsing, and intertwining with one another, presenting a very disorienting sight to behold.

At the same time, bursts of formidable illusory force surged forth from all directions, and the illusion here was countless times more potent than the oases that they had previously encountered.

"How could this be?" Lu Yuqing exclaimed with a stunned expression.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a burst of formidable illusory power descended upon her, and her eyes instantly became dazed and glazed over as she stood completely rooted to the spot, seemingly having already fallen under the control of the illusion here.

The same type of illusory power was surging toward Han Li as well, and he was naturally far better equipped to handle it than Lu Yuqing, but even so, he was still struck by a rush of dizziness.

He took a deep breath as he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and a cool and refreshing sensation instantly surged through his mind to erase the fog of dizziness.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing suddenly began flailing her arms and legs erratically through the air as a hint of insanity appeared in her eyes.

Immediately thereafter, she turned to Han Li with fierce killing intent in her eyes, and a silver longsword appeared in her grasp amid a flash of silver light.

The sword was radiating extremely bright and pure silver swordlight in the form of countless threads of silver light, and it was pierced directly at Han Li at an astonishing speed.

Even before the sword arrived, a burst of extremely formidable sword intent had already descended upon Han Li, making him feel as if there were countless red-hot needles piercing into his soul.

Even with his formidable spiritual sense, he still couldn't help but give a muffled groan, and he couldn't help but feel stunned by this unexpected turn of events.

On the way here, he had never seen Lu Yuqing use a sword before, so it was a huge surprise to him that her mastery of the sword was already so advanced that she could already harm the souls of her opponents with her sword intent alone.

However, her sword intent was still nowhere near powerful enough to inflict any substantial damage upon him, and he immediately flicked his fingers through the air, releasing five streaks of azure sword qi that intercepted the oncoming silver longsword before threatening to tear it apart.

However, to his surprise, the silver longsword suddenly sprang up like an agile fish, even though it had already left Lu Yuqing's grasp, and it was able to struggle free from the five opposing streaks of sword qi.

At the same time, radiant azure light erupted out of Lu Yuqing's body as she abruptly vanished from the spot.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, and in the next instant, five identical Lu Yuqings appeared all around him, every single one of which was giving off formidable sword qi.

The silver longswords being wielded by the five Lu Yuqings lit up once again before being thrust directly at him, with each one aimed at one of his vital regions.

A film of starlight appeared over Han Li's body to keep the five silver longswords at bay, and at the same time, Han Li swept his gaze across the five Lu Yuqings through his Eye of Truth, upon which a look of realization instantly appeared on his face.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a thick arc of golden lightning, which hurtled toward one of the Lu Yuqings on his right at an incredible speed.

That Lu Yuqing instantly slashed her sword through the air, conjuring up a dense silver sword barrier around her entire body.

The arc of golden lightning struck the sword barrier, and a burst of loud crackling instantly rang out as close to half of the lightning was eradicated by the countless opposing sword projections.

However, the silver sword barrier was also trembling unsteadily, and it didn't take long before it completely exploded, while the silver longsword in Lu Yuqing's hand was also shattered into countless silver pieces.

What little remained of the arc of golden lightning struck Lu Yuqing with tremendous force, and she was instantly sent flying through the air like a ragdoll before crashing into the side of the flying boat, upon which the other four Lu Yuqings around Han Li vanished without a trace.

The only remaining Lu Yuqing gave a muffled groan before springing to her feet. The killing intent in her eyes hadn't abated in the slightest, yet before she had a chance to do anything, a thick translucent chain emerged out of thin air around her, then wound itself around her body like lightning.

The chain was glowing faintly, and it had a rather insubstantial form.

It was a chain formed by Han L's spiritual sense, and even though it had rendered Lu Yuqing completely immobilized, the insane look on her face remained, and she continued to struggle with all her might.

Han Li quickly began to chant an incantation while flicking a finger through the air, releasing several incantation seals in rapid succession, all of which vanished into Lu Yuqing's body one after another.

Countless runes instantly emerged from Lu Yuqing's body, then transformed into several translucent rings that constricted around her.

The protective azure light around her body instantly melted away like snow under the scorching sun, and she slumped to the ground in an unconscious state.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this.

This was a secret technique that he had invented by emulating the restrictive law powers within the Seven Bright Star Rings, and evidently, it had worked quite well.

After successfully subduing Lu Yuqing, a perplexed look appeared on his face.

The silver longsword that she had been using earlier was extremely mediocre. In fact, it couldn't even be considered to be a spirit treasure, and if it weren't for that, perhaps he would still be struggling to restrain her.

The power that she had just displayed had been far more formidable than what she had revealed prior to this point, and Han Li couldn't help but wonder if she had been hiding her true power this entire time.

He took a long look at the unconscious Lu Yuqing, then quickly withdrew his gaze.

At this moment, he was still in quite a perilous situation himself, so he didn't have time to ponder the true nature of Lu Yuqing's powers.

With that in mind, the True Extreme Film around him faded, and he sat down with his legs crossed as he peered into the surrounding chaotic space.

This was quite a formidable illusion, but he could tell that fundamentally, it was no different from the oasis illusions that they had encountered prior to this.

With the experience that he had accumulated in breaking through those illusions, he was confident that he could break out of this one as well.

With that in mind, he immediately began to chant an incantation, and all of the immortal spiritual power was channeled into the Mantra Treasured Axis in front of him.

The axis immediately began to radiate dazzling golden light, and in particular, the Eye of Truth at its center had become extremely bright and translucent.

Chapter 450: A Step Behind

Han Li took a deep breath, then swept a sleeve toward the Eye of Truth, releasing a burst of golden light that vanished into the Eye of Truth in a flash.

The Eye of Truth instantly lit up even further, following which countless threads of golden light shot out from within.

These threads of golden light were extraordinarily fast, instantly spreading throughout the entire surrounding illusory space.

Han Li closed his eyes while making a rapid string of hand seals, and the Eye of Truth instantly began to flash, while the threads of golden light also began to tremble, inspecting everything within the illusory space like countless sensitive feelers.

Close to an hour passed by in the blink of an eye, and this entire time, Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed in a completely still manner.

Right at this moment, a faint thud suddenly rang out somewhere within the illusory space, and a burst of golden light suddenly erupted out of the one of the threads of golden light.

The space near that thread of light shuddered as ripples surged through the surrounding area, and Han Li's eyes instantly sprang open as he turned to that direction while flicking his fingers rapidly through the air.

At the same time, an enormous burst of spiritual sense surged out of his glabella, and a burst of silver light flashed near that patch of rippling space, following which eight or nine spiritual sense chains emerged there in unison.

All of the spiritual sense chains had sharp tips that pierced into the rippling space, and a burst of dazzling green light instantly erupted out of that area, then twisted and warped erratically before forming an extremely faint rift.

Han Li's eyes instantly lit up upon seeing this, and the flying boat beneath him sped up drastically at his behest, transforming into a blurry green shadow that vanished into the rift in the blink of an eye.

The illusory space around Han Li instantly vanished, and the flying boat reappeared in the Boundless Sand Sea before continuing onward without pause.

Only then did he heave an internal sigh of relief.

That illusion had been far more formidable than the previous ones, and even he had almost fallen prey to it.

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing has also returned to a sound frame of mind, and she was no longer struggling as she laid completely still on the ground, seemingly having fallen unconscious.

Han Li turned his gaze to her with a hesitant look on his face.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he seemed to have arrived at a decision, and he released an incantation seal, upon which the spiritual sense chain around Lu Yuqing slowly faded away.

At the same time, the translucent rings of light around her also vanished, following which Han Li flicked a finger through the air to send a streak of azure light flying into her glabella.

She immediately gave a muffled groan, and her long eyelashes fluttered slightly as she slowly opened her eyes. She was still looking a little disoriented, but at the very least, the deranged look in her eyes had faded.

After taking a moment to collect herself, her expression abruptly changed drastically as she hurriedly sat up before looking around with a panicked expression.

Only after realizing that she was safe on Han Li's flying boat did her expression ease slightly, but there was still a hint of lingering fear in her eyes as she said, "It looks like you've already managed to get through that illusion, Brother Han. I didn't think that the final mirage would be so formidable."

Han Li had been observing Lu Yuqing's expression this entire time, and he remained silent as his brows furrowed slightly.

Lu Yuqing had naturally noticed the changes in his expression, and she asked, "What is it, Brother Han?"

Han Li shook his head as he replied, "Nothing. How are you feeling right now?"

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this, then pressed her hand over her own abdomen as a hint of pain and surprise appeared in her eyes.

"How did I sustain these injuries?"

"Back in the mirage, you fell prey to the illusion and suddenly attacked me, so I had no choice but to subdue you by force, and I was a little too forceful in the heat of the moment," Han Li explained.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an apologetic look appeared on her face as she said, "I'm sorry for always being a hindrance to you, Brother Han."

Han Li waved a dismissive hand in response, then cast his gaze forward as he said, "Now that we've bypassed the final mirage, the passageway should be just up ahead. Let's take a short break before we continue onward."

He swept a sleeve through the air to cast an incantation seal as he spoke, and the azure light radiating from the flying boat instantly rippled slightly as it drew to a halt.

Lu Yuqing nodded in response, then sat back down with her legs crossed before taking a pill.

A layer of bright azure light quickly appeared around her, forming an azure light barrier that encompassed her entire body.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

It didn't seem like Lu Yuqing was putting on an act, so could it be that she had already completely forgotten what had happened in that final mirage?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, but at the same time, he made a mental note to be on his guard.

With a sweep of his sleeve, numerous streaks of blue light were released, each of which contained an array flag that landed somewhere near the flying boat.

The array flags were radiating bright blue light, forming a thick blue light barrier that encompassed the entire azure flying boat.

After setting up the array, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a crimson pill.

The pill was enshrouded in a layer of dense crimson light, and it was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations. This was none other than one of the Vast Heaven Pills that had been given to him by Wyrm 3.

In order to break that final mirage, he had expended a great deal of immortal spiritual power, and he was going to have to face a Golden Immortal Stage demon beast up ahead, so he had to replenish his own immortal spiritual power reserves as quickly as possible.

After taking the pill, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then channeled his cultivation arts to digest the pill, and a layer of red light quickly appeared over his face.

......

In the sky above a black desert in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, a green jade flying carriage was hurtling through the air.

This place was none other than the Black Rock Desert that Han Li and Lu Yuqing had just passed through, and there was a tall man standing on the flying carriage, holding a white disk treasure with a speck of red light flashing upon its surface.

All of a sudden, the man raised his head and cast his gaze forward as he mused in a cold voice, "I knew there was a Spirit Refinement Technique practitioner nearby! You're not getting away from me!"

Immediately thereafter, the four wheels of the flying carriage transformed into four miniature azure tornadoes at his behest, and the speed of the flying carriage was instantly enhanced by severalfold as it shot through the air at an incredible pace.

......

An hour passed by in the blink of an eye.

On the azure flying carriage, Han Li opened his eyes, having already completely replenished his immortal spiritual power reserves.

A short while later, the azure light around Lu Yuqing also faded, and she appeared to have recovered from her injuries as well.

"Let's go," Han Li declared, then swept a sleeve through the air to withdraw the array around the flying boat before continuing onward.

Both of them remained silent, and before long, they had already been flying for close to three hours.

This was supposed to be the deepest part of the Boundless Sand Sea, but the scorching heat in the air was gradually diminishing, and a slightly chilly aura had emerged in its stead.

All of a sudden, Han Li's pupils contracted slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the azure flying boat instantly drew to a halt.

As it turned out, another oasis had appeared up ahead.

This oasis appeared to be around 40 to 50 kilometers in radius, and it was covered in lush greenery.

At the center of the oasis was a crescent-shaped lake, the surface of which was glowing radiantly. Even though it was a bright and sunny day, the lake was still extremely eye-catching, resembling a radiant moon that had fallen upon the Boundless Sand Sea.

Unlike the oases that had come before it, this one was not a mirage.

At the center of the crescent-shaped lake was a rapidly revolving black vortex that was several dozen feet in size.

Bursts of spatial fluctuations were emanating out of the black vortex, and there was a faint speck of white light deep within it, seemingly leading to another world.

All of the water in the lake around the vortex had been stirred up and was splashing audibly.

"That's the spatial passageway!" Lu Yuqing exclaimed in an ecstatic voice.

However, Han Li wasn't looking at the black vortex. Instead, his gaze was focused on a small forest beside the lake, and his expression suddenly changed slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air to stow the azure flying boat away, then descended toward the oasis down below.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon seeing this, then immediately followed along out of habit.

As they drew closer to the oasis, a surprised look suddenly appeared on Lu Yuqing's face as she stopped in her tracks.

As it turned out, there was a demon beast that was over 100 feet in size laying in the forest down below.

The greenery in the forest was quite dense, and the demon beast had been concealed within the undergrowth, so Lu Yuqing had failed to spot it prior to this.

The beast resembled a giant ox, and it had an extremely intimidating physique, with bands of bulging muscles beneath a layer of azure jade-like fur.

However, as opposed to hooves, it had four sets of sharp talons that were giving off a cold gleam.

Even in death, the beast was still giving off a very formidable aura, so it had to have been an extremely powerful being.

However, it had been decapitated, and its huge head was laying on the ground not far away. There was a single black horn on its head, and there was a horrified look in its eyes, as if it had witnessed something extremely terrifying right before it met its demise.

"It looks like someone already got here before us... That makes sense. All of the major powers who entered the immortal manor on this occasion are aware that there's a passageway leading to another region deep in this Boundless Sand Sea. They may not have a map of this place, but given their powers, it's certainly not impossible for them to find this place before us," Lu Yuqing mused.

Han Li nodded in response, and a grim look appeared on his face as his gaze fell upon the wound on the demon beast's neck.

The cross-section of the wound was very smooth and even, indicating that the beast had been decapitated by a single blow.

Furthermore, no signs of battle could be seen in the nearby oasis, indicating that it had been slain by a single attack before it even had a chance to retaliate.

Only an extremely formidable cultivator could've dealt with a Golden Immortal Stage demon beast so easily.

Han Li landed beside the body of the huge demon beast, then brushed a hand over the wound on its neck, picking up some of its blood before taking a sniff, upon which his eyes immediately lit up.

Lu Yuqing was rather taken aback by Han Li's strange gesture, and she couldn't help but ask, "Is there something wrong, Brother Han?"

"No," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, while a burst of azure light flashed over his hand to remove the blood there. "In any case, now that the beast has already been killed, we won't have to go through the effort of trying to get past it. Let's go."

Lu Yuqing naturally had no objections to this, and the two of them flew over to the black vortex before peering inside.

"There doesn't seem to be any danger," Han Li concluded after a brief assessment, and with that, the two of them flew into the black passageway.

Chapter 451: Palace

Han Li felt his vision blur for a moment, and in the next instant, he was already in a completely new environment.

After taking a brief moment to gather his bearings, he inspected his surroundings to find that the terrain was quite flat, and he was situated in a red and barren area that was completely devoid of vegetation and living creatures.

Lu Yuqing was situated not far away from him, and at this moment, she was also gradually returning to her senses.

A whirlwind swept past not far in front of them, raising a cloud of red dust into the air, and there was a primordial aura permeating throughout the entire area.

Han Li slowly swept his gaze over his surroundings, and his brows suddenly furrowed slightly.

Just now, he had attempted to release his spiritual sense to scout the surrounding area, but he discovered that there was a type of restrictive force around his body that wasn't impeding his movements at all, but rendered him completely unable to release his spiritual sense out of his body at all.

"Just how big is this Infernal Frost Immortal Manor? And why are there so many strange things in this place?" Han Li couldn't help but sigh in a slightly exasperated voice.

In contrast, Lu Yuqing wasn't very surprised by this, and she smiled as she said, "When I was a child, I once read an ancient scripture from my father's study. According to that scripture, the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm was formerly known as the Infernal Frost Immortal Region, but for some unknown reason, its name was later changed.

“If this Infernal Frost Immortal Manor has something to do with the former name of the immortal region, then it's no wonder that it's such a massive and complex place."

Han Li was just about to respond when his expression suddenly stiffened slightly, and he was suddenly rooted to the spot with his mouth slightly agape.

Lu Yuqing was quite startled to see this, and she hurriedly asked, "Are you alright, Brother Han?"

Han Li was silent for a moment longer, then replied in an ambiguous manner, "I'm fine, I just suddenly recalled some things..."

Lu Yuqing wasn't entirely convinced, but she didn't ask any further questions.

Han Li's gaze drifted over the surrounding area before settling on a certain direction deep within this barren land, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

What had actually cut him off earlier wasn't any thought that had suddenly popped into his mind. Instead, it was his Mantra Treasured Axis.

For some reason, as soon as he cast his gaze toward that direction, the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis would begin to flash, as if it could sense the presence of time law powers there.

"Which way should we go next, Brother Han? It looks like our spiritual sense isn't going to help us here," Lu Yuqing said.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then pointed in the direction that his Mantra Treasured Axis was responding to as he replied, "Let's go in this direction first."

"Sure," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

Thus, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon that azure spirit boat, and after both he and Lu Yuqing had flown onto the flying boat, it sped away as a streak of azure light.

As they flew through the air, the sound of the howling wind instantly grew louder, and Han Li stood atop the flying boat as he continued to scour the barren land down below.

Looking down from above, he discovered that the terrain here wasn't as flat and level as it had first appeared. Instead, some hills could be seen down below, but they were far too small to be considered anywhere near mountains.

The further they went, the more complex the terrain down below became. Aside from those small hills, a series of plains and ravines of different sizes and depths had also begun to appear on the landscape. The ravines seemed to have been carved out by flowing water, but any bodies of water here had long since run dry.

After flying for a few minutes, Han Li suddenly raised an eyebrow as he spotted a set of ruins that appeared to have once been a city on the distant horizon, and the flying boat instantly accelerated in that direction at his behest.

Upon reaching the edge of the set of ruins, the azure flying boat descended in front of a moat that was over 100 feet wide.

However, the moat was also completely dry, and the parched and fractured earth at the bottom of the moat indicated that it had also been dry for a very long time.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing cast their eyes forward to find that the city wall across from the moat was still relatively intact, but it had clearly been severely ravaged by all types of weapons, and it was quite remarkable that it was still standing.

The two of them made their way toward the city over a nearby stone bridge, and upon reaching the center of the bridge, Han Li suddenly spotted a piece of bone jutting out of the bottom of the dried moat down below.

It appeared to be the curved horn of some type of demon beast, and it was roughly as thick as a grown man's arm.

Han Li stopped in his tracks as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which instantly raised that entire section of the ground down below to reveal a complete skeleton.

A hint of surprise instantly appeared on Lu Yuqing's face as she caught sight of the full skeleton, and Han Li was also quite taken aback by what he was seeing.

The skeleton was very strange in appearance, and it was impossible to identify what type of demon beast it had once belonged to. However, one thing that was certain was that it had definitely belonged to an enormous creature that wasn't inferior in size to the Giant Mountain Ape.

The piece of bone that Han Li had presumed was a horn was actually just a section of one of the creature's teeth.

"Do you recognize this beast, Brother Han?" Lu Yuqing asked with a puzzled expression.

"No aura of the beast remains at all, and I can't identify it based on its skeleton alone," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

While it was true that he didn't know what this beast was, it occurred to him that the skeleton looked as if it could belong to one of the beasts that he had seen on that mural in the hall near the spirit medicine garden from before.

Given that the mural depicted a battle, Han Li couldn't help but wonder if the battle depicted on the mural had taken place at this very place.

However, as soon as this possibility occurred to him, he immediately realized that this couldn't be true. The battle depicted on the mural had been one of a massive scale, and if it had truly taken place here, then this city would've definitely been completely razed to the ground.

After crossing the stone bridge, Han Li and Lu Yuqing arrived at the city gates to find a large plaque hanging overhead, bearing the words "Moon Lake City".

After passing through the city gate, a disturbance suddenly arose in Han Li's heart, and he couldn't help but stop in his tracks again.

The dozen or so active Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body were flashing incessantly, and they were reacting even more urgently than before.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze into the city to find that it had already been reduced to complete ruins. There were collapsed buildings everywhere, and some demon beast and human remains could be seen protruding out of the piles of rubble, but they were nothing more than bones.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing made their way down the main road deeper into the city, and it was more of the same, with more rubble and collapsed buildings littering the landscape. Only as they reached the core area of the city did they spot a golden palace that was over 1,000 feet tall in the distance.

Compared with all of the other buildings that they had seen on the way here, this golden palace was exceptionally well preserved, with only some cracks on its walls and a slightly collapsed roof.

Aside from that, the palace was glowing with dazzling golden radiance, as if there were a golden membrane over its surface that was reflecting the light of the sun.

Han Li was just about to approach the palace when he felt a burst of heat flash through his storage bracelet.

His brows furrowed slightly as he stopped in his tracks once again, then flipped a hand over to produce a glowing green jade box.

A faint crack rang out as he opened the jade box to reveal a gray eyeball inside. The eyeball looked as if it had been carved out of stone, and waves of faint gray light were constantly emanating from it.

"What's this?" Lu Yuqing asked with an intrigued expression.

"It's the eye of a Primordial Fei Beast," Han Li replied in a concise manner.

Lu Yuqing could tell that Han Li didn't want to elaborate on the matter, so she didn't ask any further questions.

Han Li examined the eye of the Primordial Fei Beast for a moment to find that all that it was doing was releasing faint waves of gray light. He was unable to tell what was happening, so he could only hold it in the palm of his hand as he continued to approach the golden palace.

Upon reaching around 1,000 feet away from the golden palace, Han Li's eyes suddenly narrowed slightly as he grabbed onto Lu Yuqing's arm, then dragged her behind a collapsed wall for cover.

As it turned out, there was a silver-robed woman standing at the foot of the gate of the golden palace. She was making a hand seal with one hand and holding a damaged Drigug in the other while casting a series of incantation seals toward the palace gates. [1]

Lu Yuqing took a glance at the silver-robed woman over the collapsed wall, then exclaimed, "Why is she here?"

Han Li hurriedly raised a finger to his own lips to make a silencing gesture.

Even though there was a spiritual sense restriction here, the silver-robed woman was clearly a very formidable Golden Immortal cultivator, and they could be overheard if they weren't careful.

The woman was none other than Qiu Ling, and the Drigug that she was holding was riddled with antiquated runes.

Rays of golden light were emanating from its surface, and they were connected to a peculiar circular design on the gates of the golden palace, seemingly undoing the restriction on the gates.

Han Li could sense clear time law fluctuations emanating from both the Drigug in Qu Ling's hand and the golden palace gates, and his brows were tightly furrowed as he carefully peered over the collapsed wall.

Only then did he notice that there was a strange figure next to her.

Even though it was resting on its haunches, the creature was still standing at 70 to 80 feet tall, and at first glance, it resembled a yellow wall. Only upon closer inspection would one be able to notice the peculiar spirit patterns all over its body.

The creature had its back facing Han Li, so he wasn't able to see what it looked like, but it reminded him very much of the Primordial Fei Beast that he had slain all those years ago.

This creature was far smaller in stature than that Primordial Fei Beast, but the outline of its body, the coloration of its skin, and those peculiar spirit patterns were all virtually identical to that of the Primordial Fei Beast.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face, and he took a glance down at the eyeball that he was holding.

Right at this moment, the faint white light that was emanating from the eye suddenly brightened significantly, resembling a beacon that had suddenly lit up in the night.

The strange creature that was resting on its haunches next to Qu Ling instantly sprant to its feet, then turned around to reveal a hideous face with a flat nose, a massive mouth, and a huge single eye situated at the center of its head.

Sure enough, this was just a miniature Primordial Fei Beast!

The Primordial Fei Beast let loose a thunderous roar as a thick pillar of white light shot out of its eye, hurtling directly toward Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he grabbed onto Lu Yuqing's wrist, then sprang up into the air to evade the pillar of white light before descending onto the main path leading to the golden palace.

As a result, the two of them were completely exposed.

[1]. A Drigug or Kartika is a Buddhist knife used for ceremonial purposes.

[Back]

Chapter 452: Trapped

Qu Ling instantly spun around in the wake of the commotion, and a slightly surprised look appeared on her face as she spotted Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

However, in the next instant, her gaze fell upon the gray eyeball in Han Li's hand, and a furious look immediately appeared on her face.

Qu Ling turned around fully to face Han Li, and there were daggers shooting out of her eyes as she said in a furious voice, "So you're the one who killed my other Primordial Fei Beast! I would've been done here a lot sooner if it wasn't for you!"

Han Li's mouth was suddenly feeling a little parched. At this point, it had become apparent that the Primordial Fei Beast that he had slain all those years ago just so happened to have belonged to Qu Ling, and it seemed that it had been quite important to her as well.

His mind was racing, and he hurriedly said to Lu Yuqing through voice transmission, "We have to split up and run!"

Immediately thereafter, he turned and fled into the distance.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this, seemingly still a little dazed and confused, but she then immediately reacted as well, flying away in another direction as a streak of azure light.

"You're not getting away!" Qu Ling harrumphed coldly as she raised a hand and pointed a finger at Han Li from afar.

A streak of white light instantly shot out of her sleeve, revealing itself to be a white rope that was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations interspersed with faint law fluctuations.

It was an immortal treasure, and it set off in pursuit of Han Li as a thin streak of white light.

At the same time, she turned to the little Primordial Fei Beast beside her and instructed, "Go and kill that woman."

The Primordial Fei Beast took a resentful glance at Han Li, but it clearly didn't dare to go against Qu Ling's orders, and it stomped a foot down onto the ground, propelling itself toward Lu Yuqing as a yellow shadow.

As Han Li was flying through the air, he could sense the white rope hurtling toward him from behind at an astonishing speed, and in the blink of an eye, it was only several kilometers away from him.

He hurriedly conjured up a pair of golden wings on his back, then began flapping them rapidly to accelerate further in his escape.

A cold smile appeared on Qu Ling's face as she made a hand seal before pointing a finger forward, and the white rope instantly accelerated as well, transforming into a blurry white shadow that caught up to Han Li in an instant, then split up into five or six identical projections that pounced at Han Li from both the left and the right.

Han Li was quite alarmed to see this, and arcs of golden lightning surfaced over his Thunderstorm Wings amid a rumbling thunderclap, allowing him to just barely evade the rope projections right before they closed in around him.

In the next instant, he reappeared close to 10 kilometers away amid a flash of lightning, but there was a very grim look on his face.

As it turned out, the spatial restrictions here were even more severe than the ones in the Light Frost Region, and that was why he wasn't able to get any further away with his lightning movement technique.

All of a sudden, Qu Ling's voice rang out from directly behind Han Li.

"Cease your futile resistance!"

Han Li was extremely alarmed to hear this, and he didn't even have time to turn around to examine the situation as he hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which instantly began to spin in reverse.

At the same time, a flash of golden lightning erupted out of his Thunderstorm Wings once again, and he vanished for a second time amid a rumbling thunderclap, this time completing the sequence of actions several times faster than before.

Only after reappearing close to 10 kilometers away amid a flash of golden lightning did Han Li dare to turn around, and he discovered Qu Ling standing on the spot where he had just been a moment ago with a surprised look on her face.

"It looks like you've got some unexpected tricks up your sleeve, but that's not going to save you!" Qu Ling harrumphed coldly, and dazzling silver light surged out of her body before forming a pair of indistinct silver wings.

The silver wings spread open, and Qu Ling instantly vanished from the spot.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability in conjunction with his lightning movement technique once again, allowing him to vanish from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning yet again.

His lightning movement technique was greatly enhanced thanks to his Reversal True Axis, and he had only just vanished from the spot when Qu Ling appeared up above, then reached out with one hand, and five streaks of gray light shot out of her fingertips.

However, in the instant that the five streaks of gray light descended, Han Li had already disappeared, so she had failed to strike her target.

Qu Ling's expression remained unchanged as she turned to a certain direction, where Han Li stumbled out of thin air amid a flash of golden lightning.

A cold sneer appeared on her face as she flapped her silver wings, vanishing from the spot once again in a wraith-like fashion, this time picking up even more speed than before.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he continued to flee using his lightning movement technique, and thus, a chase ensued, with a streak of silver light pursuing a streak of golden light through the air.

The streak of silver light was only getting faster as time passed, and it was moving in a completely silent and wraith-like fashion, leaving a trail of silver afterimages in its wake.

However, the streak of golden light was able to keep up with its pace, and it was also getting faster and faster, just barely eluding the streak of silver light every single time.

The thunderclaps ringing out from Han Li's lightning movement technique were ringing out more and more frequently, until it became one continuous rumbling sound with no gaps in between.

As the chase continued, for some reason, the two returned to the golden palace.

All of a sudden, Qu Ling emerged out of thin air amid a flash of silver light, and her brows were slightly furrowed.

Close to 10 kilometers away, Han Li also reappeared amid a flash of golden lightning, and he was panting slightly as he stared intently at Qu Ling.

Qu Ling didn't continue to come after him, so he didn't continue to run.

His immortal spiritual power was able to support both his Reversal True Axis and lightning movement technique at once, but moving at such a high speed was extremely taxing on his body and mind, so he was eager for some respite.

"I didn't think a mere True Immortal like yourself would be able to elude me for so long. It looks like I'll have to get a little serious," Qu Ling harrumphed coldly as she vanished from the spot once again amid a flash of silver lightning.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately sped away as an arc of golden lightning.

However, right at this moment, the space around him abruptly shuddered, and a vast expanse of gray light emerged, forming a gray area that instantly encompassed everything within a radius of over 10,000 feet.

Streaks of gray light were surging throughout this area, and there were countless gray shadows everywhere. Even though this area only had a radius of just over 10,000 feet, it seemed to be a completely independent realm that was extremely far away from the outside world.

An arc of golden lightning appeared on the edge of the gray area, and it was like a fish that had been caught in a net, unable to break free despite its desperate struggles.

As a result, Han Li was forced to reappear with a grim look on his face.

It was clear that this was a domain ability.

On that Transient Guild mission to kill Ping Yaozi, Han Li had witnessed Gu Jie's avatar unleash a domain ability, but that was only a pseudo-domain, and it couldn't even begin to compare with this gray domain.

At this moment, he felt as if he had fallen into a vast gray swamp, and bursts of spatial power interspersed with law powers were converging toward him from all directions, rendering him virtually completely immobilized.

The countless gray shadows within the domain resembled countless ghosts that were pouncing at him from all directions, and they were the source of the bursts of restrictive law powers.

Even before the gray shadows arrived, Han Li was struck by a sense of feebleness, and his immortal spiritual power circulation had also become a little sluggish.

What kind of law power is this?

Han Li was greatly alarmed as he let loose a low roar, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared.

The time law thread on the axis was glowing radiantly, and it was releasing bursts of time law powers that enveloped his entire body.

Even though only a small portion of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were active, and the time law powers they were releasing was rather sparse, the laws of time were still one of the three paramount laws, and the sensation of feebleness in his body was significantly alleviated.

Han Li immediately took advantage of this opportunity to make a hand seal, and a giant azure sword instantly appeared in front of him.

The sword was giving off dazzling azure light, and there were thick arcs of lightning surging all over its surface. It was giving off an astonishingly formidable aura, and it was lashed through the four times in different directions like lightning.

Four massive sword projections appeared before striking the surrounding gray shadows, and all of them were eradicated in an instant, but even more gray shadows continued to converge toward Han Li from all directions.

Han Li took a deep breath to muster up his resolve, then lashed out with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword at his surroundings over and over again, keeping all of the gray shadows at bay.

At the center of the gray domain stood Qu Ling with her hands clasped behind her back, and at this moment, she was staring at Han Li with a combination of shock and elation on her face.

"He's a cultivator of the laws of time, and he's already manifested a law thread! Even the heavens are on my side!" Qu Ling chortled with glee, but a contemplative look then appeared on her face, and it seemed that she was rather conflicted about something.

However, a determined look then quickly surfaced in her eyes, and she began chanting an incantation while sweeping her sleeves through the air, and a gray throne appeared behind her amid a flash of gray light.

This throne appeared no different from the thrones of mortal emperors, except it was gray in color instead of golden, and there was a gray dragon wrapped around each of the armrests. In contrast with normal dragons, these two dragons were extremely sinister and menacing in appearance, and the entire gray throne was giving off a burst of vast law fluctuations.

Qu Ling sat down onto the throne, and her aura was elevated once again as a layer of silver light emerged over her face to obscure her facial features, and it was as if she had instantly transformed into a cold and regal queen.

She then raised a hand before setting it down onto the head of one of the gray dragons on the armrest, and the dragon instantly opened its mouth to release a ball of dense gray light with countless gray runes flashing within it.

The ball of light was giving off terrifying law power fluctuations, and it fused into the gray domain in a flash, upon which the size and number of gray shadows in the domain instantly increased drastically.

As a result, the pressure on Han Li also became severely heightened, and his expression darkened even further as he channeled all of his immortal spiritual power into his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, causing it to glow even more brightly as it swept toward the surrounding gray shadows.

At the same time, four treasures appeared above his head in succession, namely a miniature gray mountain, a silver bell, a black tusk sword, and a large black flag.

Chapter 453: Betrayal

The four treasures that Han Li had just summoned were the very same immortal treasures that he had obtained after killing Tao Yu and his two guards.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release four balls of azure light into the four immortal treasures, and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain swelled rapidly in size while releasing dazzling gray light.

Countless balls of gray light the size of water vats flew out of the mountain one after another toward the surrounding gray shadows, while the silver bell was also glowing radiantly with silver light while chiming loudly to send silver soundwaves surging through the air in all directions.

At the same time, the tusk sword and the black flag were also releasing formidable streaks of tusk-shaped sword qi and waves of black light, respectively.

Out of these four immortal treasures, none of them had been refined much by Han Li with the exception of the Integrated Five Extremes Mountains, but their combined power was still extremely formidable, and coupled with the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, they were able to keep the surrounding gray shadows at bay again.

However, right at this moment, Han Li felt a shadow suddenly loom over him, following which a giant gray dragon claw emerged out of thin air amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

The dragon claw was formed by gray mist, yet it was extremely imposing and appeared to have a substantial form. It seemed to possess boundless power, reaching straight through the sword qi released by the tusk sword before grabbing toward Han Li's chest with unstoppable might.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as Daoist Xie abruptly appeared in front of him in its humanoid puppet form amid a flash of golden lightning, and it reached out with both hands to release thick arcs of lightning, which converged in the blink of an eye to form a giant golden lightning ax.

The ax was swung viciously through the air, and it clashed against the gray dragon claw with an earth-shattering boom.

Daoist Xie shuddered as it took a step back, but the gray dragon claw was also repelled and faded away into the surrounding gray space.

Qu Ling raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, clearly not expecting Han Li to have a Golden Immortal Stage puppet on his side, but a cold sneer then appeared on her face as she laid a hand onto the other gray dragon on her armrest.

Her gray throne began to glow radiantly once again as three gray mirrors slowly emerged from behind it. On the surface of each mirror was inscribed an ancient character for "decay", "insanity", and "death".

The entire gray spirit domain began to ripple once again as all of the surrounding gray shadows surged violently, while the gray light within the domain rapidly became denser.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, the gray throne abruptly shuddered, and the dense gray light that it was releasing quickly faded, while the unrest within the gray domain also subsided.

Qu Ling was rather taken aback by this, and she quickly noticed that for some reason, threads of white light that were crackling incessantly had appeared within the gray light being released by her throne.

She immediately stopped what she was doing upon seeing this, then opened her mouth to release a burst of silver light that enveloped the entire throne.

Only then was the throne slowly stabilized, and the hints of white light within the gray light gradually began to fade away.

Qu Ling's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, but she continued to cast a string of incantation seals into the gray throne. At the same time, she swept her other sleeve through the air, releasing two streaks of light, one azure and one golden, and they transformed into a giant azure silkworm and a huge golden beetle, respectively.

"Go and capture that man, but take care not to hurt him as he's going to be very useful to me," Qu Ling instructed.

The giant azure silkworm immediately heeded her call, flying through the air toward Han Li, while the golden beetle remained still on the spot.

Qu Ling's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and she instructed in a cold voice, "You go as well!"

"Alright..." the golden replied in a lazy voice, then began to fly toward Han Li at a leisurely pace.

Qu Ling gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then turned her attention back to her gray throne and began releasing incantation seals with greater urgency.

Meanwhile, Han Li was busy keeping the surrounding gray shadows at bay with his five immortal treasures while searching for a way out.

Daoist Xie had already returned to his body. This was a trump card that he didn't dare to use all the time, and he had to save it for unforeseen dangers like the situation that had just transpired.

At this moment, his face was rather pale, and his breathing was also a little labored.

Enshrouded within Qu Ling's spirit domain, he was unable to draw upon any of the world's origin qi from the outside world, and that severely hampered his powers and his immortal spiritual power recovery.

Furthermore, using five immortal treasures at once was extremely taxing, and he didn't have much immortal spiritual power left.

Not only that, but bursts of restrictive law powers continued to surge toward him incessantly from the surrounding spirit domain, and the time law powers around him were struggling to keep them at bay.

I have to find a way out soon!

Han Li's mind was racing as he scoured his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and all of a sudden, his gaze fell upon a certain point in the spirit domain.

Immediately thereafter, dazzling azure light erupted out of his body as he abruptly flew toward the edge of the domain while making a rapid string of hand seals.

Meanwhile, his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also began to glow radiantly like a blinding azure sun, and the golden lightning that it was releasing had also brightened significantly.

Han Li pointed a finger at the sword from afar, and it instantly circled around in the air before transforming into a giant azure dragon that was over 1,000 feet in size.

Every single one of the dragon's scales was flashing with formidable sword qi, and thick arcs of golden lightning were surging over its entire body, while its aura had also been significantly elevated compared with back when it was in its sword form.

The giant azure dragon pounced forward with formidable power, releasing countless streaks of peerlessly sharp sword qi that vanquished all of the gray shadows in its path.

Han Li was flying close behind the giant azure dragon, while the other four immortal treasures had also returned to his side, orbiting around him to shield him from the surrounding gray shadows.

It didn't take long before he reached the edge of the gray spirit domain, but right at this moment, the huge azure silkworm appeared in front of him in a flash before opening its cavernous mouth to release countless silken threads, which intertwined with one another in mid-air to form a massive azure net that descended upon him.

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this, but his mobility was severely restricted within the spirit domain, rendering him unable to take evasive measures.

The azure net didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but it was giving off bursts of special law fluctuations, and if he were to be ensnared in it, it was most likely going to be very difficult for him to break free.

In this dire situation, Han Li pointed a finger at the large black flag beside him, and it instantly swelled drastically in size while releasing a vast expanse of black light that surged toward the oncoming azure net.

A dull thud rang out as the black flag was ensnared by the azure net, and the latter instantly reverted back into countless azure silken threads that spun rapidly around the black flag, forming an azure cocoon in the blink of an eye.

The black flag was instantly immobilized within the cocoon, yet Han Li displayed no intention of trying to free it from the cocoon as he abruptly changed directions, flying around the azure cocoon before continuing onward.

The giant azure silkworm was just about to release another flurry of silken threads upon seeing this when the golden beetle suddenly appeared beside it.

Han Li instantly stopped cold in his tracks as he stared blankly at the golden beetle.

The golden beetle also looked back at Han Li with a bright gleam in its beady little eyes.

The azure silkworm was ecstatic to see that Han Li had suddenly drawn to a halt, and it opened its cavernous mouth to release another flurry of azure silken threads, which instantly formed another azure net that swooped down upon Han Li.

Han Li immediately snapped back to his senses upon seeing this, withdrawing his gaze from the golden beetle as he pointed a finger at the black tusk sword.

A vast expanse of black swordlight surged out of the tusk sword, instantly forming a sea of sword qi that was around an acre in size to oppose the descending azure net.

The giant azure silkworm screeched in derision as it opened its mouth once again, releasing a gust of fierce azure wind this time.

The gust of wind was filled with azure blades of wind that swept rapidly through the air, hurtling toward Han Li from another direction to prevent him from getting away.

All of a sudden, a burst of bright golden light erupted out of the golden beetle's body, then converged entirely onto its two front legs.

Two streaks of translucent light that were each several hundred feet in length instantly appeared on those two front legs, and they were giving off a peerlessly sharp aura.

With a wave of its two front legs, the golden beetle released the two streaks of translucent light, but instead of attacking Han Li, it was targeting the giant azure silkworm beside it.

The azure silkworm was greatly alarmed by this, and it hurriedly attempted to fly back in retreat, but the two streaks of translucent light had been unleashed from very close proximity and were far too fast for it to evade.

Two dull thuds rang out, and green blood splattered in all directions as the giant silkworm's body was sliced into three pieces by the two streaks of translucent light.

As a result, the descending azure net and the gust of fierce azure wind instantly dissipated in unison.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and there was also a hint of nostalgia, as if he had been reunited with an old friend.

The azure silkworm screeched frantically, and the three sections of its body all began to radiate dazzling azure light as they continued to flee into the distance.

At the same time, they assembled themselves back together, and the flesh around the gashes was squirming incessantly while slowly fusing as one again.

The golden beetle immediately lashed out once again upon seeing this, releasing a flurry of streaks of translucent light at once this time.

In the face of these streaks of translucent light, the azure silkworm's body was as fragile as tofu, and it was instantly shredded into countless pieces.

At the same time, the golden beetle flew through the air as a streak of golden light, passing through the shredded remains of the azure silkworm before emerging on the other side in a flash.

Held in its mouth none other than the azure silkworm's nascent soul, which appeared as if it had been carved out of green jade and was radiating dazzling azure light.

Immediately thereafter, the golden beetle opened its mouth before devouring the nascent soul whole.

After that, it still didn't seem to be completely satisfied, and a burst of golden light surged out of its mouth to draw in the scattered remains of the giant azure silkworm for its consumption.

All of this had taken place in the span of just a few seconds.

Chapter 454: Assistance

Following the demise of the azure silkworm, the cocoon around the black flag also fell apart, and it immediately flew back to Han Li as a black shadow.

However, before Han Li even had a chance to catch his breath, a thunderous roar of fury abruptly rang out from deep within the spirit domain.

"How dare you betray me!"

A streak of silver light shot rapidly through the air, then faded to reveal Qu Ling with an incensed look on her face.

As soon as she arrived on the scene, she immediately flipped a hand over to produce a red badge, which she closed her fingers around forcefully, and the badge was instantly crushed into pieces.

A pained look appeared in the golden beetle's eyes as it threw up a small mouthful of golden blood, but aside from that, it remained largely unaffected.

Qu Ling faltered slightly upon seeing this, while the golden beetle flew over to Han Li's side as it scoffed, "Did you really think that you could control me with a mere spirit subjugation badge? How naive are you!"

Qu Ling looked back and forth between Han Li and the golden beetle for a moment, then said in a cold voice, "So you must be the former owner of this Gold Devouring Immortal."

Indeed, the golden beetle was none other than Jin Tong, the Gold Devouring Immortal that Han Li had lost during his first foray into the Immortal Realm.

"I'll keep her occupied, you find a way to get out of here!" Jin Tong said to Han Li, and its body swelled drastically in size amid a flash of golden light as it pounced at Qu Ling.

Han Li took a glance at Jin Tong with mixed emotions in his eyes, then turned and continued to fly straight ahead.

"You're not getting away!" Qu Ling yelled as she pointed a finger at Jin Tong, releasing a streak of white light that contained the white rope immortal treasure from before.

The white rope vanished into thin air in a flash, then abruptly re-emerged an instant later right next to Jin Tong before tying it up in the blink of an eye.

Jin Tong was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, but instead of immediately dealing with Jin Tong, Qu Ling began to make a hand seal, and all of the gray shadows within the spirit domain quickly transformed into balls of gray flames.

All of a sudden, the entire spirit domain had been transformed into a sea of gray fire.

A vicious gleam then flashed through Qu Ling's eyes, and a vast expanse of gray flames surged toward Han Li at her behest.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, numerous streaks of bright golden light suddenly flashed past him from the side, tearing straight through the nearby gray flames.

Immediately thereafter, Jin Tong appeared in front of him, clutching the remnants of a torn white rope in its mouth.

"You thought this little string would be enough to keep me tied up?" Jin Tong scoffed as it chewed on the white rope a few times before swallowing it.

In the face of its peerlessly sharp mandibles, that immortal treasure may as well have been made out of tofu.

Qu Ling's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong's aura was fluctuating drastically in a very strange and unstable display.

The fury in Qu Ling's eyes became even more pronounced as veins began to bulge on her forehead.

At this point, it had already become apparent to her that Jin Tong had been hiding its true power this entire time.

Han Li took a long glance at Jin Tong, then adopted his Giant Golden Mountain Ape form, transforming into a giant golden ape in the blink of an eye before flying onward.

He had discovered that while this spirit domain severely restricted one's cultivation base, the impact that it had on one's physical prowess was actually quite minimal.

In his Giant Mountain Ape form, Han Li's entire body was brimming with primal power, and he was able to advance through the air far more quickly, reaching the edge of the spirit domain in the blink of an eye.

Qu Ling's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she hurriedly pointed a finger forward.

A streak of light shot out of her fingertip before vanishing into the edge of the spirit domain as fast as lightning.

The gray light on the edge of the spirit domain instantly began to flash erratically, following which a gray cloud emerged, giving off formidable law power fluctuations.

In the blink of an eye, the entire spirit domain had transformed into an independent space.

A dull thump rang out as Han Li crashed straight into the gray cloud, only to be repelled as if he had run into a giant sponge.

His expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that vanished into the body of the giant azure dragon.

The azure dragon let loose a long draconic roar, and it reverted back into a giant azure sword.

Han Li grabbed onto the hilt of the sword with both hands, then swung it viciously into the gray cloud, causing it to ripple and tremble violently, but it remained resilient.

"You're a fool if you think you can escape from my spirit domain!" Qu Ling chuckled coldly upon seeing this, and she quickly made a hand seal, upon which the gray flames within the spirit domain instantly converged toward Han Li and Jin Tong.

As a result, the gray flames around them instantly became several times denser, turning from gray to black.

A burst of law powers that were several times more formidable than before surged out of the black flames before sweeping toward Han Li, instantly shattering the time law powers around him to swallow up his entire body.

Han Li's expression instantly changed drastically as his golden fur quickly began to lose its luster, and his enormous ape body was also rapidly becoming depleted and wizened. At the same time, his immortal spiritual power circulation was slowed down drastically, and a sense of feebleness spread through his entire body.

Not only that, but a multitude of illusions had surfaced in his mind, and a burst of violent destructive intent welled up in his heart, as if he were being plagued by inner demons.

Han Li was quite alarmed by this, and he frantically tried to channel his cultivation arts and his time law powers to suppress the wild urges that were welling up in his heart, but it was a completely futile task.

Hints of red light were appearing in his eyes, and they were rapidly spreading, slowly filling the entirety of his eyes.

A hint of urgency flashed through Jin Tong's eyes upon seeing this, and it was just about to do something when the black flames around it transformed into a series of fiery black dragons that swept toward it from all directions.

In the next instant, Qu Ling appeared directly in front of it in a flash, blocking its path as she sneered, "Do you want to go save your former owner? Keep dreaming! You're in my spirit domain right now, so you have to do as I say!"

Jin Tong gave a cold harrumph as bright golden light erupted out of its body, and streaks of sword qi surged forth in all directions, instantly shredding all of the surrounding fiery black dragons.

Not only that, but the streaks of golden sword qi began to swirl to form a golden vortex, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that devoured much of the nearby black flames.

Immediately thereafter, Jin Tong pounced directly at Qu Ling, and two huge streaks of translucent light, both of which were around 1,000 feet in length, were sent hurtling toward Qu Ling from either side, slicing through all of the black flames in their path with ease.

"Which is it? Are you going to face me or are you going to save your former master?" Qu Ling chuckled as she made a rapid string of hand seals, and bursts of black flames converged from all directions to form two lines of black light in a flash.

Bursts of tremendous law power fluctuations surged out of the two black lines, and they flew through the air at Qu Ling's behest to clash against the two oncoming streaks of translucent light.

A pair of dull thumps rang out as the black lines and the streaks of translucent light dissipated in unison.

"If he can't even deal with something like this, then he's not worthy of being my master. All I can do to help him is keep you occupied so you can't attack him directly. If he still can't escape from this spirit domain, then he's far too weak and simply deserves to die," Jin Tong said in an indifferent voice as it swept its pair of front legs through the air once again, sending two more streaks of translucent light hurtling toward Qu Ling.

Qu Ling harrumphed coldly as she raised her arms, and bursts of black flames shot forth to oppose the streaks of translucent light.

Meanwhile, the red coloration in Han Li's eyes was becoming more and more pronounced, and his eyes were about to turn completely red.

Right at this moment, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in his body abruptly shuddered, following which thick arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his body amid a deafening thunderclap that resembled the roar of a scorned primordial beast.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's entire body was completely encompassed within a sea of golden lightning, and an aura of righteousness erupted out of the Divine Devilbane Lightning before surging into his mind.

The insanity that clouded his mind instantly faded, while much of the red coloration in his eyes also receded.

He immediately pounced on this opportunity as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis once again.

Perhaps it was due to the fact that it was situated in the spirit domain, but on this occasion, the Mantra Treasured Axis didn't release the same golden ripples as it always had in the past.

Bursts of time law powers surged out of the axis to envelop Han Li's entire body, acting as another barrier against the invasive law powers in the spirit domain.

At the same time, he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, and a cool and refreshing sensation instantly welled up in his mind.

The insanity and feebleness that had plagued his mind and body quickly receded, and his immortal spiritual power circulation also returned to normal.

A hint of incredulity appeared in Qu Ling's eyes upon seeing this, and she exclaimed, "How could this be..."

She then gave a cold harrumph before pointing a finger at Han Li, and a burst of black flames was instantly sent flying his way, transforming into a black arrow mid-flight.

However, the black arrow wasn't able to get very far before it crashed into a streak of translucent light, upon which both exploded violently.

"You want to switch opponents all of a sudden? I think you should stick with me," Jin Tong chortled as it positioned itself directly in front of Qu Ling.

Meanwhile, Han Li paid no heed to the battle taking place in the distance as he cast his gaze toward the gray cloud up ahead, and a fierce look flashed through his eyes as he opened his mouth to release three bursts of azure light, which surged into the silver bell, the tusk sword, and the black flag around him.

The three immortal treasures instantly shuddered in unison, and the light radiating from them brightened by severalfold, to the point that it was impossible to look directly at them.

"Go!" Han Li yelled, and the three immortal treasures short forth as three streaks of dazzling light before striking the gray cloud with tremendous force.

As soon as the three immortal treasures came into contact with the gray cloud, they immediately exploded into three balls of light, one silver and two black.

The gray cloud also shuddered violently, as did the entire spirit domain, while a large section of the surrounding black flames were swept away.

Chapter 455: A Little Girl

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The detonation of three immortal treasures at once had worn down the gray cloud significantly, but it still wasn't entirely wiped out.

Qu Ling was furious as she observed the unfolding situation from afar, but she was unable to free herself from her battle against Jin Tong, so she could only watch as Han Li continued to chip away at her spirit domain.

Right at this moment, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon that black inkstone immortal treasure that he had obtained from Tao Yu.

He tossed the black inkstone forward while making a hand seal, and a burst of piercing black light interspersed with formidable law power fluctuations instantly surged out of the inkstone.

The law powers imbued within this inkstone were far superior to that of the three previous immortal treasures, and even though Han Li hadn't been able to completely refine the treasure, he still had sufficient control over it to trigger its self-detonation.

An alarmed look appeared on Qu Ling's face as she sensed the formidable aura emanating from the black inkstone, and she immediately opened her mouth to release a burst of silver liquid, which fused into the black flames around her in a flash.

The surrounding black flames instantly swelled to exert more pressure on Jin Tong, and at the same time, Qu Ling swept a sleeve through the air to summon a green gourd amid a flash of green light.

An indescribably enormous aura instantly erupted forth as soon as the gourd emerged, and Han Li was quite stunned upon sensing this aura, but continued with what he was doing without pause.

The black light radiating from the inkstone became brighter and brighter, and it was beginning to flash erratically.

Right at this moment, he opened his mouth to expel a mouthful of blood, which vanished into the black inkstone in a flash, and the inkstone hurtled directly toward the gray cloud while glowing like a radiant black sun.

Qu Ling gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and she pointed a finger at the green gourd, which released a burst of green light that swept toward the black inkstone at an incredible speed.

Unfortunately, she was too late.

In the instant that the burst of green light reached the black inkstone, the latter exploded violently into an eruption of black light and countless black runes. A terrifying aura surged through the area before fading away an instant later, and the gray cloud was worn down even further, trembling violently as a series of cracks appeared within it.

However, this spirit domain was truly extremely resilient, and it was still just barely able to hold itself together.

An urgent look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to expel another mouthful of blood, this time into his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

The sword instantly began to glow radiantly as it swept viciously toward the gray cloud, while Qu Ling responded by making a hand seal, and the burst of green light released by the green gourd circled around to wrap itself around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

"Look out! That gourd of hers is a Profound Heavenly Treasure that can capture immortal treasures by force!" Jin Tong warned through voice transmission.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but it was too late for him to do anything.

As soon as the burst of green light wrapped itself around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, the latter was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, and Han Li's spiritual connection with it was also severed.

A cold sneer appeared on Qu Ling's face as she made another hand seal, and the green light wrapped around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword instantly brightened even further, while the giant sword shrank down rapidly before flying toward her.

Han Li fought the instinctive urge to recover his flying sword as he swept a sleeve through the air, and yet another giant azure sword emerged before him amid a flash of azure light.

Thick arcs of golden lightning erupted out of its blade, and the aura that it was giving off was no less formidable than that of the previous sword.

A stunned look appeared on Qu Ling's face upon seeing this.

There was a cooldown period that had to pass before she could use the green gourd to unleash another burst of green light, so there was nothing that she could do.

Right at this moment, Han Li swept his other sleeve through the air to summon his Heavy Water True Axis, which instantly began revolving rapidly, sending bursts of tremendous force erupting in all directions and causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

Immediately thereafter, he cast a pair of incantation seals into the two treasures, and the light radiating from them brightened significantly as they swooped toward the gray cloud up ahead in unison.

At the same time, Daoist Xie shot out of Han Li's body in its giant crab from amid a flash of golden lightning.

Bright golden lightning was surging over its entire body, and it swept its pair of massive pincers through the air to strike the gray cloud like a pair of peerlessly sharp giant blades.

The gray cloud was already on its last legs, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as a huge hole was finally blasted through it.

After unleashing that attack, the golden light on Daoist Xie's body rapidly dimmed, indicating that it had already used up all of its Immortal Origin Stones.

It flew back into Han Li's body as a streak of golden light, while Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, sweeping up his giant azure sword and Heavy Water True Axis before flying through the hole in the gray cloud.

He was flying extremely fast, and he just so happened to be traveling downward, so he was unable to arrest his momentum and crashed straight into the ground, creating a massive crater beneath himself.

He immediately rose to his feet and took a quick glance at his surroundings before preparing to flee.

Even though he had escaped from the spirit domain, his immortal spiritual power were already completely depleted, so he was unfit for further battle.

Right at this moment, his Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly emerged on its own, and as soon as it appeared, it began to revolve rapidly while releasing dazzling golden light, as was the case with the time law thread on the axis.

The golden gate up ahead also began to glow radiantly, and both the axis and the gate also began buzzing audibly, as if they were resonating with one another.

All of a sudden, the time law thread on the Mantra Treasured Axis shot through the air before vanishing into the golden gate in a flash.

A golden ring design instantly appeared on the golden gate, and a burst of dazzling golden light flew out from within before encompassing Han Li's entire body.

Han Li immediately felt a burst of immense yet gentle force descend upon him, rendering him largely immobilized.

He was naturally quite startled by this, and he raised his head with great difficulty to cast his gaze toward the gate of the golden palace, upon which he was surprised to discover that Lu Yuqing was standing beside the gate.

She was being pursued by that young Primordial Fei Beast earlier, but she had somehow returned to this place.

There was a stunned look on her face as well, and she was also looking back at Han Li with her mouth slightly agape.

Right at this moment, a burst of rumbling rang out from the gray spirit domain up above, and a streak of golden light flew out from within before transforming into Jin Tong.

At this moment, its body was riddled with gashes, and there was a weary look in its golden eyes.

Not far away, Qu Ling also appeared amid a flash of silver light.

She had already taken in the situation that was unfolding down below, and a furious look appeared on her face as she swept a sleeve through the air, upon which the gray throne reappeared before immediately fusing into the gray spirit domain above her.

The gray spirit domain instantly began to shrink rapidly as if it were collapsing in on itself, shrinking to only several hundred feet in size in the blink of an eye, and its color had also become extremely dark.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of the spirit domain, causing the nearby air to tremble and quiver, while gusts of ferocious wind were sent sweeping in all directions.

At the same time, an enormous gray dragon head projection appeared within the spirit domain. It had an extremely menacing appearance and was riddled with sharp spikes, but its eyes were completely indifferent and emotionless.

Right as Han Li's gaze fell upon the gray dragon head, it was also looking directly at him, and an indescribable sense of foreboding instantly welled up in his heart.

Right at this moment, the gray dragon head opened its mouth, and three bursts of light of different colors appeared within its maw, namely gray, black, and white.

Each burst of light contained tremendous law powers that were completely different from one another, yet were able to coexist in perfect harmony.

The gray dragon head let loose an earth-shattering roar, following which a thick pillar of three-colored light erupted forth, hurtling directly toward Han Li at an incredible speed.

At this moment, Han Li was completely immobilized, so he could only look on helplessly as the pillar of three-colored light approached him at lightning speed.

In this dire situation, a streak of golden light suddenly flashed through the air before him, and a little girl appeared in front of him without any warning.

The little girl was none other than Jin Tong, and it appeared that it had managed to attain a human form during the time that it had been separated from Han Li. The little girl appeared to be around eight or nine years of age, and her head of golden hair and porcelain-like features gave her a very adorable appearance.

At this moment, she was wearing a suit of intricate golden armor, and there was a golden gleam in her bright black pupils, but two lines of golden blood were trickling down from the corners of her lips, and her aura had become significantly weaker than before.

The little girl wore a grim expression as she raised her delicate arms, which instantly took on a golden coloration, as if they had been forged out of gold.

She then gritted her teeth as she swept her little hands through the air, and her arms instantly exploded, transforming into two thick streaks of translucent light that were each over 10,000 feet in length.

There were countless golden runes flashing over the two streaks of translucent light, and they fused as one in a flash to form a thin line.

A burst of overwhelmingly formidable law power fluctuations surged out of the thin thread, causing the nearby space to quake violently as it swept toward the pillar of three-colored light.

"Jin Tong!" Han Li called out as a series of mixed emotions surfaced in his eyes.

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling suddenly rang out from the gate of the golden palace, and it opened up ever so slightly as a peculiar aura emerged from within.

The golden light around Han Li's body instantly brightened before dragging him through the gate of the palace in a flash.

Chapter 456: Small City

Han Li felt as if he had been plunged into a cloud of gray mist, and all of a sudden, the ground gave away beneath his feet, causing him to stumble forward involuntarily, only to land back on a solid surface an instant later.

He felt as if he had passed through some type of smoky illusion, and before he knew it, he was in another space.

He massaged his slightly sore temples as his blurry vision slowly recovered, and only then was able to see the moss-covered ground beneath his feet.

He quickly looked around to find that he was the one here, and that none of Jin Tong, Lu Yuqing, or Qu Ling had managed to follow him in here. His brows furrowed slightly as he heaved a faint sigh.

Never had he imagined that he would reunite with Jin Tong under these circumstances. Even though there hadn't been many words exchanged between them, Jin Tong had swooped in to save his life without any regard for its own safety, and that was very touching to Han Li.

After all, ever since he had come to the True Immortal, he had never had a genuine connection with anyone and was constantly having to watch his back. The last person that had felt true affection and concern for him had been Liu Le'er back in the Spirit Domain Realm.

Of course, the fact that he had always regarded Jin Tong as half a child of his also had something to do with this.

It was during the time they had been separated, Jin Tong had become significantly more powerful than before, allowing it to oppose a late-Golden Immortal cultivator for such a long time. However, Han Li knew that it was definitely no match for Qu Ling, considering her exceptional mastery over law powers, as well as her array of formidable treasures, including that peculiar Profound Heavenly Gourd.

At the moment, all he could do was pray that Jin Tong could somehow find safety, even if it meant having to temporarily submit to Qu Ling. Judging from what he had seen earlier, it seemed that Qu Ling had taken Jin Tong under her wing as a spirit pet.

If something were to happen to Jin Tong, then once he reached the Golden Immortal Stage, he would be sure to go after Qu Ling and make her pay the price.

As for Lu Yuqing, at some point, he had developed the impression that something was rather strange about her, but he couldn't put his finger on exactly what it was.

Having said that, she was only an acquaintance of his, and they had entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor as collaborative partners, so he didn't feel any obligation to her. While it was true that she had run into Qu Ling because she was with him, she was the one who had chosen to follow him in the first place, so she had to accept the risks that came with such a decision.

Now that he had been sucked into the place somehow, she would just have to deal with Qu Ling's wrath on her own.

Han Li cast these thoughts aside as he swept his gaze over the surrounding area.

In doing so, he discovered that he was standing in an old courtyard, surrounded by dilapidated walls and collapsed buildings that were overgrown with moss and weeds.

However, as he cast his gaze toward the rear section of the courtyard, a hint of befuddlement appeared in his eyes.

Hovering in the air above the upper right corner of a building in that direction was a roof tile, which was frozen in the process of blowing up into pieces. It was as if it were being held in place by some type of invisible form, and the moment of its destruction had been forever immortalized.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes while also releasing his spiritual sense to examine the roof tile, and a few moments later, he sprang up into the air before landing on the roof of the building.

There, he reached out to pluck a piece of the hovering roof tile out of mid-air, while the rest of the roof tile fragments remained in their original positions, completely unaffected.

Han Li was rather bewildered and intrigued by this, and he cast his gaze out of the courtyard to find more sets of ruins in all directions, spreading as far as the eyes could see.

Among these collapsed buildings, similar peculiar scenes as this hovering roof tile could be seen everywhere. All of those destroyed buildings and pavilions had been shattered into countless pieces, but not even a single fragment had fallen onto the ground. It was as if time had stopped in the instant that they were destroyed, leaving them trapped in their perpetual purgatory.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li slowly closed his eyes before releasing his vast spiritual sense over the surrounding area.

In contrast with that barren red area from before, his spiritual sense wasn't restricted at all here.

However, only a few moments had passed before his eyes suddenly sprang open, and the blue light in his pupils faded as a peculiar look appeared on his face.

It seemed that by examining his surroundings, he had only become more perplexed.

As it turned out, this area was far smaller than he had anticipated. He had only just released his spiritual sense slightly, and it had already filled this entire space, which only had a radius of several dozen kilometers.

The entire space was surrounded in all directions by spatial walls, but theoretically speaking, the fact that he was able to enter this place meant that it wasn't completely isolated from the outside world.

At the very least, there had to be some fragile spots in the space here, and if he could track down those spots, then he would be able to break through the spatial walls to return to the outside world if such a need ever arose.

However, through his spiritual sense examination, he wasn't able to identify any weak points in the space here for him to target.

After taking a moment to contemplate how to proceed, Han Li made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

Following the emergence of the axis, the dozen or so active Time Dao Runes on its surface lit up one after another, and the Eye of Truth at its center began to scour the surrounding area while releasing a beam of golden light.

Han Li was unable to find any way out using his spiritual sense, so he had no choice but to turn to his Eye of Truth.

He flew up into the air, then turned his gaze to the center of the courtyard that he had first appeared in through the perspective of the Eye of Truth, but even under the scrutiny of the beam of golden light, the courtyard didn't display any abnormalities.

Han Li's gaze slowly roamed over the ground to the stone table in the courtyard, then to the walls, the dead trees, and the buildings, but he wasn't able to find anything worthy of note.

However, as the gaze of the Eye of Truth fell upon that room with the hovering roof tile above it, a burst of golden light suddenly erupted out of the roof of the building, following which it was quickly restored to its original state, as if it had been rebuilt anew.

Han Li was very surprised to see this.

Could it be that this building contains time law powers?

Before he had a chance to approach the building for a closer examination, the projection of the repaired building began to flash and waver in an unstable fashion.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis as he descended in front of the building, and he took some time to examine the outside of the building before entering it and conducting a thorough search, but he wasn't able to find anything that contained time law powers.

How strange... Could it be that the time law powers here are too sparse to be detectable? Surely that's not the case...

After some contemplation, he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis once again, then rose up into the air and left this courtyard to fly toward the other areas in this space.

Looking down from above, he could see that even though all of the buildings here were quite dilapidated, the general layout was quite orderly and well-structured. The layout of this place was very similar to that of the average mortal city, and Han Li began to do some exploring.

He started from the eastern side of the city and slowly made his way westward, making sure to examine all of the buildings that seemed to have been frozen in time along the way. Whenever he gazed upon them through his Eye of Truth, those buildings would present projections of back when they were whole, but those projections were also quite blurry and unstable.

It was as if faint time law fluctuations permeated throughout this entire city, but only to a very faint degree that was completely undetectable.

It took Han Li only less than half a day to explore the entire city, but he wasn't able to discover anything.

As night approached, the sun began to set.

In the southern part of the city, there stood a nine-story black wooden pagoda in a garden that was overrun with weeds. The pagoda had many scorch marks on its surface, and it was tilted severely to one side, looking as if it could collapse at any moment.

Han Li was standing on the black roof tiles atop the pagoda's roof with one hand resting on the tip of the pagoda as he cast his gaze toward the setting sun in the distance.

Standing beside him was the yellow-robed Daoist Xie with a neutral expression on its face.

"Can you see anything special about the layout of this city, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Not at all. At the very least, on the surface, it seems to only be following the standard protocol in the way normal cities are constructed. As for whether there are some special hidden mechanisms, it's impossible to tell just by looking," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of its head.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "In that case, can I trouble you to examine this place to see if there are any hidden mechanisms or arrays?"

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then vanished from the top of the wooden pagoda in a flash.

As the light of the dying sun gradually faded, Han Li abruptly shot through the air as a streak of azure light.

However, a resounding thump rang out in the air just a moment later, and Han Li was repelled back through the air like a cannonball, having just crashed into an invisible barrier.

However, as soon as he landed on the ground, a burst of azure light instantly emerged over his body as he shot straight toward another direction.

Several days passed by in a flash.

In this ruined city was a private garden, within which was a lush forest. The forest was littered with numerous strange rocks, each of which was as tall as a grown man. These rocks were quite dark in coloration, and they were covered in layers of slick moss.

Two figures were making their way side by side toward the center of the forest down a winding path.

"There are quite a few restrictions and secret chambers in the city, but barely any of them are worthy of further examination. This is the only place that I feel is worthy of note. At the very least, the array here stands out from the rest," Daoist Xie said while leading the way.

"In that case, there's probably a good chance that this is the exit of this secret area," Han Li replied as a hopeful look appeared in his eyes.

Chapter 457: Concerns

Daoist Xie made his way down the small path until it arrived at a strange rock that resembled a hunched-over old ape, where it drew to a halt and said, "Come and take a look at what this is, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he hurried over to the strange rock, then wiped a hand over it before conducting a careful examination.

A hesitant look appeared on his face as he asked, "Could this be... a Primordial Form Rock?"

"That's exactly right," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"No wonder I wasn't able to detect any array fluctuations when I was examining this place with my spiritual sense. Having said that, I didn't think that the Primordial Form Rock's concealment effect would be this potent," Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

"These Primordial Form Rocks alone wouldn't have been enough to keep you from detecting this array, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie said.

"Are you saying there's something else here?" Han Li asked with an intrigued expression.

Daoist Xie offered no reply as it led Han Li deeper into the dense forest, and the two of them arrived in an open and spacious area.

Upon entering this area, Han Li discovered that the ground was entirely charred black, and the shrubs that used to grow here had been scorched into ashes, revealing a millstone-sized stone platform.

The surface of the platform had also been scorched black, and as a result, all of the engravings on its surface had become unrecognizable.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a gentle breeze that brushed away the dirt and soot on the stone platform to reveal what was underneath, but that only seemed to present more questions than answers for him.

"What is this thing?"

There were nine strange flower-petal-like designs engraved onto the stone platform, and they were assembled together to form what appeared to be a massive flower.

There were also many special and complex runes within the flower petals, and Daoist Xie explained, "If I'm not mistaken, this appears to be an extremely advanced dream concealment restriction that can work in conjunction with Primordial Form Rocks to completely conceal the auras of many treasures and arrays."

"If you're familiar with this type of restriction, then I'm sure you must have a way of unraveling it, right?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Instead of providing a direct answer to Han Li's question, Daoist Xie said, "Please take a look at the center of this restriction, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li did as he was instructed, but there didn't appear to be anything there, and his brows furrowed slightly in befuddlement as he turned to Daoist Xie.

"That is where the stamen of the flower is supposed to be, but for some reason, it's already been completely destroyed," Daoist Xie explained.

Han Li conducted a closer examination upon hearing this, and only then did he discover that there were indeed some signs of damage there.

"That shouldn't be an issue, right? We should be able to adapt accordingly to unravel the restriction. Could it be that there's some other problem?" Han Li asked.

"Have you heard of the concept of limitless dreams, Fellow Daoist Han? Dream concealment restrictions of this nature are extremely diverse and varied. Even if the slightest alteration is made to such a restriction, the way to unravel it will become completely different. Even though I'm familiar with this type of restriction, I have no idea how to unravel it in its current state," Daoist Xie explained with a shake of its head.

"In that case, we'll just have to resort to brute force and destroy this restriction," Han Li concluded after some contemplation.

"Well, about that... You can give that a try, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li could tell from the peculiar look on Daoist Xie's face that this wasn't going to be a simple matter, but he still decided to make an attempt as he adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form amid a flash of golden light.

The profound acupoints on his body then lit up as he let loose a low roar before raising a massive fist and slamming it heavily down onto the stone platform.

The entire stone platform shuddered violently as ferocious shockwaves erupted through the air in all directions, razing everything within a radius of several thousand feet to the ground before gradually subsiding.

At the same time, a burst of golden light also appeared on the inscriptions on the stone platform, and a series of vine-like golden liens spread over the stone platform before extending into the forest like a cobweb.

In his Giant Mountain Ape form, Han Li had a much clearer view of his surroundings thanks to his enormous stature, and he could see similar golden lines spreading over the entire secret area, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

"By my estimates, one would have to be at least at the Golden Immortal Stage for them to have a chance at breaking this restriction by force. Even an all-out attack from me in my current state won't be enough to get the job done," Daoist Xie said.

"Even if that were possible, we most won't be able to do it. This restriction is connected to this entire secret area, so if we were to destroy it by force, the entire secret area would most likely collapse, and that would be catastrophic for us," Han Li said as he quickly reverted back to his human form.

"That's right," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he walked a lap around the stone platform, and a thought suddenly occurred to him as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis.

The Eye of Truth at the center of the axis slowly opened, then cast its gaze toward the stone platform, releasing a beam of golden light out of its pupil.

As the beam of golden light shone down upon the stone platform, all of the remaining char and soot on its surface instantly receded, restoring it to a pristine state.

A burst of murky light also appeared at the center of the restriction, and a series of lines began to gradually emerge, forming an extremely complex stamen design.

Right as Han Li was about to take a closer look, the projection of the stamen suddenly began to vibrate rapidly in an extremely unstable manner.

Han Li was struck by a rush of dizziness from the jarring sight, and he had no choice but to avert his gaze and withdraw his Mantra Treasured Axis.

"Did you see anything?" Daoist Xie asked.

"This secret area is truly a very strange place. Many of the ordinary-looking things here are imbued with time law powers, but only to an extremely faint degree. Whenever I try to examine them with my Eye of Truth, all I end up seeing is a jumbled blur, and this stone platform is no exception," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Your Mantra Treasured Axis isn't in its peak condition right now. Perhaps once it recovers all of its Time Dao Runes, you'll be able to see the restriction more clearly," Daoist Xie suggested.

"I've already considered that, but the problem is that it would take too much time to wait for the Mantra Treasured Axis to return to the peak of its powers. The Infernal Frost Immortal Manor is only open for a limited time, and once the exit closes, who knows when the immortal manor will be open again?"

Han Li's top priority at the moment was to find a way to get out of this place. Of course, if he did manage to find a way out, then he would also be open to the idea of staying here for some time. After all, he didn't know what had happened outside during the few days that he had been trapped in this place, but he presumed that Qu Ling wouldn’t waste much time waiting for him.

"You have a near-limitless lifespan, so why concern yourself with such matters? The world's origin qi here is no less abundant than anywhere else in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so you could easily just cultivate here and wait for the next time the immortal manor is opened," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

Having made an enemy out of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, he was not in a very good situation. Furthermore, he was now being targeted by Qu Ling as well, and there was also a chance that Feng Tiandu would come after him eventually, so for him, the Northern Glacial Immortal Region was fraught with peril.

In comparison, it was indeed safer to stay in this secret area.

However, Han Li's concerns still lingered as he said, "That may be true, but there's no telling what could happen in this secret area once the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor closes. If things take a turn for the worse, we may end up in an even worse situation than having to face Qu Ling again."

What he didn't mention was that if he were to be trapped in this secret area, even for hundreds of thousands of years, perhaps nothing would happen to him, but drastic changes would be taking place in the outside world. At the moment, Jin Tong was in direct peril of being struck down by Qu Ling, and there were many more people important to Han Li that Qu Ling could potentially go after.

"In any case, we won't be able to leave this place right away, so I suggest you give it some time so that your Mantra Treasured Axis can recover. Perhap it won't take too long before you'll be able to get a clearer look at this restriction," Daoist Xie said.

"I suppose that's all we can do for now," Han Li replied with a nod.

......

Several more days passed by in the blink of an eye.

A giant plaza with a radius of several thousand feet had appeared at the center of the ruined city.

The central area of the plaza was paved with white stone slabs, while the edges were covered in newly unearthed reddish-brown mud that was interspersed with many fragments of broken tiles, rocks, and wooden frames.

It was clear that the plaza had only been recently constructed, and it was riddled with a series of extremely deep rifts that were connected together to form a very complex array.

The array was called the Great Universe Star Gathering Array, and it had been included at the end of the second half of the Great Universe Origin Arts. It was an array that could assist one in cultivating the Great Universe Origin Arts, and it was far superior to the Star Gathering Array that Han Li had used in the past. Even the new and improved Star Gathering Array that Han Li had personally modified couldn't hold a candle to this array.

The Great Universe Star Gathering Array had a total of 81 star points distributed evenly around the array, and each star point could fit a Starheaven Stone, which could help a cultivator absorb starpower at a faster rate.

By Han Li's estimates, if he had access to this array from the very beginning, then the time it would've taken him to get to this point in the Great Universe Origin Arts would've been reduced by at least half. However, he would also require a sufficient number of Starheaven Stones, and the pain he would've had to endure would've also been at least twice as excruciating.

Chapter 458: 500 Years

Night fell, and countless stars appeared in the pitch black sky up above.

Han Li was seated at the center of the white stone plaza with his legs crossed, looking up at the sky, and his eyes were like a pair of mirrors that could reflect the starlight shining down from above.

It would take a year for each of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis to recover, so a full recovery was going to take a very long time.

Seeing as he was unable to find any alternative ways out of this predicament, he had no choice but to bide his time, and during this time, he was planning to continue his cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts. In doing so, he would be able to open more profound acupoints, which should assist him in a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage.

With a casual toss, a burst of blue light flew out of his hand, then split up into several dozen streaks of light, each of which fell into the one of the 81 star points around the array with unerring accuracy.

As soon as these Starheaven Stones fell into place, they immediately began to radiate dazzling starlight that illuminated the entire plaza.

At the same time, Han Li opened his mouth to release his Seven Bright Star Rings, and they circled around in the air before spreading out across the night sky.

These Seven Bright Star Rings weren't a part of the array, but they were also quite beneficial when it came to gathering starpower, so Han Li naturally wasn't going to neglect them.

He began to make a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and the entire array began to glow with radiant starlight, which gradually expanded to encompass the entire plaza bit by bit.

Han Li continued to look up at the night sky, and he felt as if the distance between himself and the night sky were rapidly shrinking. The stars that had appeared incredibly tiny to him in the past were becoming larger and larger, and they were also glowing brighter and brighter.

Every single star resembled a miniature sun that was blinding to behold, and if an outside observer were present, they would be stunned to discover that the black pupils in Han Li's eyes had disappeared, and the entirety of his eyes were filled with radiant white starlight.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and a vast expanse of starlight converged in the sky, forming over 100 pillars of white light that shone down onto the entire secret area from the night sky above.

The seven pillars of light passing down through the Seven Bright Star Rings appeared particularly thick and substantial.

The plaza that the Great Universe Star Gathering Array was situated on trembled violently as each of the Starheaven Stones released a pillar of white light that hurtled directly toward Han Li at the center of the array.

The 81 pillars of starlight collectively struck Han Li with a resounding boom, and a muffled groan immediately escaped his lips, which a string of cracks and pops rang out incessantly from all of the joints in his body.

His 18 profound acupoints also lit up in unison, immediately following which each of them formed a miniature vortex that sucked in the vast expanse of starlight converging toward him.

The enormous influx of starpower instantly struck Han Li with a bloated sensation in his profound acupoints, as if he had already had a hearty meal, yet was being forced to eat more, and it was not a good feeling.

A pained look flashed through his eyes as he gritted his teeth tightly, enduring the pain as his profound acupoints continued to devour starlight.

Right at this moment, the array beneath him suddenly shuddered violently, and a spatial vortex emerged under him. A burst of suction force instantly surged out of the vortex, sucking in the white starlight all over the entire plaza and drawing it toward Han Li.

All of the pillars of white light shining down from the heavens were sucked in by the vortex, causing them to veer off their original trajectories and descend toward Han Li instead.

Just a moment ago, the Great Universe Star Gathering Array resembled a vast sea formed by over 100 cascading waterfalls, while Han Li was like a small raft drifting over the sea in relative safety and comfort, but the situation was completely different now.

With all of the pillars of starlight shining down upon him at once, the influx of starpower was countless times more immense than before, and a burst of unbearably tremendous force crashed down upon him, causing him to bend forward involuntarily, to the point that he was almost flattened against the ground.

Strands of translucent starlight were piercing into every single one of his pores, and his robes were instantly soaked with blood.

However, the blood would only flow for an instant before it was evaporated into nothingness by the starlight.

Han Li's teeth were gritted tightly as a guttural snarl rang out deep within his throat. His hands were pressed firmly into knees, and veins were bulging on his arms as he struggled to push himself back into an upright posture.

His skin had already become completely translucent thanks to the starlight flowing into his body, and even through his robe, one could see all of his bones and meridians.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of light, which instantly transformed into a massive screen that positioned itself above his head.

The screen was a transparent black color with a series of glittering and translucent blue beads embedded onto its surface, giving it the appearance of a miniature night sky. This was the very same screen that he had taken from the palace in which the Great Universe Origin Arts had been hidden.

With all of the pillars of starlight shining down upon it, the blue beads on the screen began to radiate dazzling starlight, projecting a miniature starry sky.

At the same time, the entire screen became more and more transparent until it transformed into a black veil-like light barrier that encompassed Han Li's entire body.

The light barrier was rippling incessantly under the vast volume of starlight shining down upon it, but it was able to afford Han Li some protection and alleviate some of hte pressure weighing down upon him.

As a result, he was able to catch his breath, and he made a hand seal as he closed his eyes to focus entirely on the absorption of starpower.

......

The days passed by one after another in a blur.

At night, Han Li would draw starpower into his body from the night sky, while during the day, he would continue to cultivate the Great Universe Origin Arts using the Starheaven Stones, and he did this without pause every single day.

During the first few years, Han Li would recover an additional Time Dao Rune every single year, following which he would take a break from his cultivation and travel to that garden to examine the dream concealment restriction on the stone platform, but he was unable to make any progress.

After that, he knew that the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor had to have already closed a long time ago, but nothing had changed in this secret realm. This instilled within him a sense of reassurance, allowing him to focus fully on his cultivation, and it didn't take long before he opened his 19th profound acupoint.

His cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts wasn't exactly all smooth sailing from there, but there were no major obstacles, either, and he slowly became immersed in the process, forgetting the passage of time.

500 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

On this night, pillars of starlight were shining down from the heavens as usual, illuminating the entire ruined city with their resplendent white radiance.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed at the center of the plaza, completely enveloped by starlight, and his entire body looked as translucent as if it had been carved out of jade.

His long hair trailed down his back, and it had already turned from its former black color to a glittering and translucent silver color.

At this moment, there were strands of starlight gathering at a certain point on his back, and a brand new profound acupoint was taking shape.

With that, the 36th profound acupoint was formed, and his cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts was complete!

A faint crack rang out as the black screen that had been hanging above Han Li this entire time suddenly disintegrated. At the same time, the pillars of starlight shining down from above also slowly dimmed before fading away altogether.

With that, the entire secret area was also plunged into darkness.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes as he rose to his feet, and his entire body was encompassed within his True Extreme Film, which was looking denser and more resilient than ever.

He raised a hand before gently clenching his fist, and a burst of light appeared in the palm of his hand, seemingly containing some type of peculiar power.

He knew that this was a sign that the starpower in his body still hadn't completely stabilized in the wake of a newly formed profound acupoint, and that his body would soon return to normal.

Despite his latest breakthrough, Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh.

He had anticipated that it would definitely take a very long time to complete his cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts, but he wasn't expecting it to take this long.

All of a sudden, he raised his head to look up at the night sky, then took a step back before throwing a punch up at the heavens.

A burst of extremely formidable force was instantly released, forming a gust of white astral wind that was visible even to the naked eye as it erupted directly upward.

A resounding boom rang out, and it was as if the entire night sky were about to be torn apart by this burst of tremendous force. This was immediately followed by a loud whooshing sound as the surrounding air surged into the area vacuum left in the wake of the force released by Han Li's fist.

The gust of white wind surged upward for several thousand feet, and only after that did it begin to gradually dissipate.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he slowly withdrew his fist.

Even though that hadn't been an all-out punch, the power unleashed was already not inferior to that of a full-force blow from back when he had only cultivated half of the Great Universe Origin Arts.

By his estimates, if he were to return to that stone platform now, he would perhaps be able to destroy it even without progressing to the Golden Immortal Stage, but if he were to do that, then this entire secret area would most likely be destroyed along with the stone platform.

The blue light radiating from Han Li's body slowly faded, and his True Extreme Film also disappeared at his behest.

At this point, he had already reached the pinnacle of the True Immortal, so the only thing that was keeping him from reaching the Golden Immortal Stage was that 36th immortal acupoint.

However, seeing as he had already attained 36 profound acupoints, opening this final immortal acupoint wasn't going to be a difficult task, so the only concern currently on his mind was the final one of the three decays, acupoint decay.

This was an unavoidable tribulation that he would have to transcend in order to reach the Golden Immortal Stage. It was said that cultivating profound acupoints and mastering law powers would help one endure this decay, but he had never witnessed or experienced this process, so he was still feeling a little uneasy.

Han Li took a deep breath, then looked up at the moon in the sky.

He wasn't planning to continue cultivating tonight, and he sprang up into the air before landing on the rooftop of a half-collapsed building.

From there, he looked up at the moon once again, and a hint of mixed emotions flashed through his eyes as he laid down onto the rooftop, then closed his eyes to rest.

Chapter 459: The Third Decay

At around noon, three days later.

Han Li reappeared on the white stone plaza, looking completely reinvigorated.

His immortal spiritual power and his spiritual sense had both been fully restored, and he swept his gaze across his surroundings, then raised a sleeve to release a bolt of golden lightning, which transformed into Daoist Xie not far away.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Han Li, and a faint smile appeared on its face as it said, "I can see that your cultivation base has advanced even further. Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Han."

"I did manage to make some progress, but we've already been in here for several centuries, and I can't help but wonder how things are going outside. Today, I'm going to make another attempt to reach the Golden Immortal Stage to see if we can leave this place a little sooner. This space may be an isolated one, but there are still many risks involved when it comes to forcing a realm open, so I'll have to trouble you to keep a lookout for me, Brother Xie," Han Li said with a smile.

"Rest assured, just go ahead and do what you need to do," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

As soon as its voice trailed off, a flash of golden lightning surged over its body, and it vanished into thin air.

Han Li sat down with his legs crossed upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, which contained three or four white jade vials and an intricate jade box.

With another sweep of his sleeve, the stopper of one of the jade vials flew off on its own, and a longan-sized golden pill flew out from within before landing on the palm of his hand.

This was none other than the Myriad Axis Pill, the pill capable of assisting even late-True Immortal cultivators in advancing their cultivation base.

Han Li picked up the pill before promptly devouring it, and it immediately disintegrated into a surge of warmth that flowed through his meridians, but compared with the intense influx of heat and pressure from the first Myriad Axis Pill that he had taken, the effects had become far milder.

One reason for this was because he had already taken so many of these pills that he had developed some tolerance to them, and the other reason was that his physical body had become significantly enhanced after his attainment of full mastery over the Great Universe Origin Arts.

His brows furrowed slightly as he made a beckoning motion, and two more Myriad Axis Pill flew out of the vial, both of which he swallowed at once.

Only after that did he close his eyes and begin to cultivate.

As he began to chant an incantation, a layer of gentle golden light surfaced to envelop his entire body, and over 10 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Throughout the 500 years that Han Li had spent cultivating the Great Universe Origin Arts and this latest passage of over a decade, the entire secret area remained completely unchanged from back when Han Li first entered this place.

The sun rose and set every day, and there were different weather conditions on display, but there was never any passage of seasons, and even the slick moss that was extremely prevalent throughout the entire secret area maintained its dark green hue perpetually.

At the edge of the city, Daoist Xie was standing on the rooftop of a three-story azure bamboo pavilion. Its yellow robes were flapping audibly around it, but it stood completely still like a statue as its gaze remained fixed firmly on the center of the city.

Right at this moment, it suddenly murmured to itself, "It's finally here..."

As soon as its voice trailed off, a resounding boom rang out from the center of the city, and the entire secret area shuddered violently as a pillar of golden light erupted into the heavens.

Layers of dark clouds converged from all directions above the white stone plaza, and it didn't take long before a vortex of dark clouds with a diameter of several dozen kilometers had taken shape.

Lightning was constantly flashing within the vortex, letting loose bursts of dull rumbling, as if there were countless ferocious beasts trapped within the clouds.

At this moment, Han Li was seated within the pillar of golden light. His robes had already been torn to shreds, and his chiseled yet proportionate muscles were basked in golden radiance, while his long hair was standing up in a completely vertical fashion.

All of the 35 immortal acupoints that had opened up on his body were glowing radiantly, while a golden vortex was taking shape within the 36th immortal acupoint at the center of his chest, looking as if it were going to be completely opened up at any moment.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open as he let loose an earth-shattering roar, and the golden light within the swirling vortex brightened even further as wisps of the world's origin qi that were visible even to the naked eye rapidly converged toward the immortal acupoint.

The sound of howling wind rang out as the world's origin qi gushed into the immortal acupoint, but it resembled a boundless abyss that was impossible to fill, and it was displaying no signs of getting any fuller at all.

Han Li wore a solemn expression as he continued to make a rapid string of hand seals, carefully guiding the direction of flow of the world's origin qi while also moderating the rate at which the immortal acupoint was absorbing the world's origin qi to ensure that it wouldn't burst of an excessive influx.

Only after around two hours had passed did the rate of influx of the world's origin qi gradually slow down, while the light radiating from the immortal acupoint was only becoming brighter and brighter, gradually approaching a state of stability.

At this point, Han Li was already sweating profusely, but he didn't dare to let down his guard in the slightest, and he was constantly preparing for something to go wrong.

All of a sudden, a rumbling boom rang out in the sky, and the lightning that had been suppressed within the dark clouds was finally released.

A black pillar of lightning that was as straight as a spear pierced through the clouds before crashing down directly upon Han Li's head.

Han Li immediately threw a punch upward in response, and a starlight fist projection erupted upward to oppose the pillar of lightning.

Seven punches were thrown in succession, and seven starlight fist projections, each of which was several dozen feet in size, flew up toward the pillar of lightning. Halos of starry radiance surged out of the fist projections, connecting together to form a resplendent screen of silver light.

The pillar of black lightning crashed straight into the silver light barrier with an earth-shattering boom, and the latter shuddered violently before a huge hole was blasted straight through its center by the pillar of black lightning.

At the same time, an even louder burst of rumbling rang out from within the dark cloud vortex in the sky, and a pillar of black lightning that was twice as thick as the previous one came crashing down, as if the heavens had been provoked and were determined to make Han Li feel their wrath.

Daoist Xie's expression changed slightly as it witnessed this from afar, and it instantly vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning.

In the next instant, it reappeared within the space between Han Li and the pillar of lightning, and golden lightning erupted out of its entire body as it raised an arm toward the descending pillar of lightning.

A layer of golden lightning emerged from its arm, and its hand abruptly transformed into a giant golden crab pincer that clamped down forcefully upon the pillar of black lightning.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out as the pillar of golden lightning was snapped into two before exploding violently, but the point at which the pillar of lightning was severed transformed into a spherical lightning cage that trapped Daoist Xie within it in the blink of an eye.

Daoist Xie let loose a cry of alarm upon seeing this, and it hurriedly reached out to make a grabbing motion, but it was already too late.

A burst of black light emerged around the spherical lightning cage, and arcs of black lightning as thick as a grown man's arm shot out in all directions, causing the surrounding space to crackle and shudder.

One of these flailing arcs of lightning struck Han Li's back like a black whip, instantly raising a trail of black sparks and leaving a large section of his back charred black.

His brows instantly furrowed slightly as he hurriedly turned his gaze toward his own chest, only to find that a hair-thin strands of black light had suddenly appeared in the immortal acupoint that was taking shape there, and it quickly began to spread like a cobweb, staining the majority of the immortal acupoint black.

Han Li's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this.

Even though he had never experienced it before, this appeared to be the acupoint decay of the three decays.

Han Li had already anticipated that this would happen, but now that it was truly happening, he still couldn't help but feel a little panicked.

Throughout the ages, there had been countless prodigious cultivators who had overcome all types of obstacles and hardships to successfully oppose the heavens and reach the True Immortal Stage. After that, they spent countless years grinding away, finally rising up above the other countless True Immortals to reach the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage.

However, right as they were about to leave the True Immortal Stage behind altogether, they would be blighted by the curse of the acupoint decay, and all of their countless years of arduous cultivation could be for nought.

It was said that unlike the other two decays, the onset of acupoint decay was extremely fast and uncontrollable, like a spreading wildfire. Once one immortal acupoint fell into decay, all of the immortal acupoints that the cultivator had painstakingly nurtured would also suffer the same fate.

Once all of one's immortal acupoints fell into decay, one's immortal body would also wither away, and all of their immortal spiritual power would dissipate. In the end, they would be reduced to a mere mortal. In fact, they would be in an even worse situation than a mortal as they wouldn't even have the chance to begin cultivating anew.

The entirety of Han Li's attention was drawn to that acupoint, and he couldn't help but feel a little uneasy, fearing that all of his other acupoints could be infected one after another before decaying as well.

This was a very strange sensation that could only be experienced and not described.

It would be like if someone painstakingly nurtured a lotus flower, only for someone to drip a drop of lethal poison onto the flower right as it was about to bloom. The poison would quickly spread over the entire flower, then down its stem and across its leaves, leading to a rapid decay.

Right as Han Li was about to use his time law powers to counteract the decay, he noticed that something wasn't quite right.

As it turned out, the contaminated acupoint maintained a half-black, half-white coloration, and the decay didn't spread rapidly as all of the ancient records claimed it would.

What's going on here?

Chapter 460: Nascent Soul Cleansing

Why is it progressing differently from what I've read?

Han Li didn't know whether he should be concerned or elated by this turn of events.

Only upon closer inspection did he discover that there were hints of white light opposing the spreading black strands in the acupoint, forming what appeared to be a white umbrella that kept the black strands at bay.

This is... starpower!

This immortal acupoint just so happened to overlap with one of the 36 profound acupoints that he had previously opened, and to his surprise, the starpower within the profound acupoint was able to counteract the spread of acupoint decay.

Han Li was quite relieved to see this, and it seemed that he wouldn't have to resort to any extreme measures for now. With that in mind, he decided to continue observing the progression of the acupoint decay.

If the average True Immortal cultivator were to witness this, they would most likely be so envious and enraged that they would drop dead on the spot! How could there possibly be someone dealing with acupoint decay in such a leisurely fashion?!

At this moment, the black strands and the starpower in the acupoint were clashing like a pair of opposing armies, with neither side able to get the better of the other, and it seemed that they were evenly matched.

However, Han Li noticed that with each clash that took place, the black strands were always able to claim a minute advantage. This wasn't necessarily because they were more formidable than the starpower that opposed them. Instead, it was because even profound acupoints were still just that: acupoints.

While it was able to drastically enhance the immortal acupoint's ability to oppose the effects of acupoint decay, thereby significantly slowing down its onset, it wasn't able to fundamentally prevent the progression of acupoint decay.

In other words, the starpower within the profound acupoint could buy a cultivator precious time in the face of acupoint decay, but if the cultivator couldn't find a way to truly counteract acupoint decay, then they would still inevitably suffer the same terrible fate that had befallen countless True Immortals before them.

After observing the acupoint for a moment longer, Han Li made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared at his behest.

All 360 of the Time Dao Runes on the axis had already been restored at this point, and they were giving off formidable time law power fluctuations. At the same time, a beam of golden light shot out of the Eye of Truth at the center of the axis, shining down upon that immortal acupoint.

As soon as the golden light shone down onto the immortal acupoint, it immediately transformed into a series of golden threads of light that were visible to the naked eye, and they became entangled with the black strands before slowly pulling them out like uprooting carrots from the soil.

As soon as these two powers came into contact with one another, Han Li immediately felt as if the skin there were being tugged on, and the intense, tearing pain made him draw an involuntary sharp breath.

An indescribable sense of agony was instantly transmitted from that immortal acupoint into his consciousness, and he hurriedly made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the Mantra Treasured Axis, upon which it began to revolve rapidly, while the golden light radiating from its Time Dao Runes grew even brighter.

At the same time, a translucent golden light suddenly shot out of the Eye of Truth.

This golden thread was none other than the time law thread that he had painstakingly manifested, and it was imbued with incredibly pure time law powers.

The time law thread shot through the air like an arrow, piercing into that immortal acupoint of Han Li's in a flash.

As soon as the golden thread pierced into the immortal acupoint, a layer of golden light instantly emerged to encompass the entire acupoint.

As soon as the black strands within the immortal acupoint came into contact with this golden light, the former instantly began to melt away like snow under the scorching sun, and it didn't take long before they were completely cleansed.

All of this had taken place in the span of just a few seconds, and after the black strands completely receded, the surrounding world's origin qi began to surge into the immortal acupoints once again.

In the face of one of the three paramount laws, the acupoint decay that had struck fear into the hearts of countless late-True Immortal cultivators had been dispeled with ease.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, and he closed his eyes as he continued to cultivate.

A few minutes later, the 36th immortal acupoint was finally completely opened.

A resounding boom rang out within Han Li's body as all 36 of his immortal acupoints lit up in unison, forming a beam of blinding golden light that erupted upward from his body before piercing straight into the dark clouds up above.

A rare look of surprise appeared on Daoist Xie's face as it witnessed this from above.

"How could this be? How did he manage to stave off the acupoint decay so quickly? Is the combination of a Profound Immortal Physique and time law powers really this potent at counteracting acupoint decay?"

Of course, this was naturally a good thing, and it returned to the rooftop of the azure bamboo pavilion on the edge of the city.

Meanwhile, rumbling thunderclaps rang out incessantly as the dark clouds in the sky gradually faded. However, instead of a clear, blue sky, what was revealed was a vast pool of golden lightning. The lightning inside had been liquefied and was shimmering radiantly.

Han Li took a glance up at the pool of lightning, then reached out to make a grabbing motion, and the intricate jade box that had been placed in front of him this entire time instantly flew into his grasp.

With a casual sweep of his sleeve, the talismans adhered to the box were removed, and the lid flew off on its own.

After the lid was removed, a peculiar medicinal aroma instantly wafted out of the jade box. Inside the jade box was a longan-sized golden pill, and it was none other than the Golden Soul Pill that Han Li had refined in the past.

Han Li plucked the pill out of the box between two of his fingers, then brought it up to his eyes for a closer examination before swallowing it.

As the pill slid down his throat, a burst of gentle golden light instantly appeared over his chest and abdomen, basking his face in a golden glow.

A burst of peculiar energy emerged within his chest and abdomen, but instead of descending into his dantian, it rose straight up into his consciousness to fuse as one with his soul.

The first thing that Han Li felt was a sharp pain in his head, immediately following which he became unprecedentedly sensitive and conscious. In that instant, he felt as if all of his senses had been elevated to a whole new level.

The world before him was still the same world, but it also seemed to be completely different.

He was now able to see the flow of spiritual power in the air, he was able to hear the sound of dust particles colliding around him, and he was able to feel even the faintest gust of wind, as if all of his pores had been completely opened up.

Even without having to use his spiritual sense, he was able to detect everything in every single corner of this secret area. He was able to sense all of the changes taking place around him, and even the faint pulsing of the core in Daoist Xie's body had become clearly audible to him.

Right at this moment, his ears twitched slightly, and he felt as if he could hear something beneath the stone platform in that abandoned garden.

Right as he was about to focus on the sound and listen more carefully, this brief period of heightened sensitivity passed, and his senses returned to normal, while his soul became denser and more resilient.

Han Li immediately reined in his attention and began to focus. He knew that the final obstacle standing in the path of his progression to the Golden Immortal Stage had arrived.

After taking a deep breath, he tapped the top of his own head, and his nascent soul instantly flew out from within, enveloped within a layer of golden light.

Upon emerging from his body, his nascent soul flew around him for a moment before rising up into the air, flying headfirst into the pool of golden lightning up above.

As had been established, the nascent souls of Golden Immortals were far more formidable than that of True Immortals, and the reason for this was that during a Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough, a pool of heavenly lightning would emerge in the heavens. As long as a True Immortal Stage nascent soul could withstand the baptism by lightning, then it would be elevated to a whole new level.

As soon as Han Li's nascent soul entered the pool of lightning, the entire pool instantly began to churn violently, much like a pot of hot oil that had just had a drop of water splashed into it.

The liquefied golden lightning within the pool began to crash into Han Li's nascent soul in waves, while the nascent soul made a hand seal before sitting down within the pool with its legs crossed.

It remained completely still even as the pool of golden lightning churned violently around it, allowing the liquefied golden lightning to strike its body relentlessly.

Dense arcs of golden lightning appeared around the nascent soul like a golden robe, clashing against the golden light radiating from its body.

Meanwhile, Han Li's physical body remained seated in its original posture, but his brows were tightly furrowed in agony.

At this moment, his entire consciousness was churning just as violently as the pool of golden lightning.

Arcs of blinding golden lightning were flashing and intertwining incessantly, filling virtually the entirety of his consciousness, and each flash of lightning was like a whip that struck his soul.

He was able to clearly feel the torment that his nascent soul was having to endure within the pool of lightning, and this agony on a spiritual level was even more excruciating to endure than any form of physical pain.

Han Li didn't know much about what was involved in a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage, and he was planning to enquire Daoist Hu Yan about the subject following the conclusion of this immortal manor adventure, but never did he think that he would be attempting a breakthrough in this random secret area.

For a True Immortal, opening the 36 immortal acupoints only took them halfway to reaching the Golden Immortal Stage, and the other half of the breakthrough hinged on the outcome of this nascent soul refinement process.

The outcome of the nascent soul refinement process was something that was dependent on both the resilience of the nascent soul and the will of the heavens.

Upon entering the lightning pool, the nascent soul would've essentially entered a lightning prison, and it was entirely up to the heavens when the lightning pool would fade. In some cases, the refinement process would end in just half a day, while others could be subjected to this torment for days on end.

The longer this process dragged on, the more significantly the nascent soul would be enhanced, but at the same time, the probability of the nascent soul being destroyed in the process would also steadily rise.

For those with unstable nascent souls, sending their nascent souls into the lightning pool would be no different from committing suicide. There was no chance that a frail nascent soul would be able to endure this refinement process, and its destruction would be inevitable.

However, Han Li certainly didn't fall into that camp. His nascent soul was far more resilient than that of the average True Immortal to begin with, and he had cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique to the fourth level, making his nascent soul more stable and resilient than that of many Golden Immortals. Furthermore, having just consumed that Golden Soul Pill, he was almost excessively well-equipped to endure this refinement process.

The only question left was how long this refinement process was going to last.

Daoist Xie was observing all of this from afar with a calm look on its face, and it was unclear what it was thinking.

Chapter 461: The Mystique of Laws

With his nascent soul trapped within the lightning pool, every single passing second was an extremely grueling one for Han Li, and seven days felt like seven years.

On this day, a resounding boom rang out in the night sky, and a vast expanse of golden lightning surged through the heavens.

It was only for an instant, but it illuminated the entire night sky to be as bright as day.

Following this flash of golden lightning, the golden lightning pool also faded away, completely vanishing into nothingness.

Han Li's nascent soul slowly descended out of the heavens with a smile on its face, and its entire body was radiating dazzling golden light, giving it the appearance of a miniature golden sun from afar.

It slowly landed on the top of Han Li's head, then looked around for a moment before vanishing into Han Li's head.

Han Li's eyes instantly sprang open, and two radiant beams of golden light erupted out of his eyes, extending for around three feet in front of him, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

After just a few blinks, the beams of golden light gradually began to recede until they vanished altogether, but there was still a very bright gleam in his eyes.

All of a sudden, he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, and it flew around him until it was situated in front of him, hovering in mid-air while revolving incessantly.

The axis was shimmering brightly, while the Time Dao Runes on its surface were flashing incessantly. All 360 of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already recovered, and at this moment, there were as many as three time law threads wrapped around the axis.

A hint of elation emerged in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

During that brief moment of heightened sensitivity immediately after consuming the Golden Soul Pill, he had been struck by an indescribable feeling, one that granted him a hint of enlightenment when it came to the power of time laws.

At the time, he had already felt the time law thread in his body beginning to undergo a transformation, but a Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough was imminent, so he didn't have time to dwell on the feeling.

During the few days that his nascent soul had been baptized within the lightning pool, he had constantly been in a state of excruciating torment, but at the same time, that same indescribable feeling emerged once again, triggering some minute changes in the power of time within his body. Before he knew it, he had already manifested two more time law threads.

In order to manifest his first time law thread, he had gone to extreme lengths, leaving no stone unturned and even going as far as to directly swallow the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial, but still to no avail. In the end, it was only by refining a Time Dao Pill that he was able to attain the time law thread, so he was naturally ecstatic to have manifested two more so easily.

However, now that the nascent soul refinement process had concluded, he was unable to return to that mystical state of enlightenment again.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he made a beckoning motion, and the three time law threads instantly flew toward him from the Mantra Treasured Axis before wrapping themselves around his finger.

By injecting his spiritual sense into them, he could immediately feel bursts of formidable time law fluctuations.

Right at this moment, a burst of blinding light suddenly emerged over the Mantra Treasured Axis, and the Heaven Controlling Vial abruptly flew out of Han Li's robes on its own, hovering in mid-air as it also began to glow as radiantly as a green sun.

The two were resonating with one another, and both were giving off bursts of formidable fluctuations.

All of a sudden, the three time law threads wrapped around Han Li's finger shot forth through the air, hurtling toward the Heaven Controlling Vial like a trio of arrows before vanishing into it in a flash.

A dull thump rang out, and the spirit patterns on the surface of the Heaven Controlling Vial flashed as the green light it was radiating became even more blinding to behold. At the same time, the vial itself was also rapidly expanding, and it didn't take long before ti had swelled to the size of a millstone.

Countless green runes surged out of the surface of the vial while a green cloud gathered within the vial, forming a violently churning green vortex.

Bursts of special aura fluctuations were emanating out of the vial incessantly, while the green cloud within it transformed into a thick pillar of green light that tore through the space before it, then manifested that same strange translucent wall of light that Han Li had seen on several past occasions.

Here it comes again!

Before long, the vortex had already swelled to the size of a house, and a burst of tremendous suction force abruptly surged out from within it, enveloping his entire body.

His soul was instantly sucked out of his body before vanishing into the vortex in a flash.

Han Li felt a sharp pain in his head, immediately following which his vision faded, and he lost all consciousness.

In the next instant, he felt as if he could hear a loud commotion ringing out around him, coupled with the sound of howling wind.

He hurriedly opened his eyes, and only then did he discover that he was situated high up in the sky and was flying rapidly through the air, while the commotion was ringing out from behind him.

Given the last experience in which his soul had been placed into the body of that old man, Han Li already knew what to expect this time, so he wasn't overly panicked, and he continued flying through the air while looking down to examine his own body.

To his surprise, his entire body was a shimmering golden color, and he was very short and stubby. On top of that, he was clutching a green storage bracelet in his arms. It seemed that he wasn't a cultivator. Instead, he was a nascent soul that was frantically fleeing for its life.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. While it was true that Ling Yunzi had been on the brink of death, at least his physical body was still intact!

Having said that, even though this was only a nascent soul, it was far more powerful than Ling Yunzi had been.

Han Li attempted to recollect some of this nascent soul's memories, and he immediately felt as if a rumbling thunderclap had erupted in his mind, causing his head to ring incessantly.

A series of fragmented memories and indescribable emotions instantly surged into his mind, and the sensory overload was so immense that he almost fell out of the sky.

Thankfully, this sensation only lasted an instant, and he was quickly able to stabilize himself again, but as a result, he had also been stopped cold in his tracks.

Instead of continuing to flee, he turned around to look behind him with a peculiar look on his face.

In the distance, large chunks of the heavens and the earth were encompassed within spherical light barriers of different colors, and even though he was already very far away from them, he could still sense extremely formidable energy fluctuations emanating from the light barriers.

Those were dozens, perhaps even close to 100 formidable spirit domains that were giving off tremendous law power fluctuations, and these spirit domains were either overlapping or clashing against one another in a spectacular sight to behold.

This is the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace...

At this point, Han Li had already figured out the identity of the nascent soul that he had possessed. It belonged to a man by the name of Jin Hai, and he had once been a Golden Immortal Stage disciple of the Boundless Sword Sect.

The nascent soul had just fled from the sect, and the memories that Han Li had recalled were quite chaotic and jumbled, with most of them containing images of horrific battles that seemed to have taken place quite recently.

Only after some extensive contemplation was Han Li able to extrapolate some things from these fragmented memories.

It seemed that for some reason, the Reincarnation Palace's forces had suddenly stormed into the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace two days ago, and even though the Immortal Palace was prepared for the invasion, they were still unable to keep the enemy at bay.

As a subsidiary power of the Immortal Palace, the Boundless Sword Sect naturally had to make a final stand alongside the Immortal Palace's forces. They were planning to unleash the sea of swords on the enemy, even though doing so would completely ruin the foundation of the sect, but right as they resorted to this plan, an enemy High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal unleashed their spirit domain to trap the entire sect.

The spirit domain was filled with a type of unidentifiable law power that was able to suppress the vast sword qi within the sea of swords, thereby preventing the Boundless Sword Sect from using it in the battle.

The disciples of the Boundless Sword Sect had no choice but to form an array to force their way out of the Jade Immortal's spirit domain, but after that, they found themselves right in the midst of the battle between the cultivators of the Immortal Palace and the Reincarnation Palace. Jin Hai's martial brothers perished one after another, with some managing to flee in the form of their nascent souls, while others perished altogether.

After inadvertently stumbling into the spirit domain of a cultivator at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, Jin Hai's luck finally ran out, and he also met his demise. In the instant before he perished, he detonated his own bonded flying sword using a secret technique, and only then was his nascent soul able to escape.

Even so, his nascent soul was already severely wounded and on the brink of disintegrating. If it weren't for the influx of Han Li's spiritual sense, it would've most likely already completely disintegrated into nothingness.

Why did the Reincarnation Palace attack the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace? Does this have something to do with the fall of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace?

With all these questions in his mind, Han Li turned his gaze to his left, and sure enough, the faint projection of his Mantra Treasured Axis was hovering there.

The Time Dao Runes on its surface were flashing with semi-transparent light, and around a dozen of them had already faded.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this.

At this point, he had definitely already been in the wall of light for at least 30 seconds, so 30 Time Dao Runes should've been snuffed out at a minimum, so why was that not the case?

Could it be...

A thought occurred to Han Li, and he began to scrutinize the Mantra Treasured Axis intently with an unblinking gaze.

Moments later, his brows unfurrowed, and a hint of elation appeared on his face.

He discovered that each Time Dao Rune was now able to last three seconds before fading away instead of one.

Perhaps this was because he now possessed three time law threads.

If the accumulation of each additional time law thread really could extend the duration of time that each Time Dao Rune could last, then as he continued to manifest more time law threads in the future, this duration would most likely only continue to extend!

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but wonder if some other changes would take place once the number of time law threads in his possession passed certain thresholds, if such thresholds truly did exist.

Chapter 462: Astonishment

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li decided to fly back toward the Immortal Palace instead of continuing to flee.

He didn't want to waste the limited time that he had, and he wanted to confirm some things.

Firstly, he wanted to see if he could figure out exactly how the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace had met its demise. After all, he was still trapped in the ruins of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace and didn't know how to get out.

Secondly, he wanted to find out why the Reincarnation Palace had attacked the Immortal Palace. At the moment, he was a Reincarnation Disciple, so knowing more about the Reincarnation Palace certainly couldn't hurt.

Thirdly, he wanted to observe all of these spirit domains at a closer proximity.

He had actually already come into contact with a spirit domain back in the Spirit Realm, but that had only been a Profound Heavenly Spirit Domain unleashed by Bao Hua, which was really only just a faux spirit domain unleashed with the help of a Profound Heavenly Treasure. [1]

After arriving in the Immortal Realm, Han Li had spent some time searching for information pertaining to spirit domains, but opportunities to personally witness spirit domains had proven to be very few and far in between, so he naturally didn't want to pass up this prime opportunity.

This nascent soul was quite powerful to begin with, and following the injection of Han Li's spiritual sense, its speed had been enhanced by severalfold, so it didn't take long before Han Li arrived near the battlefield.

At this point, a decent number of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had already faded.

Not far in front of him was an enormous yellow spherical light barrier, and even without entering it, Han Li could already sense a burst of tremendous earth-attribute energy fluctuations emanating from it.

Through the light barrier, Han Li could clearly see that all of the trees and buildings in the area encompassed within the light barrier had been crushed under some type of tremendous force.

He could also just barely make out some cultivators in the extremely far distance, and all of them were doing everything in their power to oppose this force, but it was clear that they were fighting a losing battle, and they were so severely restricted that they could only fly at a very slow pace several dozen feet above the ground.

The other side of this light barrier overlapped with a silver spirit domain, within which were countless streaks of bright sword qi that were severely ravaging the space encompassed within the spirit domain.

Further away in the distance, there were spirit domains that were even larger and brighter, and each of them had their own unique properties.

Han Li was completely flabbergasted by what he was seeing, and he was wondering if he should venture into the spirit domain directly before him when he heard a thunderous roar ring out from extremely far away.

A burst of formidable soundwaves pierced straight into his mind without encountering any resistance, and it was like a giant blade threatening to cleave his soul apart.

Han Li's consciousness was instantly plunged into a state of extreme turbulence and disarray, and he felt as if his spiritual sense were about to fall apart, causing him to involuntarily fall out of the sky.

However, right at this moment, his Spirit Refinement Technique was activated on its own, and a layer of black light instantly spread over his consciousness to protect it.

In the instant before Han Li plummeted into the ground, his spiritual sense was finally stabilized again, and a stunned look appeared on his face as he hurriedly flew upward again to regain his elevation.

He turned to the direction where the roar had come from to find that most of the spirit domains there had already been broken. It was unclear whether they had been directly broken by that roar or if the spirit sense of the cultivators who had unleashed those spirit domains had been destroyed, thereby resulting in the disintegration of their spirit domains.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Han Li turned back to the same direction in which he had previously been fleeing and flew away even faster than before.

The power imbued within that roar wasn't unfamiliar to Han Li. It was the power of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and it was similar in nature to the Spirit Stun Thorn, but enhanced by sheer orders of magnitude.

If Han Li were to remain on this battlefield, he wasn't sure if he would be able to withstand another one of those attacks, or perhaps an even more formidable spiritual attack, and that was why he decided to flee again.

Even after fleeing for close to 100,000 kilometers, Han Li still displayed no intention of stopping, and only after he had reached the sea did he finally slow down slightly.

He swept his gaze across the surrounding area to find that on the surface of the sea not far away was a long and slender island shaped like a willow leaf. Vegetation on the island was very sparse, and the ground was littered with exposed gray rocks.

Isn't this the island inhabited by the Cold Crystal Race? Is this the Black Wind Island?

Somehow, it seemed that he had arrived in the Black Wind Sea.

Right at this moment, he was struck by another burst of sensory overload, and fragments of Jin Hai's memories began to surface once again.

However, the memories this time had nothing to do with the ongoing battle. Instead, they pertained to a treasure map.

Prior to the commencement of this battle, Jin Hai seemed to have made an arrangement with someone to leave the Boundless Sword Sect to travel to another immortal region in search of treasures, but he never got the chance to make good on that promise.

The map appeared to lead to quite a remarkable treasure, as evidenced by the deep regret and disappointment from Jin Hai attached to this memory. Perhaps that was why this memory had sprung up in Han Li's mind.

Only then did it occur to Han Li to examine the contents of Jin Hai's storage bracelet, and in doing so, he discovered that the storage bracelet was filled with a vast abundance of resources, including a huge number of Immortal Origin Stones, as well as many treasures, pills, and ancient scriptures.

Many of those treasures and pills were unrecognizable to Han Li, but he was familiar with what those ancient scriptures were.

Jin Hai's memories indicated that he treasured these ancient scriptures as much as his own life, and they contained the sword techniques and sword arrays of the Boundless Sword Sect.

If it weren't for the fact that his time in this state was very limited, Han Li would've definitely decided to study these scriptures. After all, the Boundless Sword Sect was vastly renowned as one of the most brilliant sword sects in history, so which sword cultivator wouldn't want to study its sword techniques?

Among the items in the storage bracelet, Han Li noticed a strange silken handkerchief, which, according to Jin Hai's memories, was supposed to hold the treasure map. The handkerchief was cool to the touch, and there was rainbow light flashing over its surface, indicating that it was no ordinary handkerchief.

However, as he attempted to carefully observe the patterns on the handkerchief, he discovered that he wasn't able to see anything clearly, so he was naturally unable to identify the map on it.

In order to conduct a better examination, Han Li called upon his Eye of Truth, and a beam of golden light shone down onto the handkerchief from the eye.

However, with his usage of the Eye of Truth, the rate at which the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis were fading was accelerated, and he only had fewer than 20 active ones left.

The rainbow light on the surface of the handkerchief rippled before spreading outward from the center, and a very complex map soon appeared on the handkerchief.

Han Li scrutinized the map intently, carefully looking over every single detail in order to commit everything to memory.

After that, he took a glance at his Mantra Treasured Axis, on which only several Time Dao Runes remained lit, and he stowed the map back into his storage bracelet before plunging down into the sea near the white island as quickly as he could, plummeting into the water like a meteorite.

He descended rapidly through the water, leaving a white line in his wake as he hurtled directly toward the seabed.

Meanwhile, the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis hovering above him continued to fade one after the other.

With only five Time Dao Runes left, Han Li had already plunged over 10,000 feet into the sea, and he broke through the 100,000 feet mark with only three Time Dao Runes left.

......

Finally, Han Li reached the seabed, then pierced a hand straight into the seabed's rocky surface to create a deep hole. After that, he tossed the storage bracelet into the hole, then lifted a huge rock before placing it over the hole.

Before Han Li had a chance to verify whether the opening of the hole had been properly sealed, the final Time Dao Rune was snuffed out, and a vortex abruptly appeared right next to him.

Another burst of sharp pain speared through his mind, following which his spiritual sense returned to his body.

Han Li looked on as the wall of light before him gradually faded, and he continued to recollect what he had just witnessed with a contemplative look on his face.

Only after some time had passed did he sweep a sleeve through the air, and all three of his time law threads emerged, having been reduced to a dull and lusterless state, and they returned to his Mantra Treasured Axis at his behest.

Immediately thereafter, the Mantra Treasured Axis also vanished into his body.

Han Li rose to his feet before sweeping a sleeve through the air once again, and a new azure robe appeared over his body. He then summoned a white jade hairpin and briefly arranged his own hair before securing it with his hairpin.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie flew over from afar before landing beside him.

"Congratulations on making such an important breakthrough, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie said as it cupped its fist in a salute.

"Thank you for keeping a lookout for me all this time, Brother Xie," Han Li replied with a smile.

"There's no need to thank me, my fate is directly intertwined with yours. Now that you've reached the Golden Immortal Stage, I'm sure your Mantra Treasured Axis will have made a full recovery. Should we go and take another look at that dream concealment restriction?" Daoist Xie suggested.

Han Li smiled as he replied, "My thoughts exactly..."

However, his voice then abruptly cut off as he recalled that all of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had been snuffed out again.

"Is there something wrong?" Daoist Xie asked.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face, but he shook his head as he replied, "No, let's go take a look at the restriction."

Thus, the two of them arrived in the abandoned garden once again, and everything remained much the same compared with during their last visit.

Han Li strode over the stone platform and carefully examined it with his spiritual sense. Immediately thereafter, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, and sure enough, all of the Time Dao Runes on its surface were dull and devoid of luster.

He made a hand seal with both hands, and a beam of golden light shot out of the Eye of Truth at the center of the axis before striking the center of the stone platform.

A layer of light emerged over the stone platform, but it quickly faded, and nothing else happened aside from that.

"I guess I shouldn't be surprised," Han Li murmured to himself with a faint sigh.

A thought then occurred to him, and his three time law threads flew out of his Mantra Treasured Axis at his behest before flying straight into the stone platform.

All of a sudden, the entire stone platform began to glow with dazzling golden radiance, and the golden light instantly spread in all directions like a complex system of tree branches, extending all the way to beyond the forest in which the stone platform was situated.

[1]. For more information on Bao Hua, please refer to https://rmji.fandom.com/wiki/Bao_Hua

[Back]

Chapter 463: Underground Palace

"Looks like not only has the core of the dream concealment restriction been revealed, even all of the array's hidden points have surfaced as well," Daoist Xie said as it looked at the radiantly glowing stone platform.

"In that case, can you see if you can break the restriction now, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Judging from the repaired stamen, this should be a Nine Nightmares Restriction, the most special type of all dream concealment restrictions. It's a good thing that we did try to break it by brute force. Otherwise, if we had activated this entire array, then this secret area would've been turned on its head! Having said that, now that all of the points of the array have been revealed, it'll be far easier to unravel," Daoist Xie replied.

With that established, Daoist Xie borrowed some array flags and array tools from Han Li, then began to fly back and forth through the secret area, making the required preparations to break the restriction.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained still on the spot as he waited patiently.

Around 15 minutes later, Daoist Xie returned to the stone platform while holding a white jade plate with complex patterns engraved onto its surface.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, but he didn't ask any questions.

Daoist Xie paused momentarily in front of the stone platform, then stepped onto it and placed the jade plate at the center of the platform. The jade plate was just the right size to slot into the empty area where the stamen of the restriction was supposed to be.

"I'm using this jade plate as a substitute for the damaged part of the array. I hope it'll work," Daoist Xie explained.

It then made a hand seal while chanting an incantation before pressing its palm down onto the center of the stone platform.

A beam of golden light surged out of the palm of its hand before passing through the jade plate and into the stone platform, and the entire platform instantly shuddered violently before lighting up with blinding golden radiance.

All of the patterns on the stone platform glowed radiantly as a shimmering golden projection rose up into the sky.

The higher the projection ascended, the more it expanded, and in the end, it formed an enormous flower projection that encompassed the entire secret area.

The points at which the golden lines on the nine flower petals met each corresponded with an important point in the array, and Daoist Xie had also already set up array flags at those points.

All of a sudden, hundreds of threads of golden light rained down from the dream flower projection to connect with these array flags, while a pillar of golden light erupted out of the floral projection's stamen to strike the center of the stone platform down below.

A burst of rumbling rang out as a system of cobweb-like golden patterns instantly began to spread across the ground at the foot of the stone platform, but these patterns only lingered for a few moments before fading on their own.

Immediately thereafter, the sound of rock grinding on rock rang out as the entire stone platform split apart into two down the center to reveal a hole that had a diameter or around five feet.

Han Li approached the hole for a closer inspection to find that there was nothing but inky darkness inside, but he could hear the sound of wind ringing out deep within the darkness.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he casually swept a sleeve through the air to summon seven or eight crimson fireballs, each of which was around the size of a human head. All of the fireballs descended into the hole, and it didn't take long before they struck the ground, then bounced a few times before rolling deeper into the hole.

Thanks to the light radiating from the fireballs, Han Li was able to see that the hole was only several hundred feet deep, and that its bottom was paved with stone slabs. It seemed to be a passageway, but it was clear that this wasn't the exit of this secret area.

"It looks like we won't be able to leave this place just yet," Han Li remarked with a forlorn sigh.

"The fact that this place was concealed under the dream concealment restriction indicates that it must be a special place. Perhaps there's a major opportunity waiting for us in there," Daoist Xie said.

"I don't really care about that, all I want is to be able to get out of this place as soon as possible," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"I didn't have to expend much energy while keeping a lookout for you, but I've had to remain in the outside world for over 10 years, so I'll need some time to rest and recuperate. You can call upon me if you need me," Daoist Xie said.

"Thank you, Brother Xie," Han Li said in a heartfelt manner.

Daoist Xie merely gave a dismissive wave of its hand, then flew into Han Li's sleeve as a streak of golden light and vanished in a flash.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Han Li leaped into the hole in the ground.

Upon making a landing at the bottom of the hole, he quickly discovered that the ground beneath his feet and the walls beside him were all very even and uniform. Directly in front of him was a passageway that led deeper into the darkness, and it was over 20 feet tall and around six feet wide.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes while simultaneously releasing his spiritual sense, attempting to examine the depths of the passageway, and only then did he discover that he was situated in a massive underground palace, one that was no smaller than the city on the surface.

The underground palace was completely undetectable to him due to the dream concealment restriction, but he was able to see in its full glory now.

Han Li made his way several hundred meters down the passageway before reaching its conclusion, and a bare stone wall appeared in front of him.

He laid a palm flat against the stone wall before pushing it forcefully, and a burst of rumbling rang out as the entire stone wall slowly slid back several feet to reveal a horizontal passageway.

Han Li stood at the center of the passageway, and he took a glance in either direction before making his way down the right.

The passageway down the right hand side wasn't very long either, and he reached the end after traveling for less than 200 meters. However, there was no crossroads here. Instead, there was a room that was comparable in size to a normal lounge.

Han Li pushed the door of the room open before making his way inside.

In contrast with the dark passageway outside, there were around a dozen palm-sized luminescent rocks embedded into the ceiling, and they were giving off a cold white glow that illuminated the entire room.

With just a single glance, Han Li was able to see the entirety of the room before him.

In a corner of the room was a black wooden shelf that had already decayed into an almost unrecognizable state. The vials and containers previously placed on the shelf were strewn over the ground, and their contents were mixed together with the wood scraps on the ground to produce an indescribable odor.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li drew a black porcelain vial out of the putrid rotten wood, and the vial drew to a halt in mid-air in front of him.

The stopper of the vial flew out at Han Li's behest, and a peculiar medicinal aroma instantly wafted out from within.

Han Li took a whiff of the aroma, then heaved a faint sigh as he lowered his hand, allowing the black vial to fall to the ground before rolling away to the side.

The vial once contained a type of pill that would've been useful even to True Immortals, but their medicinal effects had completely faded after such an extended period of time spent in storage.

Han Li carefully inspected the rest of the room, but was unable to find anything useful, so he promptly departed and made his way toward the left branch of the passageway.

After walking for a few minutes, he arrived in front of another stone door, this one riddled with a series of antiquated sealing runes.

After a brief hesitation, he raised a hand, and five balls of light lit up over his fingertips as he pressed them into the stone door.

As soon as the five bursts of spiritual light entered the stone door, all of the complex runes spread across the entire door began to converge toward the center to form a strange circular pattern.

Han Li pressed the palm of his hand against the circular pattern, and the stone door began to rise up on its own amid a burst of dull rumbling.

As the stone door was raised up, a glimmer of light began to pass through it.

Almost as an instinctive reaction, Han Li summoned Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword into his own grasp with a flick of his wrist.

After the stone door was completely raised, Han Li discovered that there was another passageway beyond it. The walls of this passageway were lined with a series of slots, within which some type of oil was slowly burning to give off a faint glow.

The oil seemed to be some type of fish fat, as evidenced by the fishy odor in the air, and Han Li took a quick whiff of the odor in the air before continuing onward.

From this point onward, the number of crossroads that he encountered began to increase, and there were also more rooms to explore, but barely any of them held anything important.

Initially, Han Li would enter those rooms to conduct an examination, but after a while, he began to inspect the rooms using his spiritual sense only, and he wouldn't bother to enter the room at all if he couldn't sense any special energy fluctuations inside.

Several hours later, Han Li emerged through a stone door and arrived in a straight passageway that was around 30 feet wide.

At the conclusion of the passageway was a pair of gates that were around 10 feet tall, both of which were tightly shut. Each gate had half of a fierce-looking beast's head engraved upon it, and a series of twisted patterns spread out to cover the entirety of the gates from the beastly head at the center.

Han Li wasn't able to identify the beast, but he could tell that this was a very complex restriction.

Hence, he made a hand seal and began to examine the gates through the use of his Eye of Truth.

Moments later, he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, and his brows furrowed slightly in contemplation as he began attempting to unravel the restriction.

A string of incantation seals flew into the stone gates, and the runes engraved upon them began to give off a dull yellow glow, while the eyes of the beastly head also lit up like a pair of jewels.

A faint roar rang out as a beastly projection pounced out of the stone gates, and Han Li hurriedly took evasive measures by dodging to the side.

The beastly projection was only able to make it several feet out of the stone gates before vanishing in a flash, following which light glowing from the runes on the gates and the eyes of the beastly head also faded.

Han Li strode over to the gates before pressing a palm against one of them, then exerted force through his hand to push the gate inward, opening up a gap that was several feet wide.

Through this gap, Han Li was able to see a dim light source within the hall beyond it, and a series of indistinct humanoid shadows were being cast onto the ground in front of him.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he released his spiritual sense into the hall for a careful examination, but he didn't discover anything abnormal.

However, upon entering the hall, he was instantly taken aback by what he saw.

There was a series of white stone statues around the same height as grown men spread throughout the hall, and thanks to the faint light emanating from the braziers hanging from the walls, Han Li was able to see that there were seven or eight of these statues in total.

The shadows that he had seen just now had been cast by the two stone statues closest to the gates.

Han Li made his way toward the center of the hall while carefully examining these stone statues, and in doing so, he discovered that they seemed to be acting as pillars that supported this underground hall.

The statues didn't depict any formidable warriors or ferocious beasts. Instead, they were extremely lifelike statues of a collection of male and female figures, all of which were standing straight with their arms hanging down by their sides.

Chapter 464: Unmatched Genius

Han Li swept his gaze across the statues, and he discovered that a pair of statues among them, depicting an elderly daoist priest and a woman in a palace dress, were the most intricately crafted statues of the collection.

The elderly daoist priest was quite thin with a goatee on his chin, and the creases and folds on his daoist robes were quite pronounced, as if he were in the process of flying through the air, giving him quite a graceful and elegant appearance.

As for the woman in the palace dress, she was just as tall and imposing as a man, and her features were also rather sharp and angular, giving her an appearance that was rather unbefitting of her attire.

In Han Li's opinion, it would've looked far more appropriate for her to have been presented in a suit of armor instead.

All of a sudden, Han Li raised a hand before lashing out to his left.

"Owie!"

A cry of pain rang out, followed by a loud crack, and a skeleton that was as fair and translucent as jade was sent flying by the burst of power released by Han Li's hand, crashing heavily into the wall before shattering into countless pieces.

"Who are you?" Han Li interrogated in a cold voice.

A faint glimmer of green light slowly rose up from the shattered skeleton, forming the indistinct projection of an elderly daoist priest that looked as if it were comprised of countless fireflies.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that this was a soul fragment, and that it was identical in appearance to that statue of the elderly daoist priest.

"What a rude little bastard you are! What am I supposed to use as a vessel now that you've destroyed this skeleton of mine?" the soul fragment complained in a furious voice.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he asked, "Who are you? Answer me or I'll erase you from existence!"

The projection of the elderly daoist priest was completely unfazed, and it placed its hands on its hips as it scoffed, "Looks like you're an arrogant little bastard too! Back when I reigned supreme over the Infernal Frost Immortal Region, you probably weren't even born yet!"

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this. "Infernal Frost Immortal Region... Are you from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor?"

The soul fragment took a glance at the longsword in Han Li's hand, then remarked, "I can see that you're a sword user. I'm sure you've heard of the Boundless Daoist, right?"

"Even to this day, the Boundless Sword Sect is still a vastly renowned sect across the entire immortal region, so of course I know of its founder," Han Li replied.

The soul fragment erupted into a furious fit upon hearing this, and it spat onto the ground as it yelled, "Ptui! Don't try to trick me, you little brat! After what happened to the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, there's no way that the lineage of the Boundless Sword Sect wasn't severed! After all this time, I'm sure the sect has already completely fallen into obscurity."

A hesitant look then appeared on the soul fragment's face as it murmured to itself, "Could it be that that side branch managed to continue the sect's lineage? No, that's impossible. Those bastards wouldn't have been capable of anything other than bringing disgrace to the sect's name. How unfortunate. Back in the day..."

The soul fragment seemed to have recalled some unpleasant memories, and it began mumbling to itself, completely lost in its own thoughts.

Han Li was becoming more suspicious by the second, and he interjected, "Who are you? Don't make me ask again!"

The soul fragment stood up a little straighter, seemingly trying to lend itself more prestige as it declared, "Listen up, kid! I am none other than the founder of the Boundless Sword Sect that you speak of! I am the Boundless Daoist!"

"What proof do you have to support that claim?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

The soul fragment was furious to hear this, and it retorted, "Proof my arse! Do you know I am? Why do I need to prove my identity to a little shit like you?"

"Regardless of who you were in the past, I'm the one who calls the shots here, do you understand?" Han Li said with a faint smile as he raised the sword in his hand.

The soul fragment took a glance at Han Li's longsword, and it seemed to have been intimidated into submission as it sighed, "How do you want me to prove my identity to you? You've already shattered my skeleton, so I can't even demonstrate my sect's sword techniques to you."

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "Aside from the Profound Myriad Sword Badge, does your Boundless Sword Sect have any other inherited treasures?"

A mocking sneer appeared on the soul fragment's face upon hearing this, and it scoffed, "Don't think that you can get me with your sneaky little trap! There are two inherited treasures in our Boundless Sword Sect, one of which is the Myriad Sword Iron Scripture, which was passed down in the sect, while the other is the Boundless Sword Core, which was given to the side branch of the sect."

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"Let me ask you this: does my Boundless Sword Sect still exist in some form?" the soul fragment suddenly asked.

Han Li thought back to Elder Qi Heng of the Holy Puppet Sect, and at this point, it had become clear to him that Qi Heng had to have been a member of the Boundless Sword Sect's side branch.

"The lineage of the sect has indeed already been severed. As for the side branch, that's also fallen into obscurity."

A hint of disappointment appeared on the soul fragment's face upon hearing this, but it seemed to have already anticipated this answer.

"What about the legacy of myself and the Boundless Sword Sect? Are my sect and I still mentioned with reverence by everyone in the immortal region?"

Instead of answering the question, Han Li raised one of his own. "If you really are the Boundless Daoist as you proclaim, then how did you end up getting sealed in here?"

"Who told you I've been sealed in here?" the soul fragment asked with a furious expression.

Han Li offered no response to this. In reality, he had also been rather perplexed as it simply didn't make sense to go to so much trouble just to seal away a soul fragment.

"Can't you tell? I willingly sealed myself in this place!" the soul fragment declared as it puffed out its chest in a proud manner.

"Alright, then why are you hiding here?" Han Li asked.

The soul fragment was instantly infuriated once again upon hearing the word "hide", but in the end, it could only heave a forlorn sigh as it replied, "It's all because I have to take care of her."

"Her?" Han Li took a glance at the statue of the woman in the palace dress upon hearing this. "Who is she?"

"She's a pain in the arse is what she is!" the soul fragment snapped.

After a brief pause, the soul fragment took a glance at the statue of the woman, then continued, "She's a High Zenith Stage Gray Immortal from the Gray Realm. "

"The Gray Realm?"

Han Li was only becoming more and more confused.

"The Heavenly Court has been hiding the existence of the Gray Realm this entire time, to the point that none of you are even aware of its existence. Perhaps that's a blessing, perhaps it's a curse, who knows?" the soul fragment sighed.

"What is this Gray Realm?" Han Li asked as the tone of his voice softened a little.

"You know what? I haven't had anyone to speak to in a very long time, and I'm in a pretty good mood right now, so I'll tell you about the Gray Realm. Just like our True Immortal Realm, the Gray Realm is another boundless realm inhabited by living beings unique to that realm, and those who attain immortality in the Gray Realm are known as Gray Immortals," the soul fragment explained.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "Does the fall of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace have something to do with this woman?"

Instead of answering Han Li's question, the soul fragment raised one of its own. "Why are you so interested in what happened to the Immortal Palace?"

"I still don't trust you one bit, so I want to hear you talk about what happened to the Immortal Palace in order to help me form my judgment," Han Li said with a cold smile.

The soul fragment's expression stiffened slightly upon seeing this, and it was about to put on an enraged facade once again, but it could tell that Han Li wasn't going to be intimidated, so it could only heave a deflated sigh.

A reminiscent look then appeared on its face as it began to recount the events of the distant past. "Back in the day, I had just become the master of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, and I was at the height of my powers, but this troublesome woman..."

"What did you just say?" Han Li interjected. "You became the master of the Immortal Palace? Wouldn't that make you the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord?"

The soul fragment seemed to be rather displeased with Han Li's rude interjection, and it raised an eyebrow as it retorted, "Who told you that the Boundless Daoist can't also be the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord?"

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly with skepticism upon hearing this.

"Hmph, I suppose I can't expect a mere mortal like yourself to comprehend my unmatched genius. Listen up, kid, you better not go interrupt me again! Young people these days don't even know how respect is spelt!" the soul fragment scoffed in a disgruntled manner.

Han Li adjusted his grip on the hilt of his sword in a subtle fashion as he prompted, "Please continue."

The soul fragment cleared its throat in a sheepish manner upon seeing this, then began to give Han Li a long-winded recount of his past.

According to the soul fragment, his name was Lu Yun, and he was originally a member of a side branch of a medium-sized cultivating clan on the Infernal Frost Continent. His aptitude was quite mediocre, so he didn't receive much attention from the clan, and he wasn't given any of the clan's best cultivation arts.

Hence, he had no choice but to turn to the body refinement scriptures in the clan, which no one wanted to pursue.

Through a series of strokes of fortune, he was able to embark on the path of becoming a Profound Immortal, and he discovered that he was quite suited to using these body refinement cultivation arts.

After experimenting with countless body refinement methods, he was suddenly struck by inspiration one night while looking up at the stars in the sky, and he invented a way to refine one's body using starlight. Ultimately,that led to the creation of the Great Universe Origin Arts, using which he was able to make rapid progress in his cultivation and progressed all the way to the Golden Immortal Stage.

At some point, he faced a Golden Immortal Stage sword cultivator who was half a cultivation rank above him in battle, and the battle concluded in a tie. Despite holding his own against an opponent of a superior cultivation base, he was extremely humiliated by this outcome, and he turned to cultivating the way of the sword in a fit of rage and indignation.

After over 3,000 years in obscurity, he finally re-emerged into the world as the Boundless Daoist, reaching the pinnacle of the Infernal Frost Immortal Region and founding the Boundless Sword Sect.

Eventually, he was able to reach the High Zenith Stage, allowing him to reign supreme over the entire Infernal Frost Immortal Region, and he was able to become the master of the Infernal Frost Continent's Immortal Palace without even having to join the Heavenly Court.

The soul fragment was telling the story in an extremely spirited and enthused fashion, and if it weren't for the fact that it possessed no physical body, spittle would've been flying everywhere out of its mouth.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he listened to the story, but internally, he was quite astonished.

If this soul fragment were telling the truth, then Lu Yun's feats went far beyond just "unmatched genius"!

Chapter 465: Core

Han Li suppressed the bewilderment in his heart as he continued to listen to the soul fragment's story.

"Her name is Mo Yu, and back then, she used a secret technique to conceal her cultivation base before infiltrating my Infernal Frost Immortal Palace. She possessed decent aptitude, so I decided to take her under my wing as my disciple, teaching her my sword techniques and imparting upon her a spirit domain, but alas..."

After a brief pause, the soul fragment continued in a slightly forlorn voice, "In the end, she tried to use my Immortal Palace as an entrance for a passageway to the Gray Realm so that the living beings of the Gray Realm could invade this immortal region. The Reincarnation Palace was colluding with the Gray Realm, and they also attacked my Infernal Frost Immortal Palace alongside the army of Gray Realm beings. Ultimately, things completely spiraled out of control and..."

The soul fragment's voice trailed off there with another forlorn sigh, and Han Li concluded in his stead, "Your Infernal Frost Immortal Palace was defeated."

"We were indeed defeated, but they didn't manage to reap any benefits from their victory, either! It's just a pity that my Infernal Frost Immortal Palace was torn to pieces during the battle, and many of its regions have most likely already been completely lost," the soul fragment said in a forlorn voice.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he hurriedly asked, "Is there a region in your Infernal Frost Immortal Palace known as the Vast Glacial Realm?"

"There is. Why do you ask?" the soul fragment asked as it raised an eyebrow.

A hint of enlightenment instantly welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this. The Vast Glacial Realm had most likely been lost from the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace in the wake of that battle, and it had since become a secret area in the Spirit Realm.

With that in mind, the Myriad Sword Scroll that he had obtained from the Vast Glacial Realm most likely once belonged to the Boundless Sword Sect as well.

The soul fragment was unbothered by the lack of response from Han Li, and it continued, "You've asked me a bunch of questions, so it's only fair that you answer a few questions for me now, right?"

Han Li completely ignored this request as he asked, "How did that battle conclude, and how did you end up in here?"

The soul fragment was rendered completely speechless for a moment, following which it exclaimed in an indignant voice, "How could you be so rude?"

Han Li remained completely expressionless as he subtly adjusted the positioning of the longsword in his hand once again.

"Ahem... To be honest, I don't know how the battle ended. After the reinforcements from the Reincarnation Palace arrived, I was forced to battle Mo Yu and another formidable enemy on my own. I was able to severely injure both of them, but ultimately, I was defeated, and my physical body was destroyed. In the end, only this soul fragment of mine survived, and I was forced to flee here before sealing myself away so I could wait to be saved," the soul fragment explained.

"Why didn't you receive any reinforcements from the Heavenly Court? Haven't they always been sworn enemies of the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Even though I was the master of the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, I was used to living with full freedom and autonomy, so I was unwilling to join the Heavenly Court, and I didn't follow any of their orders. Hence, they were happy to see me go down in that battle so they could swoop in and reap the spoils. My guess is that the Infernal Frost Immortal Region has already been completely taken over by the Heavenly Court by now, right?" the soul fragment asked.

"The Infernal Frost Immortal Region has already been renamed to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and the current Northern Glacial Immortal Palace is indeed under the control of the Heavenly Court," Han Li confirmed with a nod.

The soul fragment faltered slightly upon hearing this, then fell into deep thought.

Han Li stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword away, then took a glance at his surroundings before asking, "Where did these statues come from?"

"I have nothing to do in here anyway, so I made them to help pass the time. What do you think? They're not bad, right?" the soul fragment chuckled.

"If you sealed yourself in here, did you not think to make a way out so that you could leave at some point?" Han Li asked.

The soul fragment took an exasperated glance at Han Li, then replied, "I created this place for my own protection. If I left a way out, there would've been a way for my enemies to get in as well. Besides, I was in a real hurry when I fled into this place, so I didn't have time to think things over."

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "In that case, you don't know how to get out of this secret area, either, right?"

At the very most, Han Li was only willing to believe half of what the soul fragment was telling him. He had a feeling that the soul fragment was hiding some things from him, but he could find any holes in its story, either.

The soul fragment took a quick glance at Han Li, then shook his head as he scoffed, "You're dreaming if you think you can get out of this place at your current level of power!"

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked.

"Unless this secret area is opened from the outside, the only way to get out of here is to destroy its core. However, this core is directly connected to this entire secret area, and as soon as it's attacked, it'll draw upon all of the world's origin qi within the entire secret area to defend itself.

“At the peak of my powers, I would've been able to get out of this place with ease, but at the moment, you're only at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, right? I suggest you resign yourself to your fate and stay here to keep me company," the soul fragment chuckled.

"May I ask what your past cultivation base was, Senior?" Han Li asked, adopting a much more polite and respectful tone this time.

A smug grin appeared on the soul fragment's face as it humble-bragged, "My cultivation base wasn't that advanced, I was only at the late-High Zenith Stage."

Even though Han Li was already somewhat mentally prepared for this answer, he still couldn't help but feel astonished upon hearing his suspicions confirmed.

"In that case, are you saying that only a late-High Zenith cultivator will be able to break the core of the secret area?" Han Li asked.

"Not necessarily, you should be able to pull it off starting from the early-High Zenith Stage, but you're clearly not... Oh, by the way, what cultivation art are you using? Have you mastered the power of laws yet?" the soul fragment suddenly asked.

"How is that relevant?" Han Li asked.

"It's extremely relevant! If you've only mastered some normal law powers, then you would naturally have to be at the High Zenith Stage to have a chance of breaking the core of this secret area, but if, by some miracle, you've mastered one of the three paramount laws to a decent extent, then the mid-Golden Immortal Stage should suffice," the soul fragment explained.

Instead of immediately showing his hand, Han Li asked, "Could it be that the core of this secret area is somehow related to the three paramount laws?"

"The core of this secret area is an item that contains the power of time laws. By my estimates, if you try to break it through brute force alone, you'll need to be at least at the early-High Zenith Stage. If you deconstruct it using the power of spatial laws, then you'll have to be at the late-Golden Immortal Stage, and if you've mastered the power of time laws, you'll only have to be at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage," the soul fragment explained.

"May I ask where the core is? Would you be able to lead me to it, Senior?" Han Li asked.

The soul fragment seemed to be rather hesitant to oblige with this request, and it remained silent for quite some time.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "Is there something wrong?"

"There are some restrictions in this place that... I'm unable to enter in my current state," the soul fragment replied, seemingly rather embarrassed by its own admission of weakness.

"That's not a problem. I have a Soul Nurturing Burner that you can temporarily reside in," Han Li said as he flipped a hand over to produce a small dark purple incense burner that was crafted from Soul Nurturing Wood.

"I suppose there's no other option," the soul fragment sighed as it flew into the incense burner.

"Where do I need to go, Senior?" Han Li asked while holding the incense burner.

"To the left of this hall is a secret door. After you go through the secret door, keep going straight."

The soul fragment's voice was sounding a little muffled, coming from inside the incense burner.

Han Li was constantly scouring his surroundings with his spiritual sense while making his way deeper into the underground palace under the soul fragment's instructions.

After traversing through a maze-like system of passageways for around two hours, he finally arrived at the entrance of another hall.

"This is the place?" Han Li asked.

"The core of this secret area is just inside. I won't go in with you, just place this burner down at the entrance," the soul fragment replied.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes as he swept his gaze over the stone door of the hall, only to find that it was completely devoid of any markings or spiritual power fluctuations.

All of a sudden, a sly grin appeared on his face, and he tossed the incense burner into the hall.

The burner clattered onto the ground, and countless hidden patterns on the ground instantly lit up with dazzling golden radiance to illuminate the entire hall.

"Get me out of here, you little bastard! You're going to kill me!" the soul fragment wailed in panic.

Han Li briefly observed the golden light radiating from the hidden patterns on the ground, and he discovered that it had a suppressive effect on ghosts and spirits, much like his Divine Devilbane Lightning.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the incense burner was drawn back to him, and the soul fragment inside was still moaning and groaning incessantly, looking as if it could fade out of existence at any moment. It seemed that the soul fragment had been so severely weakened by that brief ordeal that it didn't even have the energy to curse Han Li anymore.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a soul stabilization talisman, then adhered it to the incense burner before placing it down by the entrance before stepping into the hall.

As soon as he entered the hall, Han Li immediately noticed an increase in the surrounding air temperature, and only then did he discover that the floor was entirely paved with Yang Melt Rock, a type of yang-attribute material that was extremely harmful to souls and spirits.

The hall was quite large, but it was also very empty, with nothing inside aside from a stone platform that was around half the height of a grown man.

Han Li strode over the stone platform before conducting an examination to find that it was riddled with all types of complex patterns that stretched all the way down to the floor.

At its center was a circular indentation, within which sat a round stone plate that was white in color.

The stone plate was placed on a slant with a series of markings engraved onto its edge, marking out the 24 hours of the day, and at its center was an upright black metal needle that was around half a foot in length. As it turned out, this was a sundial.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes as he examined the sundial, and he noticed a faint layer of light surging over it like a gently rippling pond under the delicate light of the moon.

After some observation, Han Li wasn't able to spot any amiss, so he reached out to touch the sundial, but as soon as his hand extended into the indentation that the sundial was sitting in, an unexpected turn of events instantly unfolded!

Chapter 466: Shady Cultivation Art

The black needle on the stone plate shuddered slightly, immediately following which an arc of black lightning shot out like a springing viper to strike Han Li's fingertip.

A burst of sharp pain speared straight into Han Li's soul, and he snapped his hand back as he winced involuntarily.

At this point, the soul fragment in the Soul Nurturing Burner had already recovered some of its strength, and it began to cackle in schadenfreude upon hearing the commotion ringing out within the hall.

However, in the next instant, the Soul Nurturing Burner was swept up by a streak of azure light before being wrenched into the hall.

The soul fragment instantly began to wail in panic and agony as the same burst of golden light rose up from the ground once again.

With a casual sweep of his sleeve, Han Li summoned a spherical light barrier that enveloped the entire Soul Nurturing Burner, and only then did the soul fragment's wailing subside.

"I can't believe I'm at the mercy of a rude little brat like you! Back in the day..."

Before the soul fragment had a chance to finish its sentence, Han Li extended the incense burner toward the sundial on the stone platform as he interjected, "What is this supposed to be?"

"How the hell am I supposed to know? Hey! Hold on, let's be civilized now..."

Once again, before the soul fragment could say anything else, Han Li threatened to withdraw the spherical light barrier, and the soul fragment hurriedly began begging for mercy.

"This is an Extreme Yin Sundial, and it's also the core of this secret area. Only by completely destroying it will you be able to leave this secret area," the soul fragment explained in a deflated voice.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this. "All I have to do is destroy this thing?"

"It's not as easy as it sounds, kid. You're dreaming if you think you can destroy this thing through brute force at your current cultivation base. If you're not careful, the yin lightning backlash from the sundial could easily send you to an early grave!" the soul fragment warned in a solemn voice.

"You were saying earlier that mastering the laws of time or space would be very helpful to breaking the core of this secret area, right?" Han Li asked with a contemplative expression.

"Of course! Time and space are two of the three paramount laws, and normal laws are completely incomparable to them! All spatial barriers and restrictions are built upon the basis of spatial laws, so mastery of spatial laws will allow you to tackle this restriction directly at its roots. As for the laws of time, that's also relevant as the Extreme Yin Sundial is a pseudo-immortal treasure that contains the time law powers," the soul fragment explained.

Han Li's brows instantly furrowed tightly upon hearing this.

During that brief inspection that he had just conducted, he wasn't able to sense any time law powers from the sundial.

"I'll be honest with you, Senior. I just so happen to be cultivating the laws of time, so why is it that I wasn't able to detect any time law powers in this sundial just now?" Han Li asked.

The soul fragment faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a mixture of elation and skepticism appeared in its eyes as it exclaimed, "What did you say? Is that supposed to be a joke? Don't try to fool me! Have you managed to manifest any time law threads? If so, how many?"

"Answer my question first," Han Li said in an expressionless manner.

"Fine, I'll believe you just this once. Honestly, from the moment I first laid eyes on you, I immediately knew you were no ordinary person! My eye for talent is unmatched, and I saw the talent in you right away! As for why you weren't able to detect any time law powers from the Extreme Yin Sundial, that tells me that you've only manifested fewer than five time law threads," the soul fragment said.

"Are you saying my mastery of the laws of time is insufficient?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Let me put it in simple terms for you: even if you're cultivating the laws of time, you'll have to at least be at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage and have manifested at least six time law threads in order to have any chance at destroying the core of this secret area," the soul fragment replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "Truth be told, I've only recently reached the early-Golden Immortal Stage, so it'll take me at least 10,000 years to progress to the mid-Golden Immortal Stage."

"What an impudent little brat you are! You think you can reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage in just 10,000 years? For someone who's cultivating one of the three paramount laws, it'll take you at least a million years to get to the mid-Golden Immortal Stage!" the soul fragment scoffed.

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this. The soul fragment wasn't exaggerating. Indeed, without a supply of suitable pills, Han Li had no idea how long it was going to take for him to reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage.

"Having said that, don't be disheartened. You're extremely fortunate to have met me, and I just so happen to have a way to help you drastically accelerate your cultivation. It's just a matter of whether you have the courage to pursue such a path," the soul fragment said with a hint of provocation in its voice.

"What do I need to do?" Han Li asked.

"The main obstacle to reaching the mid-Golden Immortal Stage is the 24 immortal acupoints that must be opened. These 24 immortal acupoints are far more difficult to open than the 36 immortal acupoints of the True Immortal Stage, but I have a cultivation method that can allow one to channel the power of baleful qi to drastically speed up the process," the soul fragment said.

"Baleful qi? I'm assuming using such a cultivation method will result in a whole host of future complications, right?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm not denying that. That's why this is a matter of courage. Let me finish what I have to say, and after that, you can decide whether you want to pursue this path or not. In essence, baleful qi is just like magic power in that both are inherently present in your body, except baleful qi doesn't show itself under normal circumstances.

“Using this cultivation method will leave residual baleful qi lingering in your immortal acupoints. As for exactly what impact this will have, that varies from person to person, so I can't tell you," the soul fragment explained.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to the soul fragment, and it hurriedly added, "Oh, by the way, there's another downside to using this cultivation method. Just like the Spirit Refinement Technique, this cultivation art is forbidden by the Heavenly Court, so you'll be in a lot of trouble if you run into any immortal envoys in the future."

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

This cultivation art sounded extremely shady, and Han Li was confident that the soul fragment definitely hadn't revealed all of its downsides. As for the fact that it was forbidden by the Heavenly Court, that didn't matter to Han Li as he had already cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique anyway, so it hardly made a difference.

After some contemplation, Han Li asked, "How much will this cultivation art shorten the amount of time that I'll need to reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage?"

"That also varies from person to person. Those with more baleful qi... In other words, those who have killed more will harbor more baleful qi in their bodies, and that'll make it easier for them to open their immortal acupoints using this cultivation art. As for those with less baleful qi, progress won't be as fast.

“You don't look like the type who's done much killing, so I'd guess that your rate of progress will only be sped up by twofold at most. Having said that, this is still a drastic enhancement that you may not be able to achieve even with top-tier pills!" the soul fragment said.

"How can I check how much baleful qi my body harbors?" Han Li asked.

"That's easy. I'll teach you a baleful qi manifestation mantra. Listen up."

With that, the soul fragment recited a peculiar mantra to Han Li, who quickly memorized the mantra before repeating it himself.

As the final syllable of the mantra was uttered, the entire hall shuddered violently, following which plumes of black smoke began to rise up from the top of Han Li's head before spreading through the hall like a black cloud.

Before long, the entire ceiling of the hall was completely concealed behind a dense black cloud that was as dark as ink.

Even then, there was still more and more viscous black qi constantly surging out of Han Li's body.

The soul fragment's mouth had completely gaped open in astonishment upon seeing this, and if it possessed a physical body, its jaw would've most likely already dropped onto the ground!

"This is incredible... How many people have you killed?!" the soul fragment murmured to itself in a flabbergasted voice.

After releasing all of this baleful qi, Han Li was feeling much more relaxed, as if a heavy load had been lifted from his shoulders, but at the same time, a series of wild and aggressive impulses were springing up in his heart.

Han Li suppressed these impulsive urges as he asked, "How is my baleful qi looking?"

"I've seen quite a few people with baleful qi as abundant as yours, but most of them also harbor immense bloodlust, so their baleful qi has a dark red coloration. However, your baleful qi is completely different. Suck pure black baleful qi is an extremely rare sight, and I'm sure that'll help you significantly mitigate the negative side-effects of using this cultivation art of mine," the soul fragment praised.

Han Li nodded in response, then withdrew his hand seal, and the churning black qi around him instantly receded back into his body.

"Why are you in such a hurry to withdraw your baleful qi? You haven't even released all of it yet," the soul fragment complained.

Han Li paid no heed to its complaints as he demanded, "Teach me your cultivation art."

"So you've decided to use it? Don't take this decision lightly," the soul fragment chuckled.

Han Li offered no response to this. He hadn't decided whether he was going to use the cultivation art yet. Instead, he was going to secure it first, then make up his mind on whether he was going to use it later.

After obtaining the cultivation art by the name of the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts from the soul fragment, Han Li returned it to the same hall as before.

In order to help the soul fragment stabilize itself, he left the Soul Nurturing Burner with it as well.

He still didn't know just how much he could trust the soul fragment, but it did seem to know quite a bit about the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace, and a mere soul fragment wasn't going to be able to pose any threat to him anyway, so he decided to keep it around for now.

With that in mind, Han Li arrived in a large secret chamber in the underground palace, and after closing the stone door of the secret chamber, he summoned a stack of array tools and began to set up some restrictions.

Chapter 467: Harnessing Baleful Qi

Close to an hour later, Han Li returned to the center of the secret chamber, then set down a cushion before taking a seat with his legs crossed.

After that, he pulled the storage pouch that had been given to him by Daoist Hu Yan out of a pocket of his robes.

Inside the storage pouch was a white jade slip with golden patterns engraved onto it, and Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip to inspect its contents.

The jade slip contained the fourth level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

In contrast with the second and third levels of the cultivation art, which had led Han Li down a deep rabbit hole searching for that mysterious valley, the fourth level of the cultivation art had been obtained so easily that it almost felt a little surreal to Han Li.

However, it then occurred to him that the broken monument in White Finch Valley was most likely something that Dao Lord Baili had placed there as a red herring to convince people that the Blaze Dragon Dao only had the first three levels of the cultivation art.

As for the jade slip in his hand, just like the first level of the cultivation art that he had received, it was only a replica.

The fourth level of the Mantra Axis Scripture was longer and also more complex than the third level, and it took Han Li over a month of arduous reading to finally read through the entire thing once.

Even after mastering the first three levels of the cultivation art, he had only developed a rough understanding of how the cultivation art worked, but there were still some key points that were outside of his realm of comprehension for now.

However, there was one discovery that he had made that had been very encouraging for him.

Apparently, due to the fact that those who had already mastered the first three levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture had already accumulated a great deal of time law power in their body, once they began cultivating the fourth level, they would be able to actively manifest time law threads.

As for how many time law threads one could attain, that was dependent on how much time law power one had accumulated and how deep their understanding of the laws of time was.

Over the next three months, Han Li didn't immediately begin cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture. Instead, he carefully revised the first three levels, then compared them with the fourth level of the cultivation art.

This was quite a time-consuming process, but it barely yielded any benefits, and Han Li's understanding of the cultivation art on a fundamental level wasn't really deepened at all.

However, this was no surprise to him, and he was already prepared for such an outcome. Seeing as he couldn't' leave this place for now anyway, he may as well work on his cultivation while examining the entire cultivation art again. Perhaps that would reap him some unexpected rewards.

On this day, Han Li meditated for half a day in the secret chamber, then took a cultivation enhancement pill before commencing his cultivation of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

His Mantra Treasured Axis emerged in front of him amid a flash of golden light, and as soon as he caught sight of the axis, a surprised look instantly appeared on his face.

As it turned out, one of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already been restored, much to Han Li's befuddlement.

He had been too busy reading through the Mantra Axis Scripture prior to this, so he had completely failed to notice.

Only less than four months had passed since all of the Time Dao Runes had faded, so theoretically speaking, none of the Time Dao Runes should've recovered yet. Could this be due to the two extra time law threads that he had attained?

The time law threads were very mysterious, and even now, Han Li still had no idea what purpose they could serve. However, if they could accelerate the recovery of his Time Dao Runes, then that was certainly fantastic news.

After taking a moment to settle his own emotions, Han Li began to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture.

He made a hand seal while quietly chanting an incantation, and the Mantra Treasured Axis slowly drifted through the air until it was hovering behind him above his head while giving off dazzling golden radiance.

The golden light that it was radiating instantly filled the entire secret chamber.

......

Over a century passed by in the blink of an eye.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed like a statue, but there was faint golden light all over his entire body.

Some time later, he slowly opened his eyes, and the faint golden light inside them quickly faded.

At this rate, I don't think I'll be able to open an immortal acupoint even after 1,000 years of cultivation. Will I really have to resort to the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts?

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly in hesitation as he mulled over this matter.

After some more contemplation, he decided to seek out another opinion, so he called out to Mo Guang.

The shadow that he cast onto the ground instantly warped slightly before elongating forward, and a shadowy figure emerged from Han Li's shadow before rising to its feet.

After taking so many years to rest and recuperate, Mo Guang had already made a full recovery, and its aura was even superior to back when it was at its peak.

"You've finally called upon me again, Fellow Daoist Han," Mo Guang said with a faint smile, following which its expression changed drastically as soon as it detected the aura emanating from Han Li's body.

Han Li paid no heed to its reaction as he said in an indifferent manner, "I've been through a lot over these past years, and there's never been a suitable opportunity to call upon you. I have a question for you today, and I'm hoping you can help me, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang."

"I didn't think you would already be a Golden Immortal, Fellow Daoist Han. Looks like I've gotten much better than choosing masters since last time. What is it that you want to ask me?" Mo Guang prompted with a smile.

"How much do you know about the Gray Realm?" Han Li asked.

"The Gray Realm? That's always been considered to be a taboo subject in this immortal region, and even Ma Liang didn't get involved much with it back when he was alive. [1] Hence, I'm afraid I don't know much about it. All I know is that it's a realm that's just as vast as the Immortal Realm," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li was a little disappointed to hear this, but he then asked, "What do you know about baleful qi?"

"When it comes to baleful qi, cultivators like yourself should know more than I do. Whenever one engages in the act of killing, baleful qi would naturally form in their body. It's just like how Extrarealm Heavenly Devils like myself can absorb devilish qi through killing. However, baleful qi normally can't be manifested unless someone has accumulated so much baleful qi through slaughter that their baleful qi has gained a substantial form," Mo Guang explained.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, then asked, "Have you heard of any cultivation arts in the Immortal Realm that draws upon baleful qi to advance one's cultivation base?"

"I am aware of the existence of such cultivation arts, but generally speaking, no cultivators would willingly choose to pursue such cultivation arts. I've heard that doing so will impact a certain part of one's cultivation later down the line, essentially placing a bottleneck on oneself and sacrificing one's long-term future for short-term gain," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li was silent for a long while upon hearing this, and Mo Guang also remained silent.

After some time, Han Li looked up at Mo Guang and said, "Thank you for answering my questions, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. I'll summon you for a chat once I'm out of my current predicament."

He then swept a sleeve through the air, and Mo Guang vanished back into his shadow.

"I can't afford to wait tens of thousands of years..." Han Li sighed to himself as he made a strange hand seal, and a vast expanse of baleful qi instantly surged out of his body, inundating the entire secret chamber.

He then began to chant an incantation, and all of the baleful qi that was churning in a chaotic and haphazard manner was suddenly reined in, ceasing their outward expansion before gradually converging into a single cloud.

As a result, the color of the baleful qi was becoming darker and darker, and it was also becoming more and more dense.

As soon as the baleful qi came into contact with Han Li's skin, he was immediately struck by a peculiar feeling that struck a hint of apprehension into his heart, but he didn't stop what he was doing as he continued to guide the baleful qi toward the acupoints in his body.

The baleful qi surged toward an acupoint beneath his ribcage, just like magic power would, and the acupoint immediately displayed signs of loosening in the face of the violent influx of baleful qi.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately closed his eyes to focus on his cultivation.

Some time later, a faint pop rang out from within Han Li's body, immediately following which a tiny vortex emerged beneath his ribcage, and the vortex began drawing in all of the surrounding world's origin qi in a frenzy.

Close to a minute later, a speck of golden light emerged on that spot on Han Li's body, signaling the opening of his 37th immortal acupoint!

Han Li inspected the immortal acupoint momentarily to find that not only was it filled with a vast volume of immortal spiritual power, there was also a wisp of black baleful qi inside, but it was very faint in color and didn't appear to be all that harmful.

Han Li was slightly reassured to see this, and with a sweep of his sleeve, he brought his Mantra Treasured Axis around until it was hovering in front of him.

Not only had quite a few of the Time Dao Runes on the axis already recovered, two more Time Dao Runes had emerged on its surface, taking the total to 362.

It seemed that the Time Dao Rune limit had been lifted once again, so perhaps he would be able to keep adding Time Dao Runes to his Mantra Treasured Axis using the time crystals manifested by his Heaven Controlling Vial, but that was something that he was going to save for a later date.

With that in mind, Han Li switched to a different hand seal to inject some immortal spiritual power into his Mantra Treasured Axis. The axis immediately began to glow radiantly while releasing layers of golden ripples, and it appeared to be no different from before.

During the next two days, Han Li paused in his cultivation and spent that time carefully examining his own internal condition, and only after confirming that there was nothing amiss did he recommence his cultivation.

......

Over 1,000 flew by in a flash.

On this day, gusts of ferocious wind suddenly began to sweep over the ruined city, and tremendous volumes of the world's origin qi converged toward a garden in the city.

Before long, a vortex that hung over the entire city had taken shape in the sky, and it was like an all-encompassing funnel that was directing all of the world's origin into a large black hole in the garden in a frenzy.

The surging world's origin qi instantly filled the entire hole, flowing into a secret chamber deep in the underground palace like a vast, never-ending river.

[1]. Ma Liang was Mo Guang's former master, and the latter pledged their allegiance to Han Li after he killed Ma Liang in battle.

[Back]

Chapter 468: Spirit Domain

At this moment, the entire secret chamber was filled with a churning sea of murky golden light.

Cloaked in the golden light, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed at the center of the secret chamber, and all that could be seen of him was a blurry outline.

Immense world's origin qi converged from all directions, swirling around the center of the room to form a powerful vortex, causing all of the restrictions that Han Li had set up to sway and ripple incessantly.

Only after several hours did the disturbance gradually begin to subside, and right at this moment, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he let loose a thunderous roar.

Beams of bright golden light shot out of his pupils, lingering for a long while in the air without fading.

Some time later, he exhaled before immediately inhaling again, and all of the golden light in the entire secret chamber instantly converged together before being sucked into his belly.

Immediately thereafter, a speck of golden light appeared beneath his throat. The speck of golden light was extremely bright, and it was constantly absorbing the lingering world's origin qi in the surrounding area.

With that, the final immortal acupoint required to reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage had been opened.

Right at this moment, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis flew around from behind him until it was hovering in front of him, and it was radiating dazzling golden light, as were all of the Time Dao Runes on its surface, of which there were now more than 400.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as the golden light in his eyes faded, and he made a beckoning motion, upon which six time law threads instantly shot out of his Mantra Treasured Axis toward the palm of his hand.

Right before they struck his hand, the time law threads drew to an abrupt halt, then curled around his fingertips momentarily before falling onto the palm of his hand.

Through this latest bout of arduous cultivation, Han Li had managed to manifest three more time law threads.

He had thought that he would be able to manifest at least one more time law thread now that he had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, but that didn't turn out to be the case.

Over the course of the past 1,000 years, he had constantly been immersed in cultivation, and he had only awakened three times.

Each of those times came immediately after a state of enlightenment, which led to the formation of a time law thread, seemingly completely by chance.

With each additional time law thread that he attained, his understanding of the laws of time also seemed to have deepened, and as always, any bottlenecks that he encountered during the course of his cultivation of the Mantra Axis Scripture were simply resolved on their own, resulting in very smooth progress.

For a mortal, 1,000 years could span the course of several dynasties, yet for a cultivator, it was essentially only an instant. It was said that there were some immortals using special cultivation arts that could sleep for extraordinarily long periods of time, and even a nap for them could be thousands of years.

Hence, Han Li was astonished that he had managed to reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage so quickly, and he was amazed by just how effective the Profound Baleful Spirit Arts had been.

Of course, at the same time, he was also feeling a little uneasy. After all, channeling baleful qi to accelerate one's cultivation was sure to come with negative side-effects. However, aside from the wisps of baleful qi in his immortal acupoint, which he was unable to eradicate, despite his best efforts, it seemed that there were no other negative side-effects.

Given the current situation, he could only hope for the best. Now that he had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, he finally stood a chance of leaving this place, and everything else would just have to wait until after he made his escape.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately rose to his feet, then withdrew all of the surrounding restrictions before leaving the secret chamber.

Upon arriving at the hall where the soul fragment was situated, even before entering the hall, Han Li could already hear the soul fragment mumbling to itself.

As he stepped into the doorway, Han Li caught sight of the soul fragment hovering in mid-air, talking to its own statue.

"I was so graceful and handsome back in the day. Not only was I an immortal lord, just the title of the Boundless Daoist was enough to have countless beautiful celestial maidens clamoring over me. How long have I been trapped in here? I'm sure all of my past lovers would've been distraught at my disappearance..."

Han Li was struck by the urge to roll his eyes in exasperation, and he cleared his throat to alert the soul fragment to his arrival as he said, "Looks like you're recovering quite well, Senior. You're certainly much more energetic than when I first saw you."

The soul fragment immediately turned around to look at Han Li with a surprised expression, following which an ecstatic look appeared on its face.

The soul fragment then began counting on its fingers as it exclaimed, "How could this be? It's only been just over 1,000 years and you've already reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage? This is preposterous! Unless..."

"Unless what?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly, thinking that there was something wrong.

The soul fragment looked up at him with a serious expression as it said, "Unless you're also an unmatched prodigy like myself!"

Han Li was instantly rendered speechless upon hearing this.

"I came here to bid you farewell, Senior. Now that I've become a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator, I'll be able to leave this place. As for that Soul Nurturing Burner, it's not anything precious, so you can keep it as a parting gift," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute, then prepared to turn and leave.

However, he was immediately interrupted by an urgent cry from the soul fragment.

"Hey, aren't you going to take me with you?" the soul fragment yelled as it flew around to position itself in front of Han Li.

"When did I ever say I was taking you with me?" Han Li asked with a faint smile.

"You ungrateful little..."

The soul fragment's voice abruptly cut off here, and it didn't dare to hurl any insults at Han Li for fear of retaliation.

Han Li was completely unbothered as he raised an eyebrow, seemingly encouraging the soul fragment to continue.

The soul fragment immediately changed tactics, putting on a pitiable expression as it said, "At the very least, I told you the way out, so you can't just leave me here. Besides, once you destroy the core of this secret area, this underground palace will most likely be destroyed, so how am I supposed to survive?"

Han Li intentionally put on a contemplative expression, as if he was hesitating about how to proceed.

After a brief silence, he said, "I suppose you're right. How about this? You teach me how to manifest a spirit domain, and I'll take you with me."

The soul fragment was immediately struck by the urge to slap itself.

It had boasted to Han Li earlier that it had taught Mo Yu how to manifest a spirit domain, and only now did he come to realize that Han Li had most likely been plotting this well in advance.

"I can teach you how to manifest a spirit domain, but what if you change your mind?" the soul fragment asked with a serious expression.

"If you have doubts about my character, then I suppose we'll just have to part ways. I don't want to force you to do anything against your will," Han Li replied with a casual shrug.

"You... You... Fine, you win! I'll do as you say," the soul fragment sighed in a resigned manner.

" A wise decision, Senior!" Han Li praised with a faint smile.

The soul fragment was still feeling quite exasperated, and it asked in a sullen voice, "What do you know about spirit domains?"

"Not much, I'm afraid. Please start from the basics, Senior," Han Li replied.

The soul fragment rolled its eyes upon hearing this, then continued, "I'm sure you've already witnessed your fair share of spirit domains in the past. Essentially, spirit domains are a manifestation of the effect that a cultivator has on the environment around them once they've mastered a certain type of law power. The size and potency of the spirit domain is directly correlated to the cultivator's level of mastery over law powers."

"Can a spirit domain only be unleashed after mastering a certain type of law power?" Han LI asked.

He recalled that back in the Spirit Realm, Bao Hua was able to unleash a spirit domain even without mastering any law powers.

"Mastery over law powers is a prerequisite to whether one can unleash a spirit doman, but that's not set in stone. Cultivators who haven't mastered law powers can unleash spirit domains through the use of certain special treasures coupled with special cultivation arts. However, those spirit domains are nothing but low-quality counterfeits with many fatal flaws, and they can't even begin to compare with true spirit domains," the soul fragment explained.

"I see. Seeing as law power is so integral to spirit domains, is law power also required to maintain a spirit domain?" Han Li asked.

"That's correct. Furthermore, the stability and the power of a spirit domain is also correlated to how advanced the cultivator's mastery over law power is. The more law threads you possess, the more powerful your spirit domain should be," the soul fragment replied.

As the conversation continued, the soul fragment imparted more knowledge pertaining to spirit domains upon Han Li, and in the end, the soul fragment concluded, "The cultivation art that I'm about to teach you has no name. It's one of the most common spirit domain manifestation methods in the Immortal Realm, and it's a method that's both very prevalent and very safe. Listen carefully."

With that, it began to recite the mantra of the cultivation art to Han Li.

The soul fragment was making this cultivation art sound very mundane, as if it were something that one could easily find at any streetside stall, but that was only the case for a High Zenith cultivator as he had been in the past. For someone of Han Li's current cultivation base, such a cultivation art was much more difficult to come by.

Back when he was cultivating in the Blaze Dragon Dao, he had tried to search for cultivation arts of this nature, and there were some in the inner sect, but they could only be accessed by those at or above the Golden Immortal Stage. He was also able to find certain spirit domain manifestation cultivation arts in the Transient Guild, but all of them were being sold at an extremely lofty price.

"Have you memorized all of it?" the soul fragment asked.

"I have. It doesn't seem very difficult, but I'll have to give it a try first to find out," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I knew you wouldn't believe me until you've given the cultivation art a try," the soul fragment grumbled in a disgruntled voice.

"It shouldn't take too long, so please wait here for me for a bit longer," Han Li said with a smile, then departed from the hall, leaving the soul fragment behind to continue mumbling to itself.

Chapter 469: 2,000 Years in an Instant

Several more years flew by in a flash.

At this moment, Han Li was making his way slowly into a hall in the underground palace while holding a dark purple incense burner in his hand.

Traces of golden light emerged on the ground in the hall, giving off a faint hint of warmth.

"Please pardon me, Senior, but I'll have to seal this Soul Nurturing Burner for your protection while I break the core," Han Li said as he drew to a halt at the center of the hall.

Perhaps the soul fragment was simply very eager to be finally getting out of this place, or perhaps it was already accustomed to the disrespect that Han Li constantly directed toward it. In any case, it didn't say anything to retaliate, merely sitting with its legs crossed in the incense burner in silence.

With a flick of his wrist, Han Li summoned a pair of golden sealing talismans before plastering them across the incense burner, completely cutting off the soul fragment's connection to the outside world.

After that, he raised his left hand and tucked the incense burner up his sleeve.

He then took a deep breath before making his way over to the stone platform at the center of the hall, where the sundial was sitting.

In contrast with the last time he was here, this time, he could clearly sense the time law powers contained within the sundial.

The sundial's time law powers remained as still as the surface of tranquil lake when undisturbed, but now that Han Li was inspecting it with his spiritual sense, it immediately began to churn like a turbulent river.

Han Li was slightly taken aback by this, and he made a hand seal, upon which his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

He then closed his eyes as he made a hand seal, and a beam of golden light shot out of the Eye of Truth at the center of the axis, heading straight for the Extreme Yin Sundial.

Even before the beam of golden light completely descended upon the sundial, it suddenly shuddered slightly before rising up into the air.

At the same time, the black needle at its center began to revolve rapidly while blasting forth an arc of black lightning to clash against the beam of golden lightning.

A loud crackling sound rang out as the beam of golden light was shattered into a flurry of golden powder that encompassed the entire stone platform.

A resounding boom instantly rang out in Han Li's mind, and he entered the same special state that he had been in while manifesting his past time law threads.

However, this time, instead of having his senses heightened, an illusion was displayed to him.

All of the sudden, the golden powder formed by the shattered beam of golden light swept upward like a golden river to swallow up his entire body.

He felt as if he were flying through a river of time, and there were translucent golden threads constantly passing him by. He desperately wanted to grasp onto these threads, but each time he tried, he would simply grasp onto empty air.

His agitation was growing by the second, and he unconsciously began to channel his Mantra Axis Scripture. As a result, the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him began to revolve, while all of the Time Dao Runes on its surface lit up in unison.

Situated within the river of time, a burst of golden light appeared over Han Li's hand as he reached out again, and this time, he was able to grab onto one of those golden threads, which was none other than a time law thread.

Han Li was ecstatic, and he immediately reached out toward another golden thread.

As soon as a second time law thread fell into his grasp, the entire river of time instantly became extremely fast-flowing and turbulent, making Han Li feel as if he were drowning, and even breathing had become a struggle.

He began to struggle with all his might, but was unable to free himself from the powerful current.

Right at this moment, a massive golden wave came sweeping directly toward him, and all of a sudden, Han Li arrived at a decision.

A steely look appeared in his eyes as he charged directly at the oncoming wave while reaching out with both hands toward two more golden threads within the wave.

With that, two more time law threads fell into his grasp, and the entire river of time completely fell apart with an earth-shattering boom.

Almost at the exact same moment, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and he was gasping for air.

He looked down at his hands to find that they were completely empty, and a hint of disappointment appeared in his eyes.

However, he then suddenly detected something, and he immediately turned to his Mantra Treasured Axis to find that there were now 10 time law threads wrapped around it!

As it turned out, that illusion hadn't been an illusion at all, and he had obtained four additional time law threads in the blink of an eye!

Han Li was naturally ecstatic, and he returned his attention to the stone platform.

At this point, the Extreme Yin Sundial had already returned to the slot inside the stone platform, and the black needle at its center was still rapidly revolving, but the markings around the sundial that indicated the 24 hours of the day had become extremely blurry and were completely indistinguishable.

Han Li made a hand seal once again, and another beam of golden light shot out of the Eye of Truth, releasing formidable time law power fluctuations as it surged into the indentation on the stone platform.

This time, the Extreme Yin Sundial displayed no reaction. Instead, a series of golden patterns lit up on the stone platform, then began to spread like a system of cobwebs, instantly filling the entire ground in the hall before extending to every single corner of the underground palace.

Before long, golden patterns began to spread over the ruined city outside of the underground palace as well, basking the entire secret area in a golden glow.

All of a sudden, Han Li reached out with both hands to grab onto the edge of the stone platform, then injected his time law power into it in a frenzy. At the same time, the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis began to fade one after another.

A faint crack rang out, and a series of thin cracks began to appear over the surface of the stone platform, spreading outward in all directions alongside the golden patterns.

At the same time, countless tiny black lines began to appear in the space around Han Li, and they intertwined with one another in a chaotic fashion. As the Time Dao Runes on Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis faded one after another, these black lines continued to grow thicker and more concentrated.

A solemn look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately began holding his breath while his True Extreme Film appeared over his body.

Right at this moment, the 60th Time Dao Rune on his Mantra Treasured Axis faded, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as the entire secret area began to tremble violently.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as a radiant golden sun with a diameter of around 10 feet emerged up ahead, releasing blinding golden radiance before exploding violently.

Amid the eruption of golden light, all of the surrounding black lines instantly became warped and misshapen, then converged toward the center incessantly to form an enormous black vortex that was releasing boundless suction force, sucking in everything within the secret area.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, he was also wrenched into the vortex like a tiny raft in a turbulent sea.

......

The entire world spun around him for a moment, following which he stumbled out into the open, and he quickly inspected his surroundings, upon which a stunned look appeared on his face.

He discovered that he was standing in front of a golden palace, and the gates of the palace were behind him, while none other than Lu Yuqing was standing nearby, staring at him with her mouth slightly agape in shock.

In the distance, a girl with golden hair who appeared to be around eight or nine years of age was locked in a standoff against a barefoot silver-robed woman.

Around the woman was a ring of gray light that was several hundred feet in size, while above her was a massive dragon head projection with its cavernous mouth wide open. A pillar of three-colored light was blasting out of its maw, while the girl's arms had exploded to form a pair of translucent threads that swept toward the oncoming pillar of three-colored light.

The two combatants were none other than Jin Tong and Qu Ling, and this was the exact same scene that Han Li had left behind prior to entering the golden palace over 2,000 years ago!

The only thing that was different was that the layer of golden light around the golden pattern had become a little dim and was no longer as radiant as before.

What's going on...

He had spent over 2,000 years inside that palace, yet it seemed nothing had changed in the outside world.

At this point, everyone else had also already noticed Han Li, and they were also very surprised to see him.

Lu Yuqing was just about to say something when the two translucent golden threads finally clashed against the pillar of three-colored light in the distance with an earth-shattering boom.

A burst of blinding light erupted forth as the entire sky was split in half, with one half filled with radiant three-colored light, while the other half was inundated by dazzling golden radiance.

The two halves of the sky clashed violently against one another, and the entire space rumbled violently. In particular, the space where the two intersected was warping violently, looking as if it could shatter at any moment.

Everything on the ground below instantly melted away like snow under the scorching sun under the vast expanse of light, and the ground was also rapidly melting.

An alarmed look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face upon seeing this, and she hurriedly flew to a safe distance away as a streak of azure light.

In contrast, Han Li remained still on the spot as he conjured up his True Extreme Film, and at the same time, 36 specks of bright starlight emerged over his body.

Beams of light fell upon his True Extreme Film to produce an ear-splitting grating noise, and the True Extreme Film began to tremble slightly, but it displayed no signs of breaking or being worn down.

Han Li looked up at the sky with an intense, unblinking gaze as the pillar of three-colored light became brighter and brighter, rapidly overwhelming the opposing translucent threads.

A grim look appeared on Jin Tong's face upon seeing this, and she let loose a delicate roar as a new pair of arms emerged to replace the ones that had just exploded, but these new arms were semi-transparent.

She thrust the palms of her hands through the air, and two bursts of translucent golden light shot forth before transforming into another pair of translucent golden threads.

The pair of translucent threads crossed over one another to oppose the pillar of three-colored light, but the latter was still advancing forward with unstoppable force, and the situation was quickly turning dire for Jin Tong.

Chapter 470: Intervention

Han Li could see that Jin Tong was being overwhelmed, and he immediately vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared right beside Jin Tong as if by instantaneous teleportation, and a glowing golden fist shot out of his sleeve like lightning.

The fist looked as if it had been carved out of radiant gold, and it was riddled with countless golden runes.

A pillar of golden light that was as thick as a bucket erupted out of the fist with countless golden runes flashing within it, and it was giving off bursts of fearsome time law power fluctuations.

The pillar of golden light clashed against the pillar of three-colored light with a resounding boom, and the nearby space shuddered violently as a series of ripples spread through the surrounding area.

Much to Jin Tong's relief, the pillar of three-colored light was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, but as she turned to Han Li, a stunned look instantly appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "Your cultivation base..."

Qu Ling was also scrutinizing Han Li intently from afar, and she was just as incredulous to sense the enormous Golden Immortal Stage aura that was emanating from his body.

Han Li loosened his fist before pointing a finger forward, and a near-transparent golden thread instantly appeared within the pillar of golden light.

The golden thread was quite similar in appearance to the translucent threads unleashed by Jin Tong, but this one was clearly more powerful and was giving off incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations.

As soon as the golden thread appeared, the entire sky instantly dimmed in contrast.

The golden thread shot through the air, appearing much like an extremely thin streak of golden sword qi, leaving a long tail of golden radiance behind it.

In the blink of an eye, it vanished into the pillar of three-colored light before piercing directly toward Qu Ling, and the pillar of three-colored light was being rapidly destroyed.

Jin Tong immediately pounced on this opportunity, making a hand seal to release two more translucent threads that also hurtled directly toward Qu Ling.

In the face of the three law threads, the pillar of three-colored light fell away even faster, and most of it disintegrated in the blink of an eye like a mountain in an avalanche.

Qu Ling's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she immediately shot back in retreat.

All of a sudden, Han Li pointed a finger forward, and the thin golden thread abruptly vanished into thin air.

In the next instant, the space in front of Qu Ling buzzed slightly as the golden thread reappeared without any warning.

Countless bright golden ripples were sweeping out of the golden thread, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area with a radius of several hundred feet, and Qu Ling was caught in the ripples as well.

As a result, she was instantly slowed down significantly. Even though she was still flying back, she was suddenly doing so at less than a tenth of her original speed, much to her alarm and astonishment.

In contrast, the golden thread didn't slow down in the slightest as it continued to hurtle directly toward her.

Qu Ling's expression changed drastically as countless patterns that resembled scales appeared over her entire body.

Plumes of gray mist surged out of these patterns, and the law power fluctuations emanating from this gray mist was completely unaffected by the golden ripples as they enveloped her entire body to form a dense gray cloud that was several dozen feet in size.

The gray cloud had only just taken shape when the thin golden thread vanished into it in a flash, and the cloud was instantly sliced into two, only to immediately fuse back together again.

A muffled groan rang out from within the gray cloud, following which a section of an arm fell out from within, and it was still bleeding profusely.

After slicing through the gray cloud, the golden thread continued to fly onward for several thousand feet before finally stopping.

At the same time, the gray cloud abruptly began to churn violently while radiating dazzling gray light, and it was able to struggle free from the golden ripples before flying to several thousand feet away in a flash.

All of this had transpired in the blink of an eye, so Han Li didn't have a chance to stop her, and his brows furrowed slightly as he made a beckoning motion, upon which the golden thread flew back to him in a flash like a spirit snake before vanishing into his body.

Immediately thereafter, the gray cloud began to churn even more violently while rapidly swelling to several thousand feet in size, and Qu Ling's furious voice rang out from within it. "I didn't think you were hiding your cultivation base. I'll admit that you managed to fool me, but don't think that you've got the better of me! I've lost count of how many Golden Immortals I've killed, and you'll be the latest addition to the list!"

A burst of tremendous law power fluctuations erupted out of the gray cloud before spreading in all directions, and all of the surrounding world's origin began to churn and buzz, while a series of ripples that were visible even to the naked eye surged through the nearby space.

Enveloped within this burst of law power fluctuations, Han Li was immediately struck by a sense of feebleness, and a sense of panic also welled up in his heart, as if he had fallen into a nightmare that he was unable to wake up from.

Jin Tong's brows also furrowed slightly as her complexion paled slightly.

Han Li quickly made a hand seal, and a burst of golden light erupted out of his body, forming a golden light barrier that encompassed both himself and Jin Tong.

Bursts of time law powers were surging through the golden light, keeping the law powers released by the gray cloud at bay, and the feebleness and inexplicable panic that Han Li was experiencing instantly faded, while Jin Tong's expression also eased slightly.

"You go and rest, I'll take care of her on my own," Han Li said as he turned to Jin Tong.

"Mind your own business! This bitch imprisoned me for so long, I've been plotting her downfall this entire time! She may be strong, but there's no way she can break through my defenses. I'm more than capable of taking her down on my own, but I suppose I'lll give you a chance to redeem yourself," Jin Tong harrumphed as she raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, and the pair of translucent threads flew back into her body.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he made no attempt to argue with Jin Tong as he turned his attention back to the gray cloud in the distance.

The law power fluctuations emanating from the gray cloud were very similar to those from the spirit domain from before, but also slightly different.

It seemed that she had mastered several types of laws and was able to switch between them at will.

However, Han Li was now a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator, and not only had his physical prowess been significantly enhanced thanks to his complete mastery of the Great Universe Origin Arts, his body was also brimming with tremendous immortal spiritual power, so he didn't fear Qu Ling at all.

Right at this moment, the gray cloud churned momentarily before suddenly fading away to reveal a gray dragon that was several thousand feet in length, giving off an immense aura.

There was not a single scale on the dragon's body, but it was riddled with countless thick hooked spikes, and there were several particularly enormous bone spikes on its back, resembling a series of huge spears. The dragon's claws also resembled giant swords, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

I knew it!

A hint of excitement appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of the gray dragon.

"Looks like you've figured it out as well. Qu Ling's true body is the true spirit, Nightmare Dragon, and her bloodline is quite pure, so she's not going to be easy to defeat. You better redeem yourself! I'm not gonna follow someone who gets beaten by the same person twice!" Jin Tong scoffed with a disdainful look in her eyes.

After that, she turned and flew away into the distance to observe the battle from afar.

Meanwhile, Han Li cast his gaze toward the Nightmare Dragon in the distance, and he instantly shot forward through the air as a streak of golden light.

In response, two balls of gray flames appeared within the Nightmare Dragon's eyes, and it opened its mouth to release a gray fireball the size of a house in retaliation.

The gray fireball was giving off scorching heat interspersed with bursts of tremendous law power fluctuations, causing the surrounding space to ripple violently.

Han Li's expression remained completely unchanged, and he swept a hand through the air to release a dazzling streak of azure light, which transformed into a giant azure sword.

The giant azure sword was giving off huge streaks of azure sword qi that threatened to tear the surrounding space to shreds, while thick arcs of golden lightning surged over the blade of the sword.

The nearby world's origin qi erupted into a frenzy as countless specks of five-colored light emerged, then fused together to transform the entire nearby space into a vast expanse of chaos.

Now that Han Li had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, using his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords no longer placed much of a strain on him, and he was able to unleash its true power.

Han Li made a hand seal, and the giant azure sword swept through the air to stroke the giant gray fireball, slicing it in half with ease.

Han Li flew straight through the split fireball, only for two bursts of light, one black and one white, to shoot out of the two halves of the gray fireball like lightning, sweeping toward Han Li from two different directions.

The burst of white light transformed into a giant white python that was several hundred feet in length, and it opened its mouth to release a cloud of white mist that was giving off fearsome glacial qi that was interspersed with countless snowflakes and white ice spikes.

In the blink of an eye, the white mist formed a circular area of white ice and snow, and it descended from the heavens to completely inundated Han Li.

Meanwhile, the burst of black light transformed into an inky black fish of comparable size. Its body was long and thin and covered in black spots, and its mouthful of sharp fangs gave it an extremely fearsome appearance.

Arcs of black lightning were springing out of the black spots all over the black fish's body amid rumbling thunderclap, and they intertwined to form a forest of black lightning that also completely swallowed up Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Concealed within the fireball, the pair of beasts had managed to get extremely close to Han Li and execute all of this in an instant.

The white cloud and the forest of black lightning resembled a pair of enormous millstones with Han Li caught between them, and both were giving off tremendous law power fluctuations that threatened to crush Han Li into powder alongside his nascent soul.

Chapter 471: Battle of Domains

In the distance, the Nightmare Dragon remained completely still as it observed the unfolding scene with gray light flashing incessantly in its eyes.

Right at this moment, a tiny speck of golden light suddenly emerged at the center of the black and white millstone, and it was as minuscule as a firefly, but also very eye-catching.

In the blink of an eye, the speck of golden light began to rapidly expand while spreading outward, and countless golden ripples began to surge throughout the surrounding area, giving off a vast law aura.

The white ice and black lightning were both instantly slowed down significantly upon making contact with this golden light, which continued to expand rapidly, encompassing an area that was over 10 kilometers in size in the blink of an eye to form a massive golden area.

The Nightmare Dragon's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and it instantly flew back to several dozen kilometers away, just barely avoiding the fate of being encompassed within the golden spirit domain.

However, the white python and the black fish weren't able to react as quickly, and they were also swallowed up in the golden area, with their movements slowing down significantly.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li shot out of the ice and lightning, completely unscathed.

He then raised a hand before flicking a finger through the air, and two extremely thin strands of golden light instantly shot forth, hurtling directly toward the pair of spirit beasts.

Alarmed and horrified expressions instantly appeared on their faces as they tried to take evasive measures, but the effects of Han Li's time law powers meant that they were far too slow.

The two streaks of golden light flashed over their bodies, and both of them were split into two from head to toe in complete silence.

The two halves of their bodies split apart extremely slowly, and they were still moving in the direction that the two of them had attempted to flee in, while the blood that was gushing out of their wounds was also moving just as slowly.

In contrast, the two threads of golden light were extraordinarily fast, and they vanished into thin air in the blink of an eye before reappearing in front of Han Li an instant later.

One of them was wound around a tiny white snake, while the other was wrapped around a miniature black fish.

The two nascent souls were completely immobilized, as if they had been frozen in time.

In a lightning-fast sequence, two Golden Immortal Stage demon beasts had been slain.

The Nightmare Dragon's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

"Let's not waste any more time with these unnecessary probing gestures, Fellow Daoist Qu Ling. Did you really think these two demon beasts would've been able to harm me at all?" Han Li scoffed as he cast his gaze toward the Nightmare Dragon, and at the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which swept up the pair of nascent souls.

The two nascent souls then instantly vanished from the spot, while the Nightmare Dragon exclaimed in a stunned voice, "This is impossible! If you had a spirit domain of your own, then there's no way you would've been trapped in mine! Unless..."

"Your suspicions are correct," Han Li confirmed with a faint smile. "I really have to thank you, Fellow Daoist Qu Ling."

Up to this point, Han Li was able to confirm that the spirit domain manifestation method taught to him by the soul fragment was real, and it had allowed him to attain his own spirit domain. This was the first time that he was using it, and it had worked exceptionally well.

"What are you saying?" the Nightmare Dragon asked as a hint of fury flashed through its eyes.

"Qu Ling, you tried to take my life with your spirit domain earlier, so let's have our spirit domains clash and see which one comes out on top!" Han Li declared in a cold voice as he flew through the air, and his enormous golden spirit domain followed him like a golden cloud.

In the distance, Jin Tong had pulled out a small gong, and she was beating it in a haphazard manner as she yelled in encouragement, "You can do it, Han Li! Take down that old witch!"

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing was hovering in mid-air while observing Han Li from afar with amazement in her eyes.

He's using the laws of time!

In the next instant, a burst of light flashed over her body, and she vanished into the city down below without attracting any attention.

Meanwhile, radiant gray light had emerged over the Nightmare Dragon's entire body, and it was flying back in retreat, not allowing Han Li's golden spirit domain to come into contact with itself.

At the same time, it raised one of its claws, and the gray cloud up above instantly descended to envelop its entire body.

In the blink of an eye, the gray cloud transformed into a gray spirit domain as well, and it began to expand outward, reaching close to 20 kilometers in size in the blink of an eye. Its spirit domain was close to twice the size of Han Li's, and it swallowed up his spirit domain within it.

An alarmed look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. During their previous battle, the spirit domain that she had unleashed had been far smaller than this. He had guessed that that wasn't the limit of her spirit domain, but he didn't think that it could be expanded so drastically.

Encompassed within the gray spirit domain, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he felt his strength rapidly seeping away, while his immortal spiritual power circulation was also becoming rather sluggish.

He immediately gave a cold harrumph as a golden light barrier appeared over his body. Bursts of time law powers were flowing within the light barrier, alleviating much of the feebleness in his body.

However, in the face of Qu Ling's true spirit domain, even his time law powers were unable to completely ward off the effects of her spirit domain.

While the Nightmare Dragon was flying back in retreat, that gray throne reappeared on the top of its head amid a flash of gray light.

Every single one of the spirit patterns on the gray throne instantly began to radiate dazzling gray light, while the three mirror projections emerged behind it once again.

The first mirror was radiating dazzling golden light, but the other two mirrors were completely dull and devoid of luster.

The Nightmare Dragon pointed a claw at the second mirror before releasing a streak of translucent light, and the second mirror instantly began to glow brightly as well, shooting forth a burst of radiant black light that transformed into a giant black sword before crashing down toward Han Li.

The black sword was giving off a burst of formidable law power fluctuations, the same law power that was able to sow the seed of insanity in the target's heart.

However, as soon as the giant black sword entered Han Li's spirit domain, it was instantly slowed down significantly, and he was able to dodge it with ease.

The Nightmare Dragon's heart sank slightly upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, the golden spirit domain around Han Li suddenly swept back without any warning before vanishing into his body.

Without the protection of his time law powers, a pained look instantly appeared on his face, but he gritted his teeth and withstood it.

The Nightmare Dragon was rather taken aback to see this, but before it had a chance to do anything, Han Li began to chant an urgent incantation, following which his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before beginning to spin in reverse.

Han Li's entire body instantly lit up with dazzling golden light once again, and he shot forward at an incredible speed, leaving a trail of golden afterimages in his wake.

In the blink of an eye, he had covered over half of the distance between himself and the Nightmare Dragon.

The Nightmare Dragon's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and it let loose an alarmed roar, btu right as it was about to do something, the golden light radiating from Han Li's body brightened even further while spreading outward to form his golden spirit domain again in the blink of an eye.

Before the Nightmare Dragon had a chance to take any evasive measures, it was encompassed within Han Li's spirit domain.

As a result, its speed was drastically diminished, and the distance between itself and Han Li was shrinking even more rapidly.

The Nightmare Dragon's expression changed drastically as it opened its mouth to release a pillar of gray light.

Countless runes could be seen flashing within the pillar of gray light, and it vanished into the third mirror behind the gray throne in a flash.

Traces of white light instantly emerged on the surface of the third mirror, and even though the white light was very bright, it was also completely devoid of vitality, much like the bright gleam that a bleached skeleton would emit while being baked under the sun.

The Nightmare Dragon opened its mouth once again to release a ball of gray blood essence, which swelled drastically to form a cloud of gray mist, within which were nine translucent gray threads that wrapped themselves around the three mirror projections.

The three mirrors shuddered in unison while releasing a burst of suction force that suckedd in all of the gray mist in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, three pillars of light that were gray, black, and white in color, respectively, shot out of the mirrors to form dozens of three-colored dragon projections, every single one of which was comparable in size to the Nightmare Dragon, and they were giving off three types of completely different law power fluctuations.

The dozens of three-colored dragon projections instantly pounced at Han Li at the Nightmare Dragon's behest, forming a profound array as they hurtled toward the oncoming Han Li.

Thanks to their special array, the dragon projections were able to move at an extraordinary speed, and even though they were affected by Han Li's golden spirit domain, they weren't much slower than him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he then gave a cold harrumph as he swept a sleeve through their air, and three giant azure swords emerged in front of him.

Each sword was over 1,000 feet in length, and they were radiating dazzling azure light, giving them the appearance of three radiant azure suns.

Incredibly thick arcs of golden lightning emerged over the surfaces of the three giant swords.

Now that Han Li had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, he was able to control three of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once without much trouble.

With a flick of his finger, three time law threads shot forth, and each of them vanished into one of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in a flash.

The three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly drew to an abrupt halt in mid-air, while the azure light that they were radiating became several times brighter, and it was interspersed with blinding golden light.

The thick arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning flashing over the swords also brightened significantly, then transformed into a series of giant lightning runes that revolved around the swords.

The three giant azure swords began to tremble as a burst of sword qi that was several times more formidable than before erupted forth, causing the entire surrounding space to shudder.

In the next instant, the three giant lightning swords released a flurry of lightning sword projections at Han Li's behest, and the sword projections swallowed up all of opposing dragon projections before destroying them in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, Han Li only paused for a moment before continuing to fly forward like lightning, spurred on by his Reversal True Axis secret technique.

Before long, he was no more than several thousand feet away from the Nightmare Dragon.

Chapter 472: Slaying the True Spirit

"It's time to put an end to this!" Han Li declared as he began making a rapid string of hand seals, and dazzling golden light erupted out of his body as the Mantra Treasured Axis abruptly began revolving in the right direction again.

Layers upon layers of golden ripples surged out of the axis, instantly permeating throughout the entire surrounding area in a radius of over 10,000 feet, encompassing the Nightmare Dragon within them.

Everything that was swept up within the golden ripples was instantly immobilized, as if they had been frozen in time, and the same applied to the Nightmare Dragon, which was looking on with its mouth wide open in astonishment.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared beside the Nightmare Dragon in a flash, then revolved around it like lightning.

The Nightmare Dragon's body was instantly sliced into over 10 pieces, but the pieces of its body didn't separate, nor did any blood emerge.

At the same time, a time law thread emerged out of thin air before piercing into the Nightmare Dragon's head in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the time law thread re-emerged while wrapped tightly around a miniature gray dragon, and it was none other than Qu Ling's nascent soul.

A burst of golden ripples surged forth from the time law thread, encompassing the gray nascent soul to ensure that it remained bound.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as he swept a sleeve through the air once again, and his golden spirit domain instantly surged back into his body as a vast expanse of golden light.

The golden ripples around him also flashed momentarily before surging back into the Mantra Treasured Axis, which, in turn, slowly faded away.

Right at this moment, a perplexed look appeared on his face, and his Mantra Treasured Axis reappeared behind him at his behest.

As it turned out, around a dozen more of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had faded, but he had completely failed to notice this earlier.

A hint of surprise flashed through his eyes upon seeing this, and he injected some of his spiritual sense into his Soul Nurturing Burner to inform the soul fragment inside of this situation.

The soul fragment wasn't surprised at all, and it said, "That's only to be expected. You think immortal spiritual power alone would be enough to support an ability as formidable as a spirit domain? Maintaining a spirit domain will require law power expenditure, so it's no surprise that some of your Time Dao Runes have faded."

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Thankfully, now that he had attained 10 time law threads, it wasn't going to take very long to recover these Time Dao Runes.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air, and the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately flew back to him, following which the time law threads inside also vanished into his body.

The golden light radiating from the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly faded, and the aura that was emanating from them also diminished significantly.

Han Li was quite intrigued to see this.

His Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords already possessed tremendous power, yet just the injection of a time law thread was enough to enhance their powers significantly. If he could imbue these swords with law powers that were actually suitable for them, who knew just how powerful they could become?

With that in mind, a hint of excitement instantly welled up in his heart.

He took a deep breath to compose himself, then withdrew the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords up his sleeve.

Even though he had managed to slay Qu Ling without much trouble using his spirit domain in conjunction with his Mantra Treasured Axis, maintaining his spirit domain and using his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had both been quite taxing on his immortal spiritual power.

Even though he had already reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, the immortal spiritual power expenditure had still been quite immense, and he was currently looking a little pale.

The good thing about his spirit domain was that it encompassed quite a large area, but its power was still rather limited, while the golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis covered a far smaller area, but were also significantly more formidable.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce a crimson pill, yet right after he swallowed it, Qu Ling's nascent soul suddenly began to struggle vigorously as dazzling gray light erupted out of its body.

The time law thread around it was beginning to loosen slightly in the face of its struggles.

It seemed that the gray nascent soul had used some type of ability that had granted it immunity to the effects of Han Li's time law powers.

A cold look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger at the gray nascent soul, upon which the time law thread glowed even brighter as it ensnared the gray nascent soul once again.

Right at this moment, the gray nascent soul let loose a piercing shriek, upon which its body swelled rapidly to four or five times its original size.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, while the time law thread around the nascent soul dug deep into its body.

Right as he was about to make a hand seal to completely seal the nascent soul, it abruptly exploded into a burst of gray light that vanished into nothingness.

A blurry dragon projection then shot out of the gray light, and it was none other than Qu Ling's soul. The soul was enveloped within a layer of extremely faint silver light, and it was moving at an astonishing speed, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's brows furrowed even further upon seeing this.

He had thought that Qu Ling's nascent soul would be completely immobilized by his time law thread, so it came as quite a surprise to him that it was able to get away.

It seemed that he had underestimated the power of a Golden Immortal Stage nascent soul.

He shook his head as he withdrew his time law thread.

Even if Qu Ling were a true spirit, only her soul remained at this point, so she wouldn't be able to pose any further threat to him.

Right at this moment, the three-colored spirit domain that Qu Ling had unleashed earlier shuddered a few times before rapidly fading away.

The body of the Nightmare Dragon inside instantly fell apart before falling out of the sky.

With another sweep of his sleeve, Han Li sent an azure bowl flying through the air, and it swelled to around an acre in size in the blink of an eye, catching all of the parts of the Nightmare Dragon's carcass without missing even a single one.

After that, the azure bowl flew back to him at his behest, shrinking as it did so, and by the time it fell onto the palm of his hand, it had already reverted back to its original size.

Han Li took a glance into the bowl, and a pleased look appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to stow it away.

Immediately thereafter, he drew the gray throne that was still hovering in mid-air nearby to himself as well.

After a brief inspection, he stowed the gray throne away too.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong appeared beside him amid a flash of golden light, and the gong that she had been beating earlier was nowhere to be seen.

"How useless can you be, Han Li? You couldn't even stop a nascent soul from self-detonating? What a waste!" Jin Tong grumbled with a displeased look on her face.

"A waste? Why do you say that?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

"Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls are filled with tremendous power, and they're a fantastic food source for me!" Jin Tong grumbled.

Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to produce a white jade box upon hearing this, and the lid of the box flew off on its own to reveal a pair of nascent souls, one black and one white. The two nascent souls belonged to none other than the white python and the black fish that Han Li had slain earlier.

Jin Tong's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the two nascent souls, and she began staring intently at them.

"I was going to use these two nascent souls for something else, but you can eat them to help your recovery," Han Li said as he offered the jade box to Jin Tong.

The displeasure on Jin Tong's face instantly turned to elation upon hearing this, and she swiped the jade box from Han Li as she said, "Looks like you're not a completely ungrateful bastard! Seeing as you're being so sincere, I suppose I can accept this nascent soul."

She took a deep breath, then opened her mouth to release a burst of golden light, which drew in the pair of nascent souls so that she could munch on them, and a blissful look instantly appeared on her round and childish face.

In her mouth, the two near-indestructible Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls were nothing more than a snack, and Han Li was left feeling a little speechless as he looked on with a hint of doting affection in his eyes.

Right at this moment, bursts of golden light emerged over Jin Tong's body, and they rippled like water before surging toward her arms.

Her pair of semi-transparent arms quickly gained a more substantial form, and shortly thereafter, Jin Tong swallowed the pair of nascent souls, then wiped her mouth with the back of her new hand before letting loose a loud burp.

The golden light that was surging over her body quickly faded, and her arms also made a full recovery.

"Looks like Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls really are a good source of sustenance for you," Han Li remarked. "By the way, you've certainly changed a lot since we were last together."

"Do you not like what I look like now? Speaking of Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls, if I had one more, I would be able to completely recover from my injuries. It's all your fault! We could've had three nascent souls if you were more careful!" Jin Tong said, still feeling a little disgruntled.

"Don't worry. Right now, there are many Golden Immortals gathered in the immortal manor. Even if we don't go to them, they'll most likely end up coming to us," Han Li said as he turned his gaze to a certain direction.

"You're saying there are more of them to come? That's great! With my powers and your spirit domain, none of them will be able to get away from us!" Jin Tong said with a confident grin, baring two rows of gleaming white teeth.

"Setting that aside for now, Jin Tong, there's something that I want to ask you," Han Li said as a serious look suddenly appeared on his face.

Jin Tong was rather taken aback by the sudden shift in Han Li's demeanor, and a slightly anxious look appeared on her face as she asked, "What is it?"

"Back when I first ascended to the Immortal Realm, I was forced back into a lower realm after running into a powerful enemy, and due to their law powers, I lost a lot of my memories. Do you still recall what happened to us in the Immortal Realm prior to that?" Han Li asked.

Even though he had learned some things from Tao Yu and Fang Ban, he still hadn't managed to fully piece together what had happened to him following his ascension, and now that Tao Yu's inkstone had been detonated, he had lost his final lead.

For some reason, Han Li really wanted to recover these memories.

"I don't remember anything from that time, either. My memories of the Immortal Realm start from the battle against that guy called Fang Ban. I was able to slay a spirit pet that he sent after me, then circled back around to try and find you, but you were gone.

“After that, I ran into Qu Ling, and she captured me. She was quite good at nurturing spirit pets, so when I was with her, I always had stuff to eat, and my cultivation base improved rapidly. That's why I decided to stay with her and pretend to have been subdued as a spirit pet," Jin Tong replied.

Chapter 473: Tallying the Spoils

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Even though he had managed to recover Daoist Xie and Jin Tong, he still had no idea what had happened during the 300 years immediately after his ascension. Furthermore, with the way that things were progressing, he became more and more convinced that there were some very complex circumstances involved, and that there was a very good chance he had been swept up in some type of conspiracy.

On top of that, he had made quite a few enemies, some that he was aware of, while others were still in the shadows, and most of these enemies were present in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor. Fortunately, he had somehow stumbled into a massive opportunity, allowing him to progress all the way to the mid-Golden Immortal Stage.

With his current cultivation base, he now had the power required to protect himself. As for his lost memories, he would just have to find a way to recover them after he left the immortal manor.

"Let's go and hunt down those Golden Immortals you were talking about, Han Li! That battle against that old witch was really taxing on me!" Jin Tong pouted as she tugged on Han Li's sleeve.

"We should indeed be leaving this place. Also, if you encounter an enemy that you can't defeat in the future, then run away. Don't bite off more than you can chew," Han Li cautioned with a serious expression.

"You're so ungrateful! I did all that to save you!" Jin Tong grumbled in a disgruntled manner.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as a burst of azure light appeared over his body, and he was just about to depart when he swept his gaze over his surroundings with slightly furrowed brows.

In the wake of the battle that had just taken place, the entire area aside from the golden palace had been razed to the ground, so everything was laid bare to Han Li, yet Lu Yuqing was nowhere to be seen.

"Jin Tong, did you notice where the woman who was with me went during my battle against Qu Ling?" Han Li asked.

"What woman? Oh right, that woman... She was observing the battle from afar initially, then suddenly unleashed some type of secret technique to vanish into the ground," Jin Tong replied.

"You're saying she ran away?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"She did. She was with you, so I didn't try to stop her. Otherwise, I could've done so with ease," Jin Tong replied with a wide smile.

Han Li paid no heed to Jin Tong's boastful statement as he stood on the spot in silence, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Jin Tong pouted slightly with displeasure upon seeing this, and she turned her head away, refusing to look at him any longer, but it didn't take long before she began sneaking glances at him again out of the corner of her eye.

Right at this moment, Han Li rose up into the sky, and blue light flashed in his eyes as he scoured his gaze over the surrounding area.

Moments later, the blue light in his eyes faded, but his brows became even more tightly furrowed.

He had just searched through the entire nearby area, but wasn't able to detect the auras of any other cultivators, nor was there any residual aura left behind by Lu Yuqing.

"Are we going or not? I'm starving!" Jin Tong complained as she planted her hands on her hips.

"I'm looking for her because she has an incomplete map of the immortal manor. I was only able to make it to this place thanks to her map," Han Li explained.

What he didn't mention was that he felt like there was something rather strange about Lu Yuqing. In particular, her demeanor and behavior had become increasingly more peculiar after they left the Light Frost Palace, and it was very abnormal that she had suddenly disappeared without leaving any trace behind.

"If we don't have a map, then we'll just have to look on our own. What's the big deal?" Jin Tong retorted with a nonchalant pout.

"You're right, let's go," Han Li replied with a nod, then flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light, while Jin Tong followed along as a streak of golden light.

The two of them flew for close to an hour before stopping near a semi-collapsed palace.

"Let's rest here for a bit," Han Li said as he took a seat in a side hall that was still relatively intact, then swept a hand through the air to release several dozen streaks of blue light to set up a blue array.

Jin Tong sat down beside Han Li, and the latter exhaled before closing his eyes and channeling his cultivation arts to digest the pill that he had taken earlier.

A layer of gentle azure light appeared over his body, while Jin Tong took a glance at him before also closing her eyes to cultivate.

Close to a day passed by before the azure light over Han Li's body faded, and at this point, he had already completely replenished his immortal spiritual power reserves.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong was still enveloped in a layer of golden light, and the spiritual qi around her was constantly streaming into her mouth.

Han Li took a glance at Jin Tong, then withdrew his gaze before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and two objects appeared before him, namely the gray throne and the azure bowl that contained Qu Ling's remains.

Han Li took a glance at the gray throne, then cast an incantation seal into it, and a layer of gray light instantly emerged over the throne, but it wasn't all that bright.

As he continued to cast more incantation seals into the throne, the gray light that it was emanating gradually became brighter, and the three mirror projections slowly emerged, giving off gray, black, and white light, respectively.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this. This gray throne was quite a formidable treasure that was superior to all of the immortal treasures in his possession.

What was even more remarkable was that it contained three completely different types of law power, and that was something that he had never seen before.

It was clearly an extremely powerful treasure, but unfortunately, it was Qu Ling's bonded treasure, and it contained an extremely deep-rooted bonded mark that was impossible to remove.

Even if Han Li could forcibly refine the treasure, he would only be able to unleash 50% to 60% of its power at most.

With that in mind, Han Li heaved a faint sigh before stowing the gray throne away, then turned his attention to the azure bowl.

He made a grabbing motion with one hand, and several streaks of light flew out of the bowl before landing in front of him, revealing themselves to be four small pouches of different colors, a white jade belt with hundreds of gemstones of different colors embedded into it, and a black ring.

All of these items had been carried by Qu Ling, and Han Li hadn't had a chance to examine them yet.

First, Han Li picked up the four little pouches, and after a brief examination, his eyes instantly lit up slightly.

As opposed to storage pouches, these were spirit beast pouches, and they were all quite remarkable. Each of them had massive internal space, and they were essentially miniature secret areas.

Furthermore, each space was filled with extremely abundant spiritual qi and had differing climates and environments.

Refining a spirit beast pouch like this was definitely going to cost no less than what it took to refine a powerful Acquired Immortal Treasure.

However, the four pouches were all completely empty, and Han Li presumed that they had been used to house the Golden Immortal Stage spirit beasts that he had already slain.

A hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he stowed the four pouches away.

Even though he still had no use for them for the time being, they were priceless treasures, and at the very least, he should be able to sell them to cultivators or sects that specialized in nurturing spirit beasts for a large quantity of Immortal Origin Stones.

After that, he picked up the white jade belt, and his eyes immediately lit up once again.

The belt was also an object used to store spirit beasts, and every single gem on the belt was an independent space, containing all types of different spirit beasts.

Some spaces only housed a single spirit beast each, while some housed thousands, even tens of thousands.

However, none of these spirit beasts were all that powerful, and True Immortal Stage ones among them were extremely rare, while most of them were below the Grand Ascension Stage.

Aside from that, each space contained a stone plaque that denoted the special characteristics and uses of the spirit beasts being kept inside. As it turned out, not all of them were meant for battle. Instead, there were also some who specialized in exploration and tracking.

At this point, Han Li had accumulated a vast wealth of experience, but even so, his horizons were significantly broadened as he browsed through this vast catalog of spirit beasts.

However, much to Han Li's surprise and dismay, all of the spirit beasts within the jade belt were dead, and there wasn't even a single one alive.

Furthermore, none of the spirit beasts had any visible injuries, and that made their deaths even more bewildering.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li summoned an azure deer carcass from the jade belt.

The spirit beast had blood flowing out of all of its orifices, and Han Li extended a finger forward to send a speck of azure light vanishing into the deer's head.

Moments later, his brows furrowed slightly, and he summoned another carcass, this time of a white ice silkworm, before repeating the process.

A furious look flashed through his eyes as he determined that all of the spirit beasts had perished due to a type of restriction.

Qu Ling had planted an extremely inhumane restriction in all of their bodies, one that would lead to the deaths of all of these spirit beasts should she ever meet her demise.

Han Li shook his head with a forlorn expression before stowing the jade belt away as well.

This jade belt was most likely even more valuable than the four high-grade spirit beast pouches.

Finally, he picked up the black ring before pressing it against his own forehead, and as soon as he injected his spiritual sense into the ring, an astonished look instantly appeared on his face.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a huge pile of items appeared on the ground, almost filling half of the entire hall.

These items were very diverse, containing everything from spirit plants and materials to ore and treasures, and they were radiating lights of all types of different colors to illuminate the entire hall.

Furthermore, almost every single one of these items contained extremely potent spiritual power.

Han Li had found many treasures after entering the immortal manor, but none of them could even begin to compare with Qu Ling's astonishing collection.

However, some of these items clearly belonged to other cultivators, indicating that she had claimed the lives and treasures of many past victims.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he flipped a hand over to produce a crimson badge, one that belonged to the True Flame Sect.

There were as many as six or seven identical badges in Qu Ling's collection, telling him that all of the True Flame Sect's cultivators had already been slain by her.

Han Li couldn't help but shake his head and heave another forlorn sigh. He wasn't exactly fond of the True Flame Sect's cultivators, but it was still rather saddening to see these temporary allies meeting their demise.

Han Li casually cast the True Flame Sect badges aside, then continued to examine Qu Ling's collection.

A short while later, his eyes lit up as he made a grabbing motion to draw a nearby green gourd into his grasp.

This was none other than the Profound Heavenly Gourd that Qu Ling had used earlier.

Chapter 474: This is Mine!

Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light, which vanished into the green gourd, and a layer of green light instantly appeared over its surface.

The green light was filled with countless tiny runes that were flowing like water while spreading outward, giving off an impression of abundant vitality.

A burst of faint law power fluctuations was also emanating from the gentle green light, and a hint of elation appeared in Han Li's eyes.

It seemed that a faint spiritual connection had been formed between himself and the green gourd.

Han Li slashed a fingernail over one of his fingertips, drawing a drop of blood essence that dripped onto the green gourd, but instead of fusing into the gourd, the drop of blood merely slid down its side.

However, not only was Han Li not disappointed to see this, his eyes lit up instead as he nodded to himself, confirming that this was indeed a Profound Heavenly Treasure.

Even though he once possessed the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, he didn't actually know very much about Profound Heavenly Treasures, and only after arriving in the Immortal Realm did he gradually begin to find some records and scriptures pertaining to Profound Heavenly Treasures.

These treasures were born from heaven and earth, and they were different from normal immortal treasures. One important property of Profound Heavenly Treasures was that they couldn't be refined using blood essence. Instead, they could only be slowly refined over time in one's body using their immortal spiritual power, and this refinement process was going to be a very lengthy one.

In the case of the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, it had been nurtured in Han Li's body for countless years before he was slowly able to wield it.

Furthermore, if the owner of a Profound Heavenly Treasure were killed, and the treasure fell into the hands of someone else, then that person would be able to wield it right away. In contrast, in a normal immortal treasure, the mark of the previous owner had to be removed first before it could be refined again, and even then, there was a chance that the new owner would never be able to tap into the treasure's full power.

Han Li took a deep breath, then pressed the green gourd against his forehead, and he was only just barely able to force a wisp of his spiritual sense into it, upon which a surprised look instantly appeared on his face.

Inside the gourd was a large space that was filled with green light, which was swirling to form an enormous green vortex.

The space deeper within the gourd was rather blurry and indistinct, but there seemed to be something else in there.

Hovering at the center of the green vortex was none other than Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, which Qu Ling had captured earlier, and Han Li was quite relieved to see this.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were his bonded immortal treasures, and if he were to lose one, then that would spell a lot of trouble.

Instead of immediately recovering his flying sword, he continued to extend his spiritual sense deeper into the internal space of the gourd.

However, his spiritual sense had only just reached the edge of the vortex when it was stopped in its tracks by a burst of invisible force.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this, and he tried to force his way through, but to no avail.

It was clear that this invisible barrier couldn't be bypassed using his spiritual sense alone, and he would have to find some other way to break through it. Perhaps this would only be achievable once he refined the gourd to the point that he was able to truly control it.

Of course, it was naturally the case that the more profound this gourd was, the more it would benefit him.

With that in mind, he withdrew his spiritual sense and wrapped it around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword before tugging on it, and the sword immediately flew out of the opening of the gourd.

The azure light emanating from the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword had dimmed a little compared with before, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

However, as he inspected the flying sword's internal condition with his spiritual sense, he discovered that the dimming of the light that it was emanating wasn't due to a reduction in the spiritual power that it contained.

Instead, not only had the enormous spiritual power within the flying sword not diminished at all, the previously rather chaotic and erratic spiritual power had become far purer and more condensed.

A hint of surprise and elation appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he certainly wasn't expecting the gourd to have such an effect.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that vanished into the green gourd, and a burst of green light emerged from the opening of the gourd to latch onto the flying sword and draw it into the gourd again.

After that, Han Li swept his sleeve through the air once again to summon a miniature three-story pavilion, and it was none other than that immortal treasure that he had found earlier in the Light Frost Palace.

The miniature pagoda was sucked into the green gourd as well, and Han Li was eager to test out the gourd's abilities.

After stowing the gourd away, Han Li turned his attention back to the vast collection of items on the ground, and his brows furrowed slightly in contemplation.

There were far too many things laid out on the ground, and he didn't recognize most of them, so it would take at least a day or two for him to sort through them.

After remaining silent for a while longer, Han Li called out to Mo Guang, who immediately emerged from his shadow.

"Can I help you with something, Fellow Daoist Han? Hold on a second... Your cultivation base has advanced yet again! How is this possible? You are truly an unmatched prodigy, Fellow Daoist!" Mo Guang exclaimed upon sensing Han Li's aura.

It then took a moment to inspect its surroundings, and the surprise on its face became even more pronounced at the sight of Jin Tong and the vast array of items on the ground.

Han Li paid no heed to Mo Guang as he swept his sleeve through the air to summon Daoist Xie.

Mo Guang's expression changed slightly once again upon sensing Daoist Xie's aura, and it suddenly felt like everyone was leaving it behind.

Even though it had already returned to its former cultivation base, it was still only at the mid-True Immortal Stage, while Daoist Xie had become a Golden Immortal Stage immortal puppet, and Jin Tong had also reached the Golden Immortal Stage. On top of that, Han Li had gone even further beyond them, reaching the mid-Golden Immortal Stage!

"I just defeated a Golden Immortal just now, and these are her possessions. There's quite a lot of stuff here, most of which I don't recognize, so I need your help to identify all of this stuff," Han Li said.

"I see. That's not a problem. I may be lacking in cultivation base, but I saw many things during my time with Ma Liang," Mo Guang said with a smile.

Daoist Xie also nodded in response, then sat down beside Han Li.

"Please help me organize these items and record their uses in a jade slip so I can identify them easily in the future," Han Li instructed as he pulled out a pair of blank jade slips before handing them to Mo Guang and Daoist Xie.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong made her way over to Han Li, having awakened from her cultivation, and her eyes were sparkling as she exclaimed, "Woah, there's so much good stuff here!"

"Long time no see, Gold Devouring Immortal. With Fellow Daoist Han on your side, I'm sure you'll become a Dao Ancestor and reign supreme over the Immortal Realm someday!" Mo Guang greeted as it cupped its fist in a salute.

"Get away from me, you shady-looking bastard! I can't stand the sight of you!" Jin Tong snapped as her brows furrowed slightly.

The smile on Mo Guang's face instantly stiffened upon hearing this.

"Don't be so rude, Jin Tong. All of us ascended to the Immortal Realm together, and it's very fortunate that we've all been reunited here," Han Li scolded in a stern voice.

Jin Tong took another disdainful glance at Mo Guang, but didn't say anything further, and her attention was instantly drawn back to the vast array of treasures on the ground.

"We've reeled in a massive haul, Jin Tong," Han Li said with a smile.

However, Jin Tong seemed to be completely unable to hear him, and her cheeks bulged as she opened her mouth to release a burst of golden light, sweeping up a set of seven or eight golden flying daggers nearby.

Each dagger was giving off formidable spiritual power fluctuations, clearly indicating that they were spirit treasures of a very high caliber.

The burst of golden light carried the flying daggers into Jin Tong's mouth, and she began to chomp on them with glee, chewing the daggers into pieces before swallowing them.

Both Daoist Xie and Mo Guang were very much taken aback to see this, while Han Li could only give a wry smile.

All of a sudden, a burst of golden light emerged over Jin Tong's body before flowing into her arms to further reinforce them, and her aura was also elevated slightly as a result.

Immediately thereafter, she began looking around once again, and her gaze quickly settled on a heavy silver hammer as she opened her mouth to release another burst of golden light.

The hammer was drawn into her arms, and she cradled it to her chest as she took a bite out of the treasure.

A corner of the hammer was bitten off, and she began humming a blissful tune as she crunched on the piece of hammer like a chunk of crispy radish.

The silver hammer wasn't far off from becoming an immortal treasure, and Han Li raised a hand to stop Jin Tong, but lowered it with a resigned expression in the end.

He then turned to Daoist Xie and Mo Guang and tossed a pair of storage tools at them as he instructed, "Organize everything and stow them away."

The two of them caught the storage tools, then exchanged a glance before quickly commencing their work.

Meanwhile, Han Li swept his gaze over the surrounding area, and something quickly caught his attention. He swept a sleeve through the air in a covert fashion, sneakily drawing a purple saber, a golden net, and a white archway to himself, and he was just about to stow them away when a little hand shot out from beside him like lightning to grab onto the purple saber.

"This is mine!" Jin Tong yelled as she looked up at Han Li.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he stowed the golden net and the white archway away as he negotiated, "There are so many other treasures here, and you can eat as many of them as you like, but these three are immortal treasures. Even if you eat them now, you may not be able to digest them, so I'll give them to you next time, alright?"

"You're so stingy!" Jin Tong complained, displaying no intention of releasing the purple saber.

"Alright, then how about this? You give this saber to me, and I promise you that I'll kill a Golden Immortal for you and feed you their nascent soul," Han Li proposed.

This time, Jin Tong didn't even bother to reply as she opened her mouth and bit down toward the purple saber.

Chapter 475: Courting Death

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, yet right as Jin Tong’s teeth were about to come into contact with the purple saber, she suddenly stopped, then raised her head to grin at Han Li as she asked, "Do your promises count?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "Of course."

A pleased look appeared on Jin Tong's face upon hearing this, and she let go of the purple saber.

Han Li could only give a resigned shake of his head as he stowed the saber away as well, and he was planning to examine the three immortal treasures in closer detail once he left the immortal manor.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed something else, and he swept a sleeve through the air, upon which a length of silver spirit bamboo that was several dozen feet in length and giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations flew toward him.

The silver bamboo had the same aura as the silver bamboo roots that he had dug out of the medicine garden, and beside it were some other precious spirit plants that looked as if they had all been recently picked.

It seemed that the person who had gotten to the medicine garden ahead of him and taken the Profound Heavenly Treasure had been none other than Qu Ling.

In that case, the Profound Heavenly Treasure on that vine had to have been this green gourd.

Close to half a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and all of the items on the ground were finally sorted.

Much to Han Li's elation, Qu Ling was carrying far more treasures than he had anticipated.

Just the Immortal Origin Stones in her possession alone totaled in excess of 100,000, and that was truly an enormous sum comparable to the entire wealth of many large sects.

Aside from that, there were also many precious materials, ingredients, pills, and scriptures, some of which were identified, while others remained a mystery.

However, most of the low-grade spirit treasures in Qu Ling's collection had been devoured by Jin Tong.

At this point, her aura had already swelled to beyond its former peak, while her arms had also fully recovered, and there was a blissful look on her face.

Even now, Jin Tong was still just as greedy an eater as ever. However, this was a unique mode of cultivation, so while it pained Han Li to have to part with all of those spirit treasures, it was a bittersweet feeling, overall. After all, it was definitely a good thing for him to see Jin Tong attain more power.

"Thank you for your hard work, fellow daoists," Han Li said as he turned to Mo Guang and Daoist Xie.

"Our lives are interconnected, so there's no need to thank me. Feel free to call upon me again if you need me, Fellow Daoist Han," Mo Guang said with a smile as it vanished back into Han Li's shadow.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this. Mo Guang was behaving very differently from in the past.

As for Daoist Xie, it merely cupped its fist in a salute toward Han Li in silence, then vanished into his body as a streak of golden light.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li emerged from the hall, and after taking a moment to inspect his surroundings, he suddenly looked down at a blue scroll that he was holding.

This was Qu Ling's Infernal Frost Scenic Painting.

However, at this moment, the artwork was completely dull and devoid of luster, looking as if it were nothing more than a normal painting.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he examined the artwork for a moment longer before stowing it away.

"Let's go," he said to Jin Tong, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light that swept up both of them before flying away.

......

Somewhere in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor.

There were three Southern Dawn beings making their way down a bluestone path that was overgrown with weeds in a set of severely ravaged palatial ruins, and all of them were looking quite weary.

"Wyrm 3 really got us good this time! He convinced us to enter this immortal manor, but we've run into far more peril than treasures! If you ask me, I think he coaxed us into coming in here to act as cannon fodder for him!" a short, dark-skinned woman grumbled in a disgruntled voice.

"I agree. You both saw how fast he ran away as we were exploring that palace earlier! He didn't care at all whether we lived or died, and now, he's completely disappeared," a burly man with a pair of bushy eyebrows chimed in.

"There's no point in saying things like now. Thankfully, the three of us weren't split up. I think we should take this as an opportunity to part ways with Wyrm 3 and search for treasures on our own, then leave the immortal manor once time's up," the final member of the trio, a thin elderly man, said as he stroked his own goatee.

The other two Southern Dawn beings nodded in agreement.

Right as they were conversing with one another, a green jade flying carriage suddenly flew past in the sky, then circled around before drawing to a halt above the three of them.

Standing on the flying carriage was a tall and refined-looking middle-aged man, playing with a white jade Pixiu that was giving off a warm and slightly yellow glow. [1]

Standing behind him were two men clad in suits of golden armor, but their wooden expressions and lifeless auras indicated that they were nothing more than a pair of puppets.

The three Southern Dawn beings took a glance at the man on the flying carriage, and a hint of wariness flashed through their eyes, but they were all feeling a bit more reassured upon sensing the man's late-True Immortal Stage cultivation base.

"Greetings, fellow daoists. Have any of you seen the cultivators of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace?" the middle-aged man asked with a friendly smile on his face.

None of the Southern Dawn beings immediately replied, but they were feeling a little disgruntled.

While it was true that the middle-aged man was speaking in quite a friendly tone, there was a frustrating aura of superiority and condescension that he was exuding despite his lowly cultivation base.

"No," the thin elderly man replied.

None of the people who had entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor would be so foolish as to judge one's power based solely on the cultivation base that they were displaying, so the trio decided to adopt a cautious approach.

Most importantly, they didn't recall seeing this man prior to entering the immortal manor, so he had to have altered his own appearance somehow.

"I'll be on my way then," the middle-aged man said, then flew away atop his flying carriage.

As he flew away into the distance, the burly man turned to the elderly man and asked, "What do we think?"

"I wasn't able to notice anything amiss with my spirit eye ability, so he should be a genuine late-True Immortal cultivator," the elderly man mused as he habitually stroked his own goatee.

"If I'm not mistaken, that flying carriage he's using is quite a fine treasure," the dark-skinned woman suddenly said.

A hint of a smile appeared on the faces of both of the two men upon hearing this.

"Setting aside his storage tools, I want that piece of jade that he was holding," the burly man chuckled.

"I'm taking that robe of his," the thin elderly man declared.

Ultimately, the three of them were unable to suppress their greed, and they were planning to use their numbers advantage to hunt down the middle-aged man and take all of his treasures.

The flying carriage continued to fly through the sky at a leisurely pace several dozen kilometers away, and the smile on the middle-aged man's face remained unchanged as he murmured to himself, "Throwing your lives away over a moment of greed... How unfortunate..."

As soon as his voice trailed off, three streaks of light appeared in front of his flying carriage in a flash.

"Could it be that you've recalled the whereabouts of the Immortal Palace's cultivators, fellow daoists? If you could point me in the right direction, I would be extremely grateful," the middle-aged man said with a smile.

For some reason, a sense of foreboding welled up in the elderly man's heart at the sight of the smile on the middle-aged man's face, and he immediately decided that he would abandon his two companions and run away should things go awry.

Meanwhile, the burly man and the dark-skinned woman exchanged a glance, and the two of them quickly summoned a black stone ax and a silver longsword, respectively.

As for the thin elderly man, he summoned a seven-story golden pagoda that released a golden light barrier, which instantly swelled to countless times its original size to encompass himself, his two companions, and the middle-aged man.

"You think something that can't even count as a pseudo-spirit domain can trap me?"

A cold look suddenly appeared on the middle-aged man's face as he tightened his grip around the jade Pixiu in his hand.

The trio of Southern Dawn beings faltered slightly upon seeing this, yet before they had a chance to do anything, a burst of tremendous power suddenly converged toward them from all directions, instantly destroying the light barrier released by the seven-story golden pagoda.

Immediately thereafter, their bodies were completely pulverized by this burst of power.

Their heads remained completely unscathed, but their bodies had already been crushed into mangled masses of flesh, blood, and bones.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye!

Three streaks of golden light shot up into the sky as the nascent souls of the three Southern Dawn beings fled in different directions in a blind panic.

The middle-aged man made a casual grabbing motion upon seeing this, and an enormous semi-transparent hand appeared out of thin air, causing the entire space around it to crease and fold as it grabbed onto the trio of nascent souls.

"Please spare us, Senior! It's not worth dirtying your hands putting an end to our pathetic lives!" the nascent soul of the elderly man pleaded.

The middle-aged man ignored their desperate pleas as he cast his gaze toward the trio of nascent souls with a peculiar gleam in his eyes.

After a brief moment of observation, he crushed the three nascent souls into nothingness as he mused to himself, "It looks like they weren't lying, they really don't know where the Immortal Palace cultivators are. Having said that, there's a bit of a pleasant surprise here."

He reached out to make a beckoning motion as he spoke, and three streaks of azure light flew out of the remains of the three Southern Dawn beings. The streaks of light contained their masks, one of a deer, one of a crow, and another of an ape.

The three masks flew into his hand, and he examined them briefly before sweeping a sleeve through the air, upon which a giant wooden shelf that was laden with all types of Transient Guild masks appeared.

If one were to conduct a count, they would discover that there were over 1,000 of these masks in his collection.

[1]. Pixius are creatures in Chinese mythology that are said to be symbols for wealth, good fortune, and protection.

[Back]

Chapter 476: Undercurrents

"I've collected quite a few, haven't I?" the middle-aged man chuckled to himself, then placed the three new masks onto the wooden shelf before stowing it away with a pleased nod.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a hollow golden plate, which he tossed forward, and the plate flew several feet through the air before swelling to the size of a round table, while all types of complex runes lit up on its surface.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous pillar of golden light erupted out the center of the plate, rising directly up into the heavens.

Before long, specks of spiritual light began to converge, and three blurry figures appeared around the golden plate. Their bodies were enveloped in flowing golden light, making it impossible to glean their appearance.

"What is it, Gongshu Jiu? Haven't you gone to search the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor? Why have you suddenly contacted us?" one of the golden figures asked.

"Gan Jiuzhen is also in this immortal manor right now," Gongshu Jiu replied.

The same golden figure stirred slightly upon hearing this, and they asked, "Are you sure it's her? Her identity is extremely mysterious in the Reincarnation Palace, and even the name 'Gan Jiuzhen' may not be her true name. On top of that, she's frequently changing her mask, so how can you be sure that it's her?"

"I have no concrete evidence to prove it, but according to the memories of a few Transient Guild members that I just killed, the way that their leader, Wyrm 3, likes to do things, is quite similar to Gan Jiuzhen's style," Gongshu Jiu replied.

"In that case, please make sure that you capture her alive, Fellow Daoist Gongshu. As I'm sure you're aware, she's harboring many secrets that are worth exploring," one of the other golden figures said with a smile in their voice.

Gongshu Jiu nodded in response, and he was just about to conclude the communication when he suddenly recalled something, and he said, "Oh, I almost forgot. I discovered someone using the Spirit Refinement Technique in the immortal manor earlier, and from the looks of it, they've already cultivated it to at least the third level."

"To think that there are still people willing to risk their lives to cultivate the forbidden technique. There's no need to capture that person alive, just execute them on the spot," the third golden figure declared in a cold voice.

Gongshu Jiu nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air, and the golden plate reverted back to its original size before flying back up his sleeve, following which he flew away into the distance atop his flying carriage.

......

Meanwhile, high up in the sky a vast distance away.

Han Li and Jin Tong were flying through the air when the former suddenly stopped in his tracks before turning toward a certain direction.

"What is it?" Jin Tong asked.

"I just sensed a burst of extremely formidable energy fluctuations erupt into the sky in that direction, but it seems to be gone now," Han Li explained.

"Formidable energy fluctuations? Let's go and take a look!" Jin Tong suggested as a hint of excitement appeared in her eyes.

Han Li was naturally aware of what her intentions were, and he shook his head as he replied, "Let's not go out of our way to find trouble, we'll have plenty of powerful enemies to face."

"How boring," Jin Tong scoffed with a disappointed pout.

Han Li took another glance in that direction with his brows slightly furrowed, then continued to fly away into the distance with Jin Tong.

......

In a well-preserved cluster of palatial buildings, four cultivators dressed in Vast Flow Palace attire were each using a treasure to collectively attack a restriction around a palace.

Right as they were about to succeed, spiritual light suddenly flashed over the surface of an antiquated mirror hanging directly above the palace gates, and a beam of white light shot out of it to strike the chest of one of the four cultivators, who instantly let loose an agonized howl as a hole was punched through his chest, sending him toppling to the ground.

A resounding thump rang out as the array that the four cultivators had jointly conjured up instantly exploded.

The fair-skinned scholar who was the leader of the group instantly rushed over to the cultivator that had been struck down, then flipped a hand over to summon a golden pill to feed him.

Before long, the bones and flesh in the man's chest began to recover, but he still gasping for breath.

Everyone else was quite relieved to see this, but they were still quite concerned about their current situation.

"It's already been over half a month since we lost contact with the palace master and the others. We have to get out of this place as soon as possible. Perhaps the palace master has already found that place by now," the fair-skinned scholar said with a grim expression.

The other three cultivators hurriedly gave affirmative responses, and after a short rest, they began working on breaking the restriction again.

......

On a charred hill in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, there were wisps of white smoke rising up everywhere.

Several hundred feet below the ground here was an underground palace, inside of which was a large black stone chair. At the moment, the chair was being occupied by none other than the grand elder of the Dawn Fall Sect, Feng Tiandu.

The ground in front of him was littered with giant black rocks, and they seemed to be the remains of the puppets that had previously guarded this place.

Feng Tiandu was inspecting the puppet remains on the ground with a dark expression when all of a sudden, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside the palace.

Moments later, Qi Tianxiao made his way into the palace, and he extended a salute toward Feng Tiandu as he said, "All of our people have already been sent out. There are two teams that we're currently unable to get into contact with, while the rest of them are all still searching for the High Zenith Palace, but to no avail."

"Is there any news about the people from the Immortal Palace and the Vast Flow Palace?" Feng Tiandu asked.

"There has been some news, but it was only gathered yesterday. The Immortal Palace and the Vast Flow Palace have employed a similar strategy to ours, sending out all of their people to search for the High Zenith Palace, but it seems that they haven't had much luck, either," Qi Tianxiao replied.

"There should still be some time before the heavenly cauldron opens. If we can find its location prior to that, we'll be able to set up some measures in advance and seize the initiative," Feng Tiandu said.

"Rest assured, Senior Martial Brother, I'll be sure to keep a close eye on everyone else," Qi Tianxiao said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

......

On a bleak and desolate red plain stood a pair of tall men dressed in Southern Dawn Race attire. Each of them was holding a golden cane as the sped through the air, and directly behind them were three cultivators who were dressed in Ghost Wail Sect attire, but were actually cultivators of the Ubiquitous Pavilion.

For some reason, no conflict had arisen between the two parties, and instead, it seemed that the trio of Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were merely following the pair of Southern Dawn beings.

The two Southern Dawn beings both wore wooden expressions, and they resembled puppets as they flew onward without any communication.

After flying for a few minutes, the five of them spotted a set of ruins that resembled a city in the distance, and they hurriedly accelerated toward it.

......

In another area of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, there was a series of undulating hills, interspersed with valleys of different depths.

There were also lush forests, flowing rivers, fiery valleys filled with miasma... All types of landmarks were present in the area.

Among these landmarks was a small and completely unremarkable-looking valley that wasn't filled with miasma, nor did it have any greenery or rivers running through it.

It was just a little shorter than the valleys on either side of it, and there were currently three people gathered in the valley, discussing something in hushed tones.

All three of them had rather grim looks on their faces, and they were led by none other than Dao Lord Ouyang Kuishan of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

"Fellow Daoist Ouyang, we've already roused the suspicions of the Immortal Palace by leaking the location of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor's entrance. If we warn Daoist Hu Yan and others in advance this time, surely we'll be accused of betraying the Immortal Palace," one of the other two figures said.

"So what? The Immortal Palace promised us so many things, yet have they followed through on any of them? Right now, we're the laughingstock of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and we're constantly being restricted by the Immortal Palace in everything that we do. Rather than continue to live such a cowardly and pitiful existence, we may as well at least go out in a meaningful way," Ouyang Kuishan said as a hint of sorrow flashed through his eyes.

"We only betrayed Dao Lord Baili so that we could save the Blaze Dragon Dao, but we should've known better than to expect that Xiao Jinhan would follow through on his promises. We have no one to blame but ourselves for becoming the laughing stock of the entire immortal region," the third figure mused with a wry smile.

"This experience has taught me a valuable lesson: only by attaining sufficient power can one escape the fate of being controlled by others. I think this is an opportunity for us. All of the leading powers of the immortal regions are gathered here right now, so there's no need for us to directly oppose the Immortal Palace.

“All we have to do is muddy the waters so that others can chip away at the Immortal Palace's forces. The more the Immortal Palace is worn down, the less control they'll be able to exert over us," Ouyang Kuishan said.

"You're right. In any case, all we're doing is tipping off Hu Yan and the others, and the Immortal Palace can't find any evidence to prove that we tipped them off."

With the decision made, the three of them pulled out an octagonal copper array plate each, then assembled them together, and the blaze dragon design engraved onto their surface instantly lit up with crimson light.

Deep within the valley, there was a rippling light barrier that was quite blurry and indistinct, making it impossible to clearly see what laid beyond it.

......

Beneath a blanket of dark clouds in the sky stood a black mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall.

Near the mountain summit was a spacious cliff, and the white-robed Xiao Jinhan was standing on the edge of the cliff with his robes flapping around him, looking into the distance with a complex look in his eyes, and he was accompanied by Deputy Palace Master Xue Ying.

Chapter 477: Disturbance

"According to the latest news from Lu Yue and the others, the Vast Flow Palace cultivators don't appear to have made a move for now. Up to this point, they're still wandering around in search of the High Zenith Palace's true whereabouts. As for the Dawn Fall Sect, we haven't been able to gather any information on them for the moment," Xue Ying informed.

"Whenever a powerful treasure emerges, there will surely be a sign. There's not much time left until the heavenly cauldron is set to open, so it won't be long until some signs begin to appear. Everyone is currently desperately searching for the High Zenith Palace so that they can get there first before these signs emerge and conceal these signs to prevent others from finding the palace," Xiao Jinhan said.

"Lu Yue and the others are already searching as quickly as they can, so I'm sure they'll be able to find it soon," Xue Ying said.

"What about Ouyang Kuishan and the others?" Xiao Jinhan asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"They're searching through the area that we passed through earlier, and the High Zenith Palace most likely isn't there," Xue Ying replied.

"If they remain obedient and don't step out of line for the rest of this trip, then we can loosen my control over them a little and give them a bit more freedom," Xiao Jinhan instructed.

There was an element of finesse when it came to subjugating others, and constantly doing so with an iron fist wasn't the way to go. As the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Xiao Jinhan was naturally well aware of this.

"Yes, Palace Master," Xue Ying hurriedly replied.

All of a sudden, a slightly peculiar look appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face, and he said, "You can go now. I want to stay here on my own for a while."

Xue Ying naturally didn't dare to go against his wishes, and she hurriedly took her leave.

She had only just departed from the cliff when a figure that was enshrouded in a cloud of black mist suddenly rose up from the foot of the cliff, then arrived directly in front of Xiao Jinhan.

After extending a respectful bow, the misty figure began to converse with Xiao Jinhan through voice transmission.

At the end of the conversation, the misty figure concluded, "All of the arrangements on our end are already complete, so you can rest assured, Palace Master."

Xiao Jinhan's expression remained unchanged as he nodded in response, then gave a dismissive wave of his hand, gesturing for the misty figure to leave.

The misty figure immediately obliged, flying back down into the valley before vanishing as a cloud of black smoke.

Xiao Jinhan took a glance at the spot where the misty figure had just vanished, and he pursed his lips with a rather distracted look in his eyes.

Right at this moment, Xue Ying suddenly returned once again, and there was a hint of excitement in his eyes.

Xiao Jinhan immediately spotted the excitement in her eyes, and he asked, "Has the High Zenith Palace been found?"

"Ouyang Kuishan says that it's where they are," Xue Ying replied with a nod.

"Let's go," Xiao Jinhan instructed, and the two of them immediately flew away into the distance.

......

Close to half a month later.

Han Li was speeding through the sky atop his azure flying boat, while down below was a bleak and desolate red plain that was completely devoid of life.

The only thing that changed in this monotonous environment were the red clouds in the sky, some of which were large, while others were small. Despite the wind blowing over the plain, the clouds remained completely still and unmoved, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Han Li was seated atop his flying boat, holding a jade slip that was pressed against his forehead.

The jade slip was a map, one that he had drawn based on his memory of Lu Yuqing's map, and it definitely wasn't a perfect replica, but it was the best that he could do.

He was referencing the map while observing the surrounding terrain, trying to ascertain their current location, but even though he had already been searching for the past few days, he was still unable to pinpoint the location of this red plain on the map.

His brows furrowed slightly as he removed the jade slip from his forehead.

"So what if we can't find where we are? It's more exciting if we don't know anything!" Jin Tong yawned as she laid on the deck of the flying boat in a lazy manner.

Han Li paid no heed to her as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Even though he had reached the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, he didn't know what perils there were lurking in the immortal manor, so he didn't dare to get complacent.

After some contemplation, he stowed the jade slip away, then flipped a hand over to produce a crimson communication array plate, the very same one that had been given to him by Daoist Hu Yan.

Han Li cast a series of incantation seals into the array plate, and the spirit patterns on its surface flashed with crimson light before converging to form a miniature crimson array.

Han Li communicated a message into the array plate, and it continued to flash and revolve, but there was no response.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he stowed the array plate away.

The lack of response could simply be due to the fact that Daoist Hu Yan was in a special environment where the communication array plate couldn't be used, or it could hint at something far more foreboding.

Han Li pondered this matter in silence for a moment, then cast aside this train of thought.

Seeing as he was unable to get into contact with Daoist Hu Yan, then he would just have to act on his own for now. With his current level of power, he should be able to ensure self-preservation under the vast majority of circumstances.

There was still quite some time left until the immortal manor was scheduled to close, and this was the first time that this region had been discovered, so there had to be many rewards still left to be reaped.

With that in mind, Han Li made a hand seal to accelerate his azure flying boat, yet right at this moment, a resounding boom suddenly rang out in the distance, and the entire area within a radius of thousands of kilometers shuddered slightly.

Han Li immediately turned to the direction that the sound had come from, and there in the distance, countless dazzling balls of white light had emerged, flying over the landscape amid a burst of rumbling resembling that of countless thundering horse hooves.

The world's origin qi trembled and churned as streaks of spiritual light surged through the air, raising gusts of ferocious wind that swept over heaven and earth.

A burst of tremendous pressure was coming from that direction, and even Han Li couldn't but feel a little stunned as he swept a sleeve through the air to stop his azure flying boat cold in its tracks.

Right at this moment, the light in the distant sky began to ripple once again, but on this occasion, instead of spreading outward, it was converging toward a certain spot, and in the blink of an eye, all of it had vanished without a trace.

The churning world's origin qi also quickly subsided, and it was as if the phenomenon had never even taken place at all.

At this point, Jin Tong had already sprung to her feet, and she was looking into the distance with wide eyes.

"That was such a massive phenomenon! Could it be that some powerful treasure has emerged? Let's go take a look, Han Li!" Jin Tong urged.

Han Li was rather hesitant as he mused, "It doesn't seem like the emergence of a treasure. The light just now contained a great deal of spatial power, so it seems more like the emergence of a secret area."

"Who cares? If we don't go there now, someone will get there before us!" Jin Tong said in an urgent voice.

After some more hesitation, Han Li nodded in response. "Let's go take a look, but be careful, and also, don't call me by my name in front of others."

"Fine. Let's go, Uncle!" Jin Tong replied with an excited expression.

Han Li was left feeling rather speechless upon hearing this, and he shook his head with a resigned expression before guiding his azure flying boat in that direction.

......

Meanwhile, a ball of white light was flying over a crimson hill.

Standing atop the ball of white light were a group of Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators, among which were Xiao Jinhan and Xue Ying.

All of a sudden, Xiao Jinhan's expression changed slightly, and the ball of white light drew to an abrupt halt as he turned to a certain direction.

"What is it, Palace Master?" Xue Ying asked.

"I sensed a disturbance in that direction just now," Xiao Jinhan replied.

"A disturbance?"

Xue Ying faltered slightly upon hearing this. She hadn't detected anything at all.

A layer of white light surfaced over her eyes as she cast her gaze toward that direction, while Xiao Jinhan shook his head as he said, "The disturbance took place too far away from here, so you wouldn't be able to detect it at your cultivation base. On top of that, it's already faded by now."

"Could it be that the High Zenith Palace has finally emerged?" Xue Ying speculated as her eyes lit up.

Everyone else immediately turned to Xiao Jinhan upon hearing this, while Xiao Jinhan himself was standing still on the spot with a hesitant look on his face.

Even though he had sensed the disturbance in the distance, it was too far away for him to detect it clearly.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light appeared on Xiao Jinhan's body, and he raised an eyebrow as he pointed a finger forward, upon which the burst of white light flew out into the open, revealing itself to be a communication array plate.

The array plate released a miniature array, which, in turn, conjured up a projection of Ouyang Kuishan.

"We've found the entrance of the High Zenith Palace, Palace Master!" Ouyang Kuishan declared with an ecstatic expression.

Xiao Jinhan's expression remained unchanged as he asked, "Oh? Where is it? And how did you discover it?"

"Just now, a phenomenon took place at the entrance, and I just so happened to be nearby. This is the location."

Ouyang Kuishan swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, releasing a burst of light that transformed into a map, upon which an azure speck of light was pulsing incessantly.

Xiao Jinhan took a glance at the map to find that the location of the purported entrance matched the direction where the disturbance had just arisen.

"Alright, make sure to keep the entrance guarded, I'm coming right now," Xiao Jinhan instructed.

"The phenomenon has already subsided, but it caused a massive commotion just now, so please get here as quickly as possible. Otherwise, if other people get here first, we may not be able to keep them at bay," Ouyang Kuishan urged.

Xiao Jinhan's expression darkened a little as he replied, "I'll get there as soon as I can."

With that, he concluded the communication, and the projection of Ouyang Kuishan instantly vanished, while Xiao Jinhan remained on the spot with his brows slightly furrowed, seemingly contemplating something.

Chapter 478: Entrance of the Palace

After some time, Xue Ying couldn't help but interject, "Isn't the location that Ouyang Kuishan just pointed out in the same direction where the disturbance just arose? Surely that has to mean the information is reliable."

"There's no hurry. If that really is the entrance of the High Zenith Palace, then it'll surely be protected by restrictions and guards, so even if others manage to get there before us, they won't be able to enter the palace anytime soon," Xiao Jinhan replied with a shake of his head.

"Are you saying that Ouyang Kuishan is lying to us? Surely not! If he had the courage to lie to us, then he wouldn't have betrayed Baili Yan," Xue Ying said as a hint of derision flashed through her eyes.

"Ouyang Kuishan is not to be fully trusted, and it's always better to be safe than sorry," Xiao Jinhan said as he pointed a finger at the array plate, upon which the same communication array was conjured up again.

The array flashed a few times, following which a projection of Lu Yue emerged.

"Greetings, Palace Master. Do you have some instructions for me?" Lu Yue asked with a respectful salute.

"Where are you right now? Did you sense anything just now?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"I am currently situated in the southeast relative to the location where we split up, and I didn't sense anything just now," Lu Yue replied.

"I see. Keep searching that area, and report back to me immediately if you discover anything," Xiao Jinhan instructed.

Lu Yue nodded in response, and the communication was concluded.

Xiao Jinhan made a hand seal, and he was just about to contact someone else when a burst of black light suddenly appeared on his body.

His expression instantly changed slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a black array plate appeared in his grasp, emanating rings of black light.

An indistinct black figure was standing in the black light, and it was the same person that he had spoken to atop the cliff last time.

"Palace Master Xiao, the entrance of the High Zenith Palace has already emerged. Feng Tiandu has already discovered it and is heading there right now. Everything has already been set up according to our plan," the black figure declared.

A hint of elation flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes upon hearing this, but he remained level-headed as he asked, "Where is the entrance?"

The black figure swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of black light that conjured up a map, and there was a marked location on the map that was virtually identical to the location indicated by Ouyang Kuishan earlier.

"Alright, I'm coming right now," Xiao Jinhan immediately said, and the communication was concluded.

"Let's go!" Xiao Jinhan instructed as the ball of white light continued onward, and Xue Ying also cast an incantation seal into the ball of white light to accelerate it even further.

The Immortal Palace cultivators flew onward for a while before a burst of blue light suddenly appeared to their right, and it was rapidly approaching them, reaching them in the blink of an eye.

Xue Ying's brows furrowed slightly as the ball of white light drew to a halt at her behest, and she was just about to yell out at the approaching burst of blue light, but Xiao Jinhan gestured for her to remain silent.

The blue light up ahead faded, revealing a group of Vast Flow Palace cultivators, led by none other than Grand Palace Master Luo Qinghai.

"What a coincidence, Palace Master Xiao. You look like you're in quite a hurry. May I ask where you're going?" Luo Qinghai asked as he cupped his fist toward Xiao Jinhan and the others in a salute.

"How can I help you, Grand Palace Master Luo?" Xiao Jinhan asked in an indifferent voice.

"I discovered a set of ruins up ahead, but there's a restriction inside that's proving to be quite difficult to break. We've already been trying for several days to no avail, and we presume that there must be a precious treasure inside. Would you like to come and have a look with us, Palace Master Xiao?" Luo Qinghai asked with a smile.

"Where are these ruins?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"Not far up ahead, only about half a day away from here," Luo Qinghai replied as he pointed in the direction that he came from.

Xiao Jinhan cast his gaze toward that direction to find that it was precisely the direction where the entrance of the High Zenith Palace was situated.

"From my observations, it seems like there's an ancient tomb under the restriction. I don't know who's buried there, but it's definitely a very important person," Luo Qinghai said as he pulled out a blue jade talisman.

The jade talisman released a burst of bright blue light at his behest, which transformed into a mirror of water that depicted a vast wilderness filled with howling wind and swirling sand.

There was also a massive yellow ovular light barrier in the image, and it was rather murky and indistinct, concealing what was underneath.

Only the outlines of a giant tomb could be made out through the light barrier, and it resembled a giant beast that was resting on the ground.

"Looks like you stumbled upon quite a stroke of fortune, Grand Palace Master Luo, but wouldn't you have much preferred for your Vast Flow Palace to have claimed this place alone? Why are you inviting me?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"I just told you. The restriction outside the tomb is extremely formidable, and all of us have been attacking it non-stop for several consecutive days without being able to make much progress at all. If we're delayed any further, other powers will most likely begin to arrive on the scene.

“That's why I'm inviting you to come and help us break the restriction, and we'll split the treasures inside evenly between our two sects. What do you say?" Luo Qinghai asked as a serious look appeared on his face.

"If this is a restriction that even you can't open, then it's most likely beyond me as well," Xiao Jinhan refused with a shake of his head.

"Don't worry about that, Palace Master Xiao. Even though we haven't been able to break the restriction, I've managed to find a way to do so, but it requires six Golden Immortals working together at once, and that's why I'm inviting you to come along," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

Xiao Jinhan contemplated the offer momentarily, then turned to Xue Ying as he said, "Your Vast Flow Palace already has five Golden Immortals, so you only need one more. Xue Ying, take everyone else and make a trip to the ruins with Grand Palace Master Luo."

Xue Ying's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she hurriedly said to Xiao Jinhan through voice transmission, "But Palace Master, what if this is a trap..."

"Don't worry, I know what I'm doing," Xiao Jinhan interjected, and Xue Ying fell silent upon hearing this.

"Deputy Palace Xue Ying will also suffice for the task," Luo Qinghai said. "Time is of the essence, so let's set off right away, Deputy Palace Master Xue."

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light that swept up all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators before flying away into the distance.

"I'll be going then, Palace Master," Xue Ying said to Xiao Jinhan, then flipped a hand over to produce a bird-shaped flying boat for all of the Immortal Palace cultivators to pile onto.

"Make sure to help Grand Palace Master Luo to the best of your abilities," Xiao Jinhan instructed, making sure to place extra emphasis on the word "help".

Xue Ying nodded in response, then made a hand seal, and the flying boat immediately departed, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Xiao Jinhan looked on as the two groups departed into the distance, and only after all of them had completely vanished out of sight did he continue onward as a streak of white light.

Several days later, a streak of white light arrived from afar, then faded to reveal Xiao Jinhan in the sky above a giant canyon.

His hands were clasped behind his back, and his robes were flapping audibly in the wind as he inspected his surroundings.

The location that had been pointed out by both Ouyang Kuishan and the shadowy figure wasn't very far away from this place.

Some time later, his eyes suddenly lit up, and he shot forth like lightning, flying toward a certain direction in the canyon in complete silence.

......

At the foot of the canyon was a giant rectangular stone wall that was white in color and several thousand feet in size. Its surface was extremely smooth, and it seemed to be an enormous gate.

There was a piece of scenery engraved onto the stone wall from left to right, and it was extremely vibrant and lifelike.

Behind the stone wall was a thick white light barrier that was flashing incessantly, and there were many people gathered in front of the stone wall, split up into four different factions.

The largest group consisted of the Dawn Fall Sect's cultivators, with almost all of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators who had entered the immortal manor present. All they were missing were a couple of True Immortal cultivators, who had presumably perished elsewhere in the immortal manor.

Not far away from the Dawn Fall Sect's cultivators stood a group of Southern Dawn beings, but out of their four Golden Immortals, only the elderly man and the elderly woman were present, while the other two were absent.

As for their True Immortal cultivator, only about half of them were present, and it was unclear whether the other half had already perished or were still on their way.

The group with the second-least number of people was Ouyang Kuishan and the other two Blaze Dragon Dao Dao Lords, while the final group only consisted of two people, namely a man and a woman.

If Han Li were present, he would've immediately been able to identify them as Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

Right at this moment, a figure emerged in the sky amid a flash of golden light.

The new arrival didn't say anything, and there was no aura escaping from his body at all, but everyone was struck by a sense of pressure in his presence.

It was none other than Xiao Jinhan.

His arrival was met with varying degrees of dismay from everyone, with the exceptions of Ouyang Kuishan's trio, who immediately approached him with elated expressions.

"We pay our respects to the esteemed palace master!"

"Good job. The three of you will be rewarded once we leave the immortal manor," Xiao Jinhan said.

"Thank you, Palace Master!" Ouyang Kuishan's trio replied in unison.

Xiao Jinhan's gaze then swept over the Southern Dawn beings and the duo of Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

"These people were most likely nearby as well, and they arrived not long after the phenomenon here subsided," Ouyang Kuishan hurriedly explained via voice transmissions at the sight of Xiao Jinhan's expression.

Xiao Jinhan gave a slight nod and offered no response.

"Welcome, Palace Master Xiao. I wasn't expecting you to get here so soon. Why are you here on your own? Where are the other fellow daoists from the Immortal Palace?" Feng Tiandu asked.

Chapter 479: Observing from the Shadows

"Everyone else is busy with other things. That's none of your concern, Fellow Daoist Feng," Xiao Jinhan replied in an indifferent voice.

"I don't mean to pry. It's just that you're normally always surrounded by your subordinates, so it's rather strange to see you alone," Feng Tiandu said.

"To be honest, I prefer being on my own. Sometimes, when there are less burdens and hindrances around, it makes it easier to do what needs to be done without any unnecessary qualms. Wouldn't you agree, Fellow Daoist Feng?" Xiao Jinhan asked.

"I'm not as much of a free spirit as yourself, Fellow Daoist Xiao. I still think having more people around makes things easier," Feng Tiandu replied with a smile.

"It does appear as if you have a numbers advantage over everyone else. Have you already decided to claim this High Zenith Palace as a territory of your Dawn Fall Sect, Fellow Daoist Feng?" Xiao Jinhan asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Of course not, Palace Master Xiao. No one has any right to claim ownership over the High Zenith Palace, and anyone can come and go from the palace as they please. In particular, now that you're here, I feel much more at ease," Feng Tiandu replied with a shake of his head.

A faint smile appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face as he took a glance at the people behind Feng Tiandu, then suddenly turned to the white stone wall before raising a hand.

A streak of white light flew out of the palm of his hand, transforming into a translucent arrow that struck the light barrier with a loud crack.

The arrow was instantly shattered, while the light barrier only flashed momentarily before immediately returning to normal.

"What a sturdy restriction," Xiao Jinhan exclaimed as a grim look flashed through his eyes.

"The Dawn Fall Sect cultivators have already tried to break this restriction through their collective power just now, but they were unable to make any progress, so it looks like breaking this restriction definitely won't be an easy task," Ouyang Kuishan informed through voice transmission.

Xiao Jinhan gave a slight nod upon hearing this.

"Having said that, there's no need to be overly concerned, Palace Master," Ouyang Kuishan continued. "The white light barrier over this stone wall was previously twice as thick as it is now, but for some reason, it's constantly been getting thinner over time. I'm sure this trend will continue to hold true, and perhaps the restriction will eventually even disappear altogether. When that time comes, we should be able to bypass it with ease."

"Oh? Is that true?" Xiao Jinhan asked as his expression changed slightly.

"I wouldn't dare to lie to you, Palace Master. If you don't believe me, just take some time to observe the restriction and see for yourself," Ouyang Kuishan hurriedly replied.

Xiao Jinhan took a long glance at Ouyang Kuishan upon hearing this, and the latter hurriedly lowered his head and averted his gaze. With no better course of action to pursue for now, Xiao Jinhan made his way over to a large rock off to the side, then sat down onto it and closed his eyes to rest.

Feng Tiandu took a brief glance at Xiao Jinhan before also looking away, while the rest of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators behind him exchanged a few glances before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Everyone else present quickly followed suit as well, and a tense silence descended upon the entire scene.

Time slowly passed by, and before long, it had already been close to an hour.

Xiao Jinhan inspected the white light barrier briefly to find that it had indeed become a little thinner than before.

......

Meanwhile, in a discreet cave far away from the valley, Han Li and Jin Tong were standing next to each other in a completely still manner.

They had used some type of secret technique to completely conceal their auras, so even if someone were to sweep their spiritual sense over them, it would appear as if they weren't there.

Through a gap between a pair of large rocks, Han Li was observing everyone in the distance with blue light flashing in his eyes.

He had been quite close to the stone wall when the phenomenon had taken place, so he had actually only gotten here a little later than Ouyang Kuishan and the others.

However, as soon as he spotted Ouyang Kuishan's trio, he immediately concealed himself and Jin Tong using a secret technique.

There are more and more people arriving on the scene... Judging from what they said earlier, this place is the entrance of a so-called High Zenith Palace. What is this place, and why is it garnering so much attention from the likes of even Xiao Jinhan and Feng Tiandu? Could it be...

Additionally, Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were also present, and that was quite a relief for him.

Daoist Hu Yan was somewhere between a friend and a teacher for him, and Han Li had been quite concerned for him this entire time, so it was definitely a good thing to see him here safe and sound.

Jin Tong was standing beside him with a bored look on her face, and she suddenly tossed something into her mouth before chomping down onto it. The sound that was produced wasn't very loud, but it gave Han Li quite a fright, and he hurriedly cautioned through voice transmission, "Be quiet! We'll be in trouble if those people discover us."

Thankfully, the secret technique being used by Han Li concealed both sound and auras, and were quite far away from Xiao Jinhan and the others. Additionally, everyone's attention was focused on the stone wall, so no one noticed Han Li and Jin Tong in the distance.

"Hiding here is so boring, Uncle! How much longer do we have to keep hiding?" Jin Tong complained through voice transmission with a displeased pout.

"Be patient," Han Li replied.

"Are those people your enemies?" Jin Tong asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Some of them are," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"Which ones?" Jin Tong asked as she prepared to rush out to face them.

Han Li hurriedly grabbed onto Jin Tong's arm as he urged, "Wait! There are too many of them and only two of us, so we'll be at a disadvantage in a direct battle. On top of that, it's clear that all of them are plotting against each other as well, so perhaps they'll start fighting even before the restriction is broken."

"You're right!" Jin Tong exclaimed as a hint of excitement surfaced in her eyes. "If they don't start fighting among themselves, then we'll wait until they split up and hunt them down one after another. Aren't I smart?"

"You're a genius, Jin Tong," Han Li praised as he patted Jin Tong on the head.

"Fine. In that case, I'll wait for a bit longer," Jin Tong said as she sat down and rested her head on her folded arms.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as he continued his observation.

Several hours passed by in the blink of an eye, and Jin Tong had already fallen asleep.

At this point, all that remained of the light barrier over the stone wall was a thin layer, and no one else arrived during this time.

Furthermore, everyone, including Xiao Jinhan and Feng Tiandu, had already risen to their feet, and they were staring intently at the white stone wall.

The light barrier on the stone wall was still slowly becoming thinner and thinner, and everyone was already channeling their immortal spiritual power with tense looks on their faces, bracing themselves to strike as soon as the light barrier reached its most fragile state.

At the same time, they were also making sure to keep tabs on one another.

"The restriction has already become very thin, Senior Martial Brother. If all of us attack it at once, we should be able to break through it. Should we strike now?" Qi Tianxiao asked through voice transmission.

"Let's wait a bit longer until the restriction is reduced to its weakest state. After all, we also have Xiao Jinhan to worry about on top of this restriction," Feng Tiandu replied.

"You're right, Senior Martial Brother," Qi Tianxiao said with a nod.

In the distant cave, Han Li was also staring intently at the stone wall with blue light flashing in his eyes.

Right at this moment, the white light barrier, which had become as thin as a sheet of paper, suddenly flashed momentarily, and countless thin strands of white light appeared over its surface as it abruptly began to thicken again.

Everyone's expressions instantly changed drastically upon seeing this, and they all lashed out in unison.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Xiao Jinhan released a streak of piercing white light, which contained what appeared to be a sharp spike.

It was an immortal treasure that had white lightning flashing over its surface, releasing a burst of loud crackling and thunderous rumbling as it pierced viciously toward the white light barrier.

Ouyang Kuishan's trio also sprang into action, with each of them summoning a golden flying sword, on the hilt of which was a beastly head that seemed to belong to a dragon, but was also somewhat different.

On one side of the sword's blade was engraved a piece of scenery, while on the other side was etched a vast starry sky.

The three flying swords were arranged in a triangular formation, and they gave off dazzling swordlight as they swept toward the white light barrier.

At the same time, the two elderly Golden Immortals of the Southern Dawn Race pointed their golden canes forward, and radiant golden light erupted out of their canes, transforming into a pair of golden dragons in a flash.

Both dragons were glowing radiantly, looking as if they had been forged out of pure gold, and they were giving off a peerlessly sharp aura as they swooped toward the white light barrier.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni also summoned immortal treasures of their own, namely a crimson flying sword and a blue flying wheel. They didn't appear to be immortal treasures of a particularly high caliber, but they were also sent flying toward the light barrier with ferocious power.

However, out of all of the people present, the collective assault unleashed by the Dawn Fall Sect's cultivators was the most formidable one.

At this moment, all of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators were gathered around in a loose circle, but there was a method to the way in which they were arranged, and it seemed that they had formed an array.

All of them began to glow with radiant black light, which converged to form a series of thick beams of black light that connected together before surging into Feng Tiandu's body.

As a result, Feng Tiandu swelled noticeably in size, and his skin bulged as a countless thick green veins emerged over his body, wriggling and writhing like worms.

The aura that he was exuding instantly swelled drastically to completely exceed that of everyone else present, and even Xiao Jinhan's expression changed slightly upon sensing this.

Immediately thereafter, he took a deep breath as he began to chant a rapid incantation, and his body took on a drastic change, becoming withered and yellow and reverting back into what resembled a dried corpse in the blink of an eye.

A string of loud clangs rang out from within his body, following which a series of thick black chains numbering in the dozens shot out of his robes, swaying from side to side around him like a mass of tentacles.

Every single chain was riddled with countless tiny black runes, which were flashing incessantly and giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly as he witnessed this from afar.

Even though they were situated quite far away from one another, he could clearly sense that the aura being emitted by the black chains summoned by Feng Tiandu was identical to that of the two Origin Separation Law Chains in his possession.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately realized who Feng Tiandu was.

Chapter 480: Caught Off Guard

In front of the white stone wall.

Feng Tiandu closed his eyes while making a hand seal, and all of the chains in the air around him shuddered in unison, then shot forth through the air as countless black lines, hurtling toward the white light barrier like rain.

A string of loud thumps instantly rang out in rapid succession as specks of black light emerged over the surface of the white light barrier, causing it to ripple incessantly.

At this point, all of the other cultivators present had also sprung into action, launching attacks of their own at the light barrier.

With so many True Immortals and Golden Immortals joining forces at once, the resulting assault was just as ferocious as it was spectacular to behold, and the white light barrier twisted and warped violently as countless runes surged out of its surface.

All of a sudden, an earth-shattering boom rang out, and the entire canyon suddenly began to tremble and sway violently.

Countless large cracks appeared over the ground and the mountain faces, intertwining with one another like a system of cobwebs.

In the face of so many formidable attacks, the light barrier was struggling to hold itself together, and a series of cracks had begun to appear on its surface.

This was naturally a very encouraging sight for everyone, and they all redoubled their efforts for one final push.

Finally, all of the runes on the surface of the white light barrier exploded, immediately followed by the light barrier itself, and the white stone face beneath it was finally exposed.

Feng Tiandu's eyes sprang open, and a hint of elation appeared on his face.

He made a hand seal while chanting a quiet incantation, and all of the black chains around him instantly vanished back into his body, immediately following which he took a large stride forward, yet right as he was about to say something, an unexpected turn of events abruptly unfolded.

Qi Tianxiao and three other Golden Immortals near him lashed out in unison, raising their arms at the same time without any warning.

A chorus of loud clangs rang out as bright golden light emerged within the sleeves of the four Golden Immortals, and four golden chains with countless runes surging all over them shot forth in unison before wrapping themselves around Feng Tiandu's limbs.

Each chain was radiating bright golden light that was filled with golden runes, and they were also releasing formidable restrictive law powers.

Feng Tiandu's expression changed drastically as a layer of black light abruptly appeared over his body, instantly forming a protective black light barrier.

Almost in the exact same instant that the black light barrier took shape, the four golden chains arrived and wound themselves around the light barrier.

As soon as the two made contact with one another, the golden runes on the surface of the chains instantly lit up in unison, and they were able to slice through the black light barrier with ease like hot knives through butter before tying up Feng Tiandu like lightning.

Arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the four chains to strike Feng Tiandu, causing plumes of white smoke to rise up from his body.

Feng Tiandu let loose a muffled groan, and the black light barrier around him was instantly shattered, much to the elation of the four Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals, who began chanting a collective incantation, upon which the four golden chains intertwined to form a square golden cage with Feng Tiandu trapped in the center.

A burst of incredibly formidable restrictive force surged out of the golden cage, causing the nearby air to ripple violently, and even the surrounding world's origin qi had fallen completely still.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and everyone was caught completely off guard, looking on with dazed expressions, even temporarily forgetting about the white stone wall.

Han Li was also rather taken aback as he looked on from afar.

Looking at the four golden chains, he was immediately reminded of the eight chains that Ouyang Kuishan and the other dao lords had used against Baili Yan all those years ago.

Even though there were only four of these chains on this occasion, they were several times thicker than the eight chains from last time, and the aura emanating from this golden cage was also more formidable than that one.

"What is the meaning of this?" Feng Tiandu roared as he struggled with all his might, and a layer of black light appeared over his body, only to be instantly suppressed by the enormous restrictive powers of the golden cage, rendering his tremendous cultivation base completely useless.

"My apologies, Senior Martial Brother, but you've brought this entirely upon yourself, so you can't blame anyone else. Our master passed the position of sect master down to me, yet you've shown me no respect at all, forcibly taking over ownership of the sect and claiming all of its resources.

“You've gone too far, and it's time that someone stopped you," Qi Tianxiao declared in a cold voice while making a hand seal, and more thick arcs of golden lightning emerged over the golden cage before transforming into seven thick golden nails.

Each nail was around a foot in length with countless golden lightning runes on their surface, and they were giving off astonishing lightning law power fluctuations as they pierced viciously into Feng Tiandu's glabella, chest, lower abdomen, and other vital regions.

Feng Tiandu gave another muffled groan as blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips.

Arcs of golden lightning surged out of the seven golden nails before rapidly flowing over Feng Tiandu's body while crackling incessantly.

A series of gashes instantly appeared over his skin, and blood came pouring out of those gashes as his aura diminished significantly.

Feng Tiandu's eyes narrowed slightly as he gave an enraged harrumph, and his hands balled up into tight fists as began to chant a rapid incantation.

A burst of black light instantly emerged over his body, and his entire body turned black, while strings of black runes surged out of the spots on his body that had been impaled by teh golden nails.

At the same time, a burst of rustling rang out within his body, and the seven chains shuddered before slowly pulling back, as if they were being forced out by something.

Qi Tianxiao's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, around a dozen black chains shot out of Feng Tiandu's body before wrapping themselves around the surrounding golden cage.

Inky-black light emerged from the black chains, quickly staining the golden cage black, while the golden chains around Feng Tiandu began to rapidly dim while also displaying signs of loosening.

Qi Tianxiao was greatly alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly attempted to bolster the golden chains, but to no avail.

In the blink of an eye, half of the golden cage had already been stained black.

Right at this moment, a white figure emerged behind Feng Tiandu without any warning, and it was none other than Xiao Jinhan.

With a flick of his wrist, a white shadow flew out of his sleeve, piercing directly toward Feng Tiandu's throat like lightning. It was a translucent longsword that was giving off tremendous glacial qi, and Qi Tianxiao and the others merely continued with what they were doing, displaying no reaction to Xiao Jinhan's sudden intervention.

Feng Tiandu's pupils contracted slightly as he opened his mouth to release a streak of yellow light, which revealed itself to be a shield in the shape of a yellow turtle shell. The shield was riddled with profound patterns, and judging from the formidable earth law power fluctuations that it was giving off, this was clearly a powerful immortal treasure.

The yellow shield instantly swelled to several times its original size as it positioned itself in front of him, and the white longsword struck the yellow shield with a resounding clang.

The latter was forced back from the force of the clash, but it was ultimately able to keep the longsword at bay.

"Qi Tianxiao! How dare you collude with Xiao Jinhan!" Feng Tiandu roared in a furious voice.

In the distant cave, Han Li continued to look on in silence, but a cold look had appeared in his eyes as he gazed upon Xiao Jinhan.

It was clear that he had employed the same tactics that he had used to bring down the Blaze Dragon Dao to sow dissension among the Dawn Fall Sect's cultivators as well.

If Feng Tiandu were to also be eliminated, then the Vast Flow Palace would be the only one that remained of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region's three premier sects. It would be completely powerless to oppose the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace on its own, and before long, the entire immortal region would fall under the Immortal Palace's control.

Jin Tong had been roused from her nap by the commotion, and she rushed over to Han Li's side as she clapped her hands together with an excited expression and yelled, "They really have begun fighting! You were right, Uncle! Do we strike now?"

"Let's wait for a bit longer. The best is still yet to come," Han Li said.

In the distance, the expressions of the Southern Dawn beings changed slightly at the sight of the scene unfolding before them, as was the case with Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni.

However, before they could do anything, Ouyang Kuishan's trio abruptly appeared before them, standing in their way.

Ouyang Kuishan cast his gaze toward the Southern Dawn beings and Daoist Hu Yan's duo as he declared in a threatening tone, "This has nothing to do with any of you, fellow daoists, so please do not intervene."

Daoist Hu Yan and the others exchanged a few glances upon hearing this, and they decided to oblige.

Xiao Jinhan was rather relieved to see this out of the corner of his eye, and he made a hand seal, upon which a burst of white mist with countless runes dancing within it erupted out of his white longsword before enveloping the yellow shield in a flash.

Bright yellow light flashed from the yellow shield, and it was just about to release something,only for a burst of law power fluctuations to surge out of the cloud of white mist to slow down the release of the yellow light.

Immediately thereafter, a millstone-sized chunk of white ice emerged, presenting quite a spectacular sight to behold.

The yellow shield was completely encased within the block of ice, and all of the law power fluctuations it was releasing had been sealed away.

The block of ice then fell to the ground with a loud crack, while Han Li looked on from afar with a hint of admiration in his eyes.

To think that his laws of ice have been cultivated to such a degree that they're capable of even freezing other law powers! As expected of the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace!

Chapter 481: A Good Show

Feng Tiandu's expression changed slightly upon seeing his shield being encased in ice, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which black light began to surge through his eyes.

Radiant black light also erupted out of his body to stain the golden cage at an even faster rate, and the seven golden nails were also being forced out of his body faster than before.

"Hurry, Palace Master Xiao! We won't be able to restrain him for much longer!" Qi Tianxiao urged as he released two bursts of black light out of his hands into the golden chain that he was holding.

At this point, his face was bright red, and a sheen of sweat had appeared on his forehead. His hands were also trembling slightly, clearly indicating that he was already going all-out, but it was still to no avail, and the same applied to the other three Golden Immortals as well.

Feng Tiandu was far more powerful than all of them had anticipated.

A hint of hesitation flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes, but he couldn't just pass up such a prime opportunity to strike down Feng Tiandu. With that in mind, a fierce look appeared in his eyes as he advanced forward, leaving a flurry of snowflakes in his wake.

At the same time, he pierced his sword through the air four times in rapid succession, unleashing four streaks of white qi that hurtled directly toward Feng Tiandu like four white snakes.

However, right at this moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted behind Qi Tianxiao, and an inky-black hand appeared out of thin air. Faint black mist was emanating from the hand as it crashed down toward the top of Xiao Jinhan's head like lightning.

Xiao Jinhan was greatly startled by this unexpected turn of events, and radiant white light emerged over his body as he frantically sprang to the side.

However, his attention had been entirely focused on Feng Tiandu, so he reacted a fraction of a second too late, and he was unable to completely avoid the black hand.

The hand crashed down onto his shoulder with a bone-splitting crack, and Xiao Jinhan stumbled slightly before steadying himself again not far away.

However, his left shoulder was clearly mangled, and a black palm print had appeared on his back, giving off a putrid odor.

The robes on his also quickly withered away, as if they were being eroded, while the blackened part of his skin was rapidly necrosing amid a sinister hissing sound, and the rot was quickly spreading.

Xiao Jinhan inhaled briefly as he made a hand seal, and white light flashed over his body as all of the swirling snowflakes around him instantly revolved to form a white tornado that converged toward the wound. In the blink of an eye, a layer of white frost took shape over the black palm print, preventing the rot from spreading any further.

At the same time, he spun around like lightning to see who it was that had attacked him, only to be stunned to find that it was none other than Qi Tianxiao!

At this moment, there was a faint smile on Qi Tianxiao's face, and he didn't appear to be under any strain at all.

While Xiao Jinhan was rooted to the spot in shock, eight chains appeared around him out of thin air, and they were none other than Origin Separation Law Chains.

Xiao Jinhan's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly opened his mouth to release a white jade bowl, out of which countless golden and silver runes surged forth to form a golden and silver net of light that enveloped his entire body.

However, the eight black chains were able to pass straight through the golden and silver net without encountering any impediment before vanishing into his body in the blink of an eye.

Xiao Jinhan's entire body stiffened as the white light around him quickly faded, and his aura also began to rapidly diminish.

Immediately thereafter, Feng Tiandu abruptly appeared behind him in a flash.

The seven golden nails in his body had already been completely removed, and he seemed to have made a full recovery. Eight black chains were currently extending out of the palms of his hands, and the other end of the chains were lost into space.

Clearly, he was the one who had unleashed the eight Origin Separation Law Chains that had struck Xiao Jinhan.

Xiao Jinhan let loose a furious roar as the white light emanating from his body abruptly brightened, forming a translucent white barrier over his skin.

As a result, the rate at which the black chains were piercing into his body was slowed down significantly.

Right at this moment, four golden chains arrived on the scene amid a flash of golden light before wrapping themselves around Xiao Jinhan, and they were the very same chains that had been used to restrict Feng Tiandu earlier.

At this point, the black runes on the golden chains had already completely faded, and they were radiating dazzling golden light while also giving off formidable restrictive power.

The four golden chains quickly intertwined with one another to form the same golden cage from before, this time with Xiao Jinhan trapped inside.

At the same time, Qi Tianxiao and the other three Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals appeared around Xiao Jinhan in a flash before making a rapid series of hand seals.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes as he observed the unfolding scene from afar.

"What are those people doing? Weren't they targeting that old zombie before? Why have they suddenly started attacking the silver beard guy now?" Jin Tong asked in a surprised manner.

"The first part was all an act, and they're actually all plotting against silver beard. He's been betrayed by his own allies," Han Li explained as a hint of realization appeared in his eyes.

"That's kind of sad, isn't it?" Jin Tong mused as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Let this be a lesson to you, Jin Tong. Do not trust anyone, and always have your guard up," Han Li said in a solemn voice.

"Does that mean I can't even trust you?" Jin Tong asked as she blinked in an innocent manner.

Han Li was left a little speechless by this question, and he replied in an exasperated manner, "I'm an exception, of course!"

......

"How dare you betray me! You're all going to pay with your lives!" Xiao Jinhan harrumphed coldly as he made a hand seal, and a speck of dazzling white light emerged over his hand with countless white runes flashing inside.

Qi Tianxiao and the other three Golden Immortals abruptly shuddered slightly, and a layer of white light appeared over their dantians, immediately following which a vast expanse of snowflakes emerged above them.

A cruel smile appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face as he prepared to initiate the killing blow, but right at this moment, a burst of black light emerged over the dantians of Qi Tianxiao and the others, and there was a black chain projection in each burst of black light.

The chain projections whipped around in a forceful motion, and the white light around their dantians was instantly shattered like eggshells, while the vast expanse of snowflakes above them also faded away.

"Impossible!" Xiao Jinhan exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"You thought such a crude nascent soul restriction would work on cultivators of our Dawn Fall Sect? Are you not aware that my Origin Separation Yin Devil Arts specifically targets the nascent soul?" Feng Tiandu scoffed with a cold sneer.

Xiao Jinhan's expression darkened slightly, and before he could do anything else, several more figures suddenly appeared around him.

They were none other than Daoist Hu Yan, Yun Ni, and the two Southern Dawn Race Golden Immortals.

All of them had fierce killing intent in their eyes, and a crimson flying sword, a blue flying wheel, and two golden canes hurtled directly toward Xiao Jinhan at their behest.

Xiao Jinhan's expression changed slightly once again upon seeing this, but he remained calm and collected as a ball of white light appeared in front of him.

All of the surrounding swirling snowflakes instantly converged to form a semi-transparent wall of white ice, which was giving off a faint glow. Countless white runes were dancing over the wall of ice, while streaks of white light were flashing within it.

Four resounding booms rang out as the four immortal treasures unleashed by Daoist Hu Yan and the others struck the wall of ice, and a series of cracks instantly appeared over the wall, following which it was completely shattered, but the four immortal treasures were also successfully repelled.

Immediately thereafter, Xiao Jinhan began to chant a rapid incantation, and all of the surrounding snowflakes instantly converged toward him, forming a ball of white ice that was over 100 feet in size, encompassing both himself and the golden cage within.

The golden cage and the eight black chains were all frozen in the ball of ice, rendering them completely immobilized.

Feng Tiandu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately flicked a finger through the air, releasing a black longsword that transformed into a streak of black swordlight that was several hundred feet in length before striking the ball of ice with tremendous power.

A resounding boom rang out as a gash that was over 100 feet in length was sliced into the ball of ice, but it wasn't very deep.

However, the streak of black swordlight was also repelled, and it reverted back into a black serpentine flying sword that circled around repeatedly above Feng Tiandu's head.

A layer of white ice crystals had appeared over the surface of the sword, and the black swordlight emanating from it had also become rather erratic, indicating that its spiritual nature had been harmed.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of black light that vanished into the flying sword.

The black flying sword twisted and writhed like a spirit snake, and the white crystals on its surface were quickly shattered, restoring it to its normal state.

Meanwhile, all of the Golden Immortal and True Immortals present had converged to surround Qi Tianxiao.

Ouyang Kuishan's trio wasn't surprised in the slightest to see this, nor did they display any intention to try and free Xiao Jinhan. Instead, all of them rose up into the air and began inspecting their surroundings as if they were standing on lookout duty.

Inside the ball of ice, Xiao Jinhan looked around at all of his assailants with a completely fearless expression as he said, "I'm assuming the Vast Flow Palace is also involved in this, right? On the way here, Lu Qinghai made up an excuse to divert away all of my subordinates. Now that your plan has succeeded, why don't you get him to come out as well?"

Everyone faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"Looks like there's been a misunderstanding, Palace Master Xiao. We actually only hatched this plan on the spur of the moment, and we're not colluding with the Vast Flow Palace. However, it seems like even the heavens are on our side, and Grand Palace Master Luo has certainly saved us a lot of trouble by diverting your subordinates away," Qi Tianxiao chuckled.

"Xiao Jinhan, ever since you took over the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, you've been nothing but a menace to our immortal region, lashing out at all of the major sects that possess the power to oppose you for your own selfish gain! You've already brought down the Blaze Dragon Dao, and now, you're trying to do the same to our Dawn Fall Sect!

“This is the day that you receive your retribution!" Feng Tiandu declared with a cold look in his eyes, while everyone else was also glowering intently at Xiao Jinhan with fierce killing intent.

Xiao Jinhan's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he declared in a cold voice, "I am the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace! If you dare to harm me, the Heavenly Court will strike you all down! None of you will be able to get away from the envoys sent down to avenge me!"

"That's right, we didn't dare to touch you back in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but here in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, who's going to find out?" Daoist Hu Yan chuckled coldly.

Chapter 482: Keep Watching

"Who are you? I don't think we've met before, so there certainly shouldn't be any vendetta between us. I presume you must be in disguise right now. Why is it that someone of your cultivation base doesn't even dare to show their face? Are you perhaps harboring some ulterior motives?" Xiao Jinhan asked as he turned to Daoist Hu Yan.

Everyone else also turned to Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni with a hint of suspicion in their eyes upon hearing this.

In response, Daoist Hu Yan's expression remained unchanged, and he displayed no intention of replying.

"Do not be swayed by Xiao Jinhan's baseless accusations, fellow daoists! He's already a spent force, and he's only trying to stall for time to delay the inevitable!" the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race suddenly said in a rather sharp and unpleasant voice.

"That's right! All of us have to attack at once to strike him down once and for all! If we let him escape, there will no longer be a place for us in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region!" Feng Tiandu declared with a determined look in his eyes.

Everyone's hearts stirred slightly upon hearing this, and the killing intent in their eyes became even more pronounced.

Feng Tiandu took a deep breath, then made a hand seal, and bright black light erupted out of his body, spreading in all directions to form a black spirit domain that was close to 30 kilometers in size, encompassing Xiao Jinhan within it.

A burst of formidable restrictive law powers spread through the spirit domain, immobilizing everything inside it.

Daoist Hu Yan and the others were caught off guard, and they also felt themselves being rooted to the spot, making any movement exceedingly difficult, while their immortal spiritual power circulation also slowed down significantly.

However, this sensation only lasted for an instant before fading, much to everyone's relief, but it also instilled within them a sense of apprehension toward Feng Tiandu.

The cave that Han Li was situated in was very far away from the site of the battle, so it wasn't encompassed within the black spirit domain, but he could still sense the law power fluctuations emanating from it.

This spirit domain seems to be even bigger than Qu Ling’s...

The size of a spirit domain was an important indication of a cultivator's power, so it seemed that Feng Tiandu was even more formidable than Qu Ling.

Enshrouded within Feng Tiandu's black spirit domain, the white light emanating from Xiao Jinhan's body instantly dimmed, while the light within his ball of white ice also diminished significantly.

At the same time, the black chains within his body suddenly lit up once again, seemingly resonating with the black spirit domain.

Xiao Jinhan's expression darkened even further upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, everyone else present also sprang into action.

Bright gray light erupted out of Qi Tianxiao's body, spreading outward to form a gray spirit domain in the blink of an eye.

This gray spirit domain was far smaller than Feng Tiandu's, but its gray light was tinged with a lifeless yellow color, and there was a nauseating odor of rot and decay permeating throughout it.

Furthermore, ripples that were visible even to the naked eye were spreading through the space within the spirit domain, as if even the very space itself were being eroded.

The spirit domain quickly spread to encompass everyone present, but of course, no one else was affected aside from Xiao Jinhan.

This was partially due to the fact that Qi Tianxiao was controlling the law powers within his spirit domain so that they didn't impact his allies, while the other factor was that his cultivation base was significantly inferior to Feng Tiandu's, and everyone else had already channeled their own law powers to protect themselves.

Almost at the exact same time, Daoist Hu Yan made a hand seal, and a burst of bright red light emerged over his body to form a series of scorching crimson fireballs.

The crimson light rapidly erupted outward in all directions, forming a fiery spirit domain that also encompassed Xiao Jinhan.

Meanwhile, the elderly woman of the Southern Dawn Race swept her golden cane through the air, and a burst of crimson light erupted out of her body as well, forming another fiery spirit domain.

Outside of those four, none of the other Golden Immortals unleashed their spirit domains, but all of them had summoned various immortal treasures and spirit treasures to bombard Xiao Jinhan with attacks.

Encompassed within four enemy spirit domains at once, a grim look appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face, and the spiritual light emanating from his body also diminished significantly.

However, he displayed no fear in the face of the barrage of oncoming attacks, and white light began to swirl within his eyes, forming a pair of white vortexes that were revolving incessantly.

A burst of bright white light surfaced over his body before spreading outward, quickly forming a white spirit domain that was slightly larger than Feng Tiandu's.

Gusts of white glacial wind were howling through the spirit domain, filling the entire area with a bone-chilling aura.

Enshrouded within the white spirit domain, everyone surrounding Xiao Jinhan involuntarily shuddered as their teeth began to chatter, and their bodies, immortal spiritual power, and souls were all encased within a burst of glacial power.

Feng Tiandu and the other Golden Immortals were able to envelop themselves in their own law powers to ward off some of this glacial power, but the True Immortals were unable to do the same, and all of them were frozen solid in the blink of an eye.

All of the spirit treasures and immortal treasures that had been summoned were also frozen into chunks of ice, and many of them began falling out of the sky.

Even though the True Immortals of the Dawn Fall Sect had all been frozen solid, layers of protective spiritual light had emerged over their bodies to ensure that their lives wouldn't be under threat for the time being. In contrast, the True Immortals of the Southern Dawn Race were a little weaker, and the one with the lowliest cultivation base among them was killed on the spot by the unbearable glacial aura.

The elderly woman's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this, and she swept a hand through the air to release a burst of red light that swept up the other Southern Dawn True Immortals before sending them flying away.

Feng Tiandu also swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of black light that carried all of the Dawn Fall Sect True Immortals away as well.

In a clash between spirit domains and law powers, True Immortals were nothing more than cannon fodder.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and a layer of white ice crystals had appeared over the immortal treasures summoned by the Golden Immortals, thereby slowing them down significantly, but they were all still hurtling toward Xiao Jinhan.

Several of the immortal treasures struck the ball of white ice around Xiao Jinhan, and it shuddered slightly, but was able to withstand the blows.

Xiao Jinhan paid no heed to what was happening outside as he began chanting an incantation while spiritual light flashed within his eyes, and eight translucent threads emerged around him before wrapping themselves around the surrounding black chains.

A layer of white light instantly appeared over the surface of the black chains, and the restrictive law powers within them were suppressed even further.

Xiao Jinhan then grabbed onto the black chains before tugging onto them forcefully, and all of them were instantly pulled out of his body.

With those black chains removed, his complexion instantly improved significantly.

"As expected of the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace to be able to struggle free from my Origin Separation Law Chains even while being subjected to four spirit domains at once! Having said that, your struggles are futile!" Feng Tiandu chuckled coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, instantly drawing the black chains back to himself.

At the same time, he raised his other hand before spreading his fingers open, and five streaks of black light shot out of his fingertips.

All of the black light within the spirit domain instantly surged into the streaks of black light in a frenzy, and they immediately swelled drastically in size before fusing as one to form a black vortex that was several dozen feet in size.

A burst of tremendous law power fluctuations erupted out of the vortex, and Feng Tiandu pointed a finger at it, sending it hurtling toward Xiao Jinhan like lightning.

In the blink of an eye, the black vortex appeared right in front of Xiao Jinhan, then exploded without any warning, sending countless streaks of black light shooting through the air to strike the ball of white ice around him.

At the same time, a huge gray palm projection emerged behind him amid a flash of gray light, and it came crashing down while giving off a formidable aura of decay.

The palm projection had been unleashed by none other than Qi Tianxiao, who had appeared behind Xiao Jinhan with a cold look on his face.

At the same time, red light flashed on either side of Xiao Jinhan, and Daoist Hu Yan and the elderly woman emerged one after the other, with the former wielding a giant crimson sword and the latter controlling a fiery dragon projection.

Both were giving off tremendous fire law power fluctuations as they struck the ball of white ice, and in the face of this devastating barrage of attacks, countless cracks instantly appeared over the surface of the ball of ice.

Immediately thereafter, it exploded violently before being completely inundated by black, gray, and red light.

Xiao Jinhan shot out of the explosion of light in a flash, but his robes were in tatters, and half of his body was drenched in blood, giving him a very disheveled appearance.

Right at this moment, another black vortex appeared in front of him without any warning, and it swept up his body like a giant black mouth.

As a result, Xiao Jinhan was instantly stopped cold in his tracks, then began to move involuntarily in accordance with the rotation of the vortex.

Immediately thereafter, Feng Tiandu appeared in front of Xiao Jinhan in a flash, and he swept a sleeve through the air as he declared, "Your fate is sealed, Xiao Jinhan!"

A huge black sword projection erupted out of his hand, and it came crashing down upon Xiao Jinhan with tremendous power, slicing his body into two in the blink of an eye.

"Damn, I was kind of rooting for him. Oh well, at least that means I get to have his nascent soul now. I'll grab it," Jin Tong said as she prepared to spring out of the cave in the distance.

"Wait!" Han Li called out as his hand shot forth like lightning to grab onto Jin Tong's little golden braid.

"Hey, you promised that I would get some Golden Immortal Stage nascent souls!" Jin Tong protested as she attempted to struggle free from Han Li's grasp, but to no avail.

"Keep watching, the show has only just begun," Han Li said.

......

Inside the valley, a faint smile appeared on Feng Tiandu's face at the sight of Xiao Jinhan's split body, but in the next instant, his smile abruptly stiffened.

As it turned out, no nascent soul had flown out of the two halves of Xiao Jinhan's body. Furthermore, his remains had transformed into a pair of translucent ice statues, which shattered into specks of white light that surged into the surrounding white spirit domain.

Chapter 483: Domain Spirit

As the ice statue shattered, a ball of white light emerged out of thin air in front of a mountain face around half a kilometer away from Feng Tiandu and the others, and it began to revolve on the spot, stirring up all of the surrounding snowflakes into a frenzy.

These snowflakes converged to form a block of ice that was around 10 feet tall in the blink of an eye, and the block of ice then exploded to reveal Xiao Jinhan, except he was looking even paler than before.

Even though he was looking rather worse for wear, the spirit domain that he had released still hadn't faded, and upon closer inspection, one would discover that the white light in the area immediately around his body was particularly dense, forming a translucent protective barrier that kept the power of the four opposing spirit domains at bay.

Feng Tiandu turned his gaze to Xiao Jinhan, and he gave a cold harrumph while making a hand seal, upon which the giant black sword in front of him instantly swiveled around before transforming into countless black sword projections that swept toward Xiao Jin Han like a torrential wave.

All of the other Golden Immortals also instantly set off in pursuit of Xiao Jinhan while unleashing attacks of their own.

A giant gray palm projection, an enormous fiery sword, and a crimson fiery dragon were sent hurtling toward Xiao Jinhan once again, and they were even more formidable than before.

As for the other Golden Immortals, they had no spirit domains of their own, so their mobility was quite significantly impacted by Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain, and as a result, they were lagging far behind.

Even though Xiao Jinhan was looking a little worse for wear, he wasn't displaying any signs of panic as he flew straight down as a streak of white light. Upon landing on the ground,he remained still on the spot as he raised his head to look up at Feng Tiandu and the others.

The entire sky above his head was already filled with spiritual light, and an assortment of attacks came crashing down upon him.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from the ground below, and all of a sudden, a white stone pillar that was several hundred feet tall abruptly erupted out of the ground.

Four more resounding booms rang out as an additional four white stone pillars emerged, forming a circle around Xiao Jinhan.

The five stone pillars were of a translucent white color, looking as if they had been forged from ice crystals, and they were riddled with countless strange patterns. Furthermore, there were numerous glowing white gemstones embedded into the pillars, and they were flashing incessantly like eyes.

Radiant white light erupted out of the five stone pillars, then quickly connected together to form a white light barrier that encompassed Xiao Jinhan within it.

All of the attacks unleashed by Feng Tiandu and the others struck the white light barrier with tremendous force, causing it to warp and tremble, and the runes on its surface swirled and churned.

It looked as if the light barrier could shatter at any moment, but it was ultimately able to hold itself together, much to the surprise of Feng Tiandu and the others.

Far away in the cave, Han Li wasn't all that surprised to see Xiao Jinhan escape from the spirit domains of his four assailants. After all, he had dared to come here on his own, so he had to have been prepared, and as the master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, it was only to be expected that he had some life-saving trump cards up his sleeve.

However, what did evoke a sense of surprise within him was the sight of the stone pillars that had emerged around Xiao Jinhan.

The five stone pillars were trembling slightly, and the spiritual light that they were releasing was becoming more and more radiant. There were also countless white runes swirling within the spiritual light like snowflakes before fusing into Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain.

The spirit domain rapidly expanded as a result, and its area was increased by twofold in the blink of an eye.

This was rather alarming to Han Li as the cave that he and Jin Tong were situated in was now also encompassed within the spirit domain.

Additionally, all of the Dawn Fall Sect and Southern Dawn Race True Immortals, as well as Ouyang Kuishan's trio, had also been swallowed up by the spirit domain.

Not only has the spirit domain expanded in size, the glacial qi within it was also rapidly becoming denser, as were the snowflakes swirling around in the air, and the potency of the ice law powers within the spirit domain had also been roughly doubled.

Inside the spirit domain, the rock faces of the valley were instantly covered in a thick layer of ice crystals, while a bed of snow appeared on the ground.

In the blink of an eye, the entire area within a radius of dozens of kilometers around the valley had been transformed into a world of ice and snow.

At the same time, a layer of ice crystals also appeared over the bodies of Feng Tiandu and the others, and they were instantly turned into ice statues.

The True Immortals in the distance were faring even worse. They had only just defrosted after being sent out of Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain, and now, they were frozen solid once again, with even their expressions frozen on their faces.

However, immediately thereafter, lights of different colors began to appear within the ice crystals that Feng Tiandu and the other Golden Immortals had transformed into.

The ice crystals that they were encased in were quickly shattered, but all of them were looking slightly pale.

Ouyang Kuishan and the other dao lords knew they couldn't just stand by passively any longer, and they also flew down to join Feng Tiandu and the others.

Meanwhile, for all of the True Immortals, this was the straw that broke the camel's back, and all of them were quickly frozen to death on the spot.

Feng Tiandu and the others were furious to see this, but they had too much on their plates to worry about those True Immortals.

"What are those five pillars? I've never heard of anything that can enhance the power of a spirit domain so drastically! And when did he even set them up?" Qi Tianxiao asked with a stunned expression.

Everyone else exchanged clueless glances with one another, and they were clearly just as perplexed.

Even Feng Tiandu seemed to have no idea what these pillars could be.

Even though they had a numbers advantage, their aura was being completely outmatched.

"You think I was completely oblivious to this little plot of yours? I was merely playing along so I could lure you all in and strike you all down at once! You will be the ones to die here today, not me!" Xiao Jinhan declared in a cold voice.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, the entirety of Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain began to rumble once again, and it was gradually suppressing the other four spirit domains.

Grim looks instantly appeared on the face of Feng Tiandu and the others, and they all channeled their cultivation arts in an attempt to enhance their spirit domains to keep Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain at bay, but to no avail.

"This is impossible! How could this restriction possibly elevate the power of a Golden Immortal's spirit domain to this extent?" Feng Tiandu murmured to himself with tightly furrowed brows.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a ball of white light emerged in the air above the five stone pillars, and countless streaks of white light appeared around it before converging toward it.

The ball of light instantly began to rapidly expand, transforming into a giant white figure that was over 100 feet tall.

The top half of the giant figure belonged to a man, but the bottom half was nothing more than a cloud of indistinct white mist that was churning incessantly, and the entire figure was giving off an astonishingly formidable law aura.

"This is a domain spirit! His spirit domain has been elevated to the third level, the Spiritform Stage!" Feng Tiandu exclaimed in a grim voice.

Everyone's expressions instantly changed drastically upon hearing this.

The domain spirit cast its gaze toward Feng Tiandu and the others, and its eyes were clear and lucid, looking no different from the eyes of a normal person.

With a sweep of its sleeves, the spirit domain around it instantly began to churn violently, and countless snowflakes converged around it while swirling incessantly to inundate its entire body.

In the blink of an eye, an enormous white glacial wave had taken shape, and it swept toward Feng Tiandu and the others with tremendous force.

Even before the giant glacial wave arrived, a burst of fearsome ice law powers had already descended upon everyone, and it encompassed too large an area for them to evade.

The entire space was encased in a layer of white ice crystals, and Feng Tiandu and the others were all frozen within it.

Immediately thereafter, spiritual light of different colors erupted out of their bodies to shatter the surrounding ice crystals, and Feng Tiandu declared, "Don't hold back anymore, fellow daoists! Otherwise, we really will be the ones to die here!"

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and his black sword instantly shot forth through the air, conjuring up countless identical black sword projections that converged to form a sea of black swords to oppose the glacial wave.

Everyone else also summoned all of their immortal treasures to support the sea of black swords, thereby further bolstering it as it surged toward the glacial wave.

......

Inside the cave, Han Li and Jin Tong were also affected by Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain, and both of them were instantly frozen into a pair of ice statues.

A burst of bone-chilling ice law powers spread through Han Li's entire body, striking him with a sense of excruciating pain. At the same time, his immortal spiritual power was also frozen solid, slowing its circulation to a crawl.

Han Li had faced ice law powers in the past during his battle against Han Qiu back in the Black Wind Sea, but compared with Xiao Jinhan, Han Qiu's ice law powers were like a candle next to the sun.

Immediately thereafter, a golden light barrier appeared over Han Li's entire body in a flash, and a burst of time law powers erupted out of the golden light barrier to keep the majority of the invading ice law powers at bay.

At the same time, a burst of tremendous force surged out of his body to shatter the ice crystals around him, and he remained unharmed through that brief ordeal.

While it was true that Xiao Jinhan's ice law powers were extremely formidable, he was able to escape injury thanks to his incredible physical constitution.

Meanwhile, the layer of ice crystals around Jin Tong was also shattered amid a flash of golden light, following which she cast her gaze toward the five stone pillars in the distance with a furious look on her face.

Her physical constitution was superior even to Han Li's, so she was naturally also completely unharmed, but being subjected to Xiao Jinhan's ice law powers had been a very painful experience for her.

In the next instant, radiant golden light emerged over her body, and a sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart as he hurriedly called out, "Jin Tong, wai..."

However, before he had a chance to finish his sentence, Jin Tong had already vanished from the spot.

His brows furrowed tightly as he stomped onto the ground in frustration, then abruptly vanished from the spot as well.

Chapter 484: Opposing the Domain Spirit

A resounding boom rang out as Xiao Jinhan's white glacial wave clashed against the opposing wave of immortal treasures, resulting in a clash of epic proportions.

The entire valley rumbled and swayed, while countless criss-crossing rifts appeared over the layer of ice that covered the ground.

Thankfully, the entire valley had already been frozen solid by the ice conjured up by Xiao Jinhan's spirit domain, which was far more resilient than normal ice. Otherwise, this entire area would've already been completely pulverized in the wake of such a formidable clash.

Even so, the valley was still beginning to collapse, and it wasn't going to be able to hold itself together for much longer.

The glacial wave shuddered violently before exploding and reverting back into a vast expanse of snowflakes that drifted away in all directions.

The wave of immortal treasures was also vanquished, and every single immortal treasure within it was also encased in a thick layer of ice that significantly hampered their spiritual nature.

Right at this moment, a white figure shot out of the swirling ice and snow, and it was none other than the white domain spirit.

The domain spirit was pouncing at the nearest Golden Immortal, which was a portly elderly man from the Dawn Fall Sect, and white light flashed over its fingertips, upon which all of its fingernails elongated to several feet in length, resembling a set of sharp sword as they pierced toward the elderly man's head.

The elderly man's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this, and he shot back in retreat while opening his mouth to release a red flying dagger, which swelled to several times its original size in the blink of an eye.

There was an extremely life-like phoenix design engraved onto the dagger, and it was giving off radiant white light.

The elderly man made a hand seal, and the phoenix suddenly spread its wings as if it had sprung to life, and its entire body was radiating dazzling red light.

Bursts of crimson flames emerged over the flying dagger to form a fiery phoenix projection, which was giving off formidable fire law power fluctuations as it swept toward the white domain spirit.

The domain spirit made no effort to take evasive measures, and radiant white light erupted out of its right hand as it reached straight into the phoenix projection.

The fiery phoenix instantly let loose an anguished wail as it faded away into nothingness, while the flying dagger was caught in the grasp of the domain spirit. It was instantly trapped in a thick layer of white ice, rendering it completely immobilized.

The rotund elderly man was astonished to see this.

The red flying dagger didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but it was actually one of his most powerful treasures. It had been refined using a set of true spirit phoenix remains that he had found by chance, and it was capable of unleashing extremely formidable phoenix true flames, but it was made to look like a toy in the face of the domain spirit.

The white domain spirit then swept its left hand through the air like lightning, releasing five streaks of white glacial light that appeared in front of the rotund elderly man in the blink of an eye.

The elderly man was greatly alarmed by this, and he hurriedly rubbed his hands together before thrusting his palms into his own body.

Several protective light barriers of different colors instantly appeared around him, and he shot back in retreat as quickly as he could.

However, the protective light barriers weren't able to pose any resistance against the five streaks of glacial light, and they were torn apart with ease.

A look of alarm and horror instantly appeared in the elderly man's face upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a burst of gray light shot forth from the side, then transformed into a giant gray hand that managed to keep four of the streaks of glacial light at bay, but one of them was able to slip through the cracks and glide past the elderly man's left arm.

The arm was instantly amputated at the shoulder before plummeting out of the sky as a block of ice. No blood flowed out of the wound. Instead, it was covered in a layer of white ice crystals that began to rapidly spread toward other parts of his body.

The elderly man immediately summoned an azure talisman with his remaining hand before adhering to the wound.

The talisman instantly exploded to form a ball of green light that enveloped the wound, and the spread of the ice crystals was immediately slowed.

At the same time, the elderly man continued to shoot back in retreat until he was a relatively safe distance away from the white domain spirit.

The domain spirit immediately set off in pursuit, but right at this moment, the gray hand swelled to around twice its original size amid a flash of black light, then grabbed onto the domain spirit like lightning.

At the same time, a giant white seal, an azure jade ring, and a gray jade scepter shot forth from afar. These were the immortal treasures of the other three Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals, and they struck the domain spirit with tremendous force, causing it to explode into a vast expanse of white light.

"Are you alright, Elder Yan?" Qi Tianxiao asked as he appeared beside the rotund elderly man before pointing a finger at him, and a crimson talisman shot out of his fingertip, giving off faint fire law power fluctuations as it transformed into a ball of red light that vanished into the elderly man's body.

A layer of pulsing red light instantly appeared over the wound on his shoulder to ward off the invasive ice crystals.

"I'm fine. I didn't expect this domain spirit to be so powerful. Thank you for saving me, Sect Master," the rotund elderly man replied.

"A domain spirit can draw upon all of the law power within a spirit domain, so it's no less formidable than Xiao Jinhan himself. Make sure to be on your guard, everyone. I may not be able to protect all of you from here onward," Qi Tianxiao said in a grim voice.

Grim looks appeared on the faces of all of the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators upon hearing this, but they quickly realized that they had nothing to fear as the domain spirit had already been slain just now.

Given how powerful the domain spirit was, surely it wouldn't be easy to conjure one up, so they didn't have to worry about it for the foreseeable future.

However, right at this moment, the vast expanse of white spiritual light that the domain spirit had disintegrated into suddenly began to converge toward a single spot, and another domain spirit emerged amid a flash of white light, much to the shock and dismay of all of the Golden Immortals present.

With a sweep of the domain spirit's sleeve, all of the snowflakes within the spirit domain began to churn and surge once again, forming another enormous glacial wave that was even larger than the one before.

Everyone immediately braced themselves to oppose the glacial wave, only for Feng Tiandu to appear in front of them in a flash.

"A domain spirit isn't that easy to destroy. Go and destroy those five stone pillars! In the meantime, I'll hold off the domain spirit."

Radiant black light erupted out of Feng Tiandu's body as he spoke, and countless bursts of black qi instantly surged out of the black spirit domain around him.

At the same time, he began chanting an incantation while releasing a string of incantation seals, and a series of black chains emerged within the black qi.

All of the black qi instantly converged toward a single spot to form a giant black mountain, which stood directly in the path of the glacial wave.

A resounding boom rang out, and the black mountain shuddered violently, as did the chains around it, many of which were snapped, but the glacial wave was ultimately kept at bay.

Feng Tiandu peered into the glacial wave, and black light flashed within his eyes as he thrust a palm into the black mountain.

Black light flashed over the mountain as well, and a series of chains shot out of the mountain before piercing into the glacial wave like lightning to tie up the white domain spirit.

Everyone's expressions eased slightly upon seeing this, and they immediately swooped down toward the stone pillars below.

A cold harrumph rang out from within the white light barrier at the center of the stone pillars, and countless bursts of white light converged from all directions, forming a huge white net that swooped toward everyone.

A burst of incredibly formidable ice law powers instantly surged out of the net, and everyone knew that they would be in immense trouble if they were to be ensnared by the net.

Hence, they immediately stopped cold in their tracks, then parted down the middle to try and skirt around the net.

However, the white net abruptly expanded outward, instantly swelling to several times its original size to stop everyone again.

Qi Tian opened his mouth to release a burst of gray light, interspersed throughout which were four or five gray law threads, all of which vanished into the gray jade scepter.

The scepter instantly began to glow radiantly and swelled to several dozen times its original size. At the same time, gray light flashed over its tip, and a gray serpentine head with a large fleshy growth on its head emerged.

The serpentine head opened its mouth to release a cloud of dense gray mist, which transformed into four or five huge gray pythons.

The serpent's body was covered in scales that were riddled with countless gray patterns, giving it quite a fearsome appearance, and it released a vast expanse of corrosive law powers that struck the white net.

The corrosive law powers instantly began eating away at the net rapidly, and before long, several large holes had appeared on it.

The other Golden Immortals were ecstatic to see this, and they flew through those holes in the net to continue on toward the stone pillars.

Qi Tianxiao made a hand seal, and the huge gray pythons abruptly fused as one into a giant python that was over 1,000 feet in length, then swooped down to strike the white light barrier around the stone pillars with tremendous force.

A resounding boom rang out as the white light barrier rippled slightly, then immediately returned to normal.

Qi Tianxiao faltered slightly upon seeing this.

They had previously attacked this white light barrier, but it hadn't been that resilient at the time.

Immediately thereafter, everyone else's attacks also arrived.

Three golden flying swords shot out of the bodies of Ouyang Kuishan's trio, and they instantly transformed into three giant golden swords that were radiating dazzling golden light.

All of the patterns on the flying swords began to glow radiantly, and there were countless golden runes dancing within the golden light.

Each of the three Blaze Dragon Dao dao lords expelled a mouthful of blood essence, then made a hand seal, and the golden light radiating from the three giant swords brightened even further as they fused as one to form a single golden sword that was 3,000 to 4,000 feet in length.

Under the collective efforts of the three dao lords, the enormous golden sword reared up before crashing down toward the white light barrier.

Meanwhile, the elderly woman raised a hand, and the two golden canes shot forth through the air once again while transforming into a pair of golden dragons that were each several hundred feet in length.

At the same time, two balls of red light containing a pair of red bracelets flew out of her sleeve, and they fitted themselves around the necks of the two golden dragons in a flash.

Crimson flames were instantly ignited over the bodies of the golden dragons, transforming them into a pair of fiery dragons, and their auras also swelled drastically as they pounced at the white light barrier.

Immediately thereafter, the clear cry of a crane rang out across the entire valley.

A ball of scorching descended from the heavens, containing a fiery crimson bird that was several hundred feet in size. There was a fiery crown on its head, giving it a sense of regal majesty and an appearance similar to that of the legendary Vermilion Bird.

The fiery bird lashed out with its enormous talons, unleashing streaks of crimson sword qi that also hurtled directly toward the white light barrier.

At the same time, a giant blue wheel that was over 1,000 feet in size appeared beside the fiery bird in a flash before immediately beginning to revolve rapidly..

Bursts of radiant blue light appeared over the giant wheel, then transformed into numerous blue ice spikes that filled the entire surrounding area in a radius of several hundred feet.

All of the ice spikes had hints of law powers swirling around them, and in the next instant, all of them were also sent flying toward the white light barrier as if they had been fired out of crossbows.

The crimson fiery bird and the giant blue wheel were being controlled by none other than Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, respectively.

Chapter 485: Unexpected

Immediately following the crimson Vermilion Bird and the giant blue wheel came a massive white seal, an azure jade bracelet, and a crimson bead, all of which were hurtling through the air from different directions. The other three Golden Immortals of the Dawn Fall Sect had unleashed attacks of their own, and of course, they were all directed at the white light barrier as well.

It was clear that everyone was determined to kill Xiao Jinhan, and this barrage of attacks was significantly more formidable than the one that had been unleashed against the restriction at the entrance of the High Zenith Palace.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out, and the white light barrier warped and trembled violently as the spiritual light on its surface quickly faded.

However, for some reason, it had become several times more resilient than before, and it displayed no signs of breaking.

Not only that, but countless white runes had appeared over the light barrier, and as these runes began to flash, countless specks of spiritual light converged within the surrounding spirit domain before surging into the light barrier, and spiritual light radiating from it began to quickly recover again.

Everyone's expressions changed once again upon seeing this, and Qi Tianxiao's brows furrowed slightly as he made a hand seal, upon which the giant gray python sprang forth before wrapping itself several times around the white light barrier.

Countless gray runes emerged over its body, and clouds of liquid-like gray mist spilled out to envelop the entire white light barrier.

Due to the corrosive effects of the gray mist, the recovery of the light barrier wasn't instantly slowed, but the rate of erosion was lagging far behind the rate of recovery, so the detrimental effect was virtually negligible.

A hint of urgency appeared in Qi Tianxiao's eyes upon seeing this, and he was just about to call upon everyone to attack again when a resounding boom suddenly rang out from the ground below.

Immediately thereafter, countless shards of ice were sent flying in all directions as a giant golden beetle that was several hundred feet in size flew out.

Qi Tianxiao faltered slightly at the sight of the golden beetle, which spread open its legs to grab onto the white light barrier before hacking viciously at it with its sharp claws.

The giant gray python was instantly sliced into several pieces by the gray beetle, and its body disintegrated into a vast cloud of gray mist amid an anguished wail.

Qi Tianxiao was astonished to see this. Even though the gray python had been formed by gray mist, it was interspersed with his law threads, so it possessed just as much structural integrity as the average immortal treasure, yet the golden beetle had managed to tear it apart with ease.

Everyone else was also completely rooted to the spot, and they had no idea whether this golden beetle was friend or foe, but Feng Tiandu's eyes lit up slightly as he caught sight of the golden beetle while still locked in battle against the white domain spirit.

The golden beetle paid no heed to any of the Golden Immortals present as it opened its mouth up wide, and a pair of scythelike sharp teeth sprang out of its mouth.

These two teeth were different from its other golden teeth in that their coloration was far lighter, and they were also slightly translucent.

The golden beetle chomped down onto the white light barrier with ferocious might, and its two sharp fangs were able to tear a pair of long gashes into the light barrier with ease, even though it had managed to withstand such a ferocious barrage of attacks from the other Golden Immortals.

Immediately thereafter, the white light barrier exploded with a dull thump to reveal the five stone pillars inside.

The stone pillars were riddled with countless complex white patterns that extended all the way down onto the ground, where they intertwined to form an extremely complex white array.

At this moment, Xiao Jinhan was seated at the center of the array, and he was just as flabbergasted as everyone else.

"How dare you use your ice to freeze me!" the golden beetle yelled in the voice of a little girl, then pounced directly at Xiao Jinhan as a ball of golden light.

Is this... a Gold Devouring Immortal? But that's impossible!

A perplexed look flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes, and he remained seated as he made a hand seal.

The white array around him instantly began to glow brightly as a thick streak of white light emerged, then instantly transformed into a sharp sword that shot forth like lightning to strike the ball of golden light.

A loud clang rang out as the ball of golden light was sent flying, and it faded to reveal the golden beetle tumbling end over end through the air.

However, after the golden beetle steadied itself, it was revealed that only a faint white mark had appeared on its golden shell.

In the next instant, the golden beetle began to rapidly shrink, reducing itself to only the size of a millstone, following which it pounced at Xiao Jinhan once again, this time reaching around twice the speed as during its previous attack.

However, as soon as it drew close to the stone pillars, the array on the ground lit up once again, and another streak of swordlight shot forth to strike it with unerring accuracy, sending it flying back through the air once again.

The golden beetle was becoming even more enraged, and it was just about to fly forward once again when it suddenly stopped in its tracks and took a glance in a certain direction, following which it abruptly vanished from the spot.

Xiao Jinhan was rather taken aback to see this, and before he could do anything else, Qi Tianxiao and the others descended out of the sky to surround him and the five stone pillars.

Everyone took a collective glance at the spot where the golden beetle had been just a moment ago, and a hint of bewilderment flashed through their eyes, but they quickly turned their attention back to Xiao Jinhan.

"It looks like even the heavens are on our side! You should surrender and accept your fate, Palace Master Xiao!" Qi Tianxiao declared as he made a hand seal, and his gray jade scepter instantly began to glow radiantly while releasing a cloud of dense gray mist.

A giant gray dragon took shape around the gray scepter, and it pounced at Xiao Jinhan with almighty power.

All of the other Golden Immortals were also attacking Xiao Jinhan from all directions with their immortal treasures, and in response, Xiao Jinhan began to chant an incantation while flicking his fingers through the air in rapid succession, sending a string of incantation seals flying into the five stone pillars around him.

The attacks unleashed by Qi Tianxiao and the others had only just drawn close to the stone pillars when the white array on the ground began to revolve rapidly, and around a dozen thick beams of white light shot out of the array in all directions.

A string of resounding booms rang out as all of the oncoming attacks were sent flying or kept at bay, and not even a single one of them was able to slip through the cracks, much to the dismay of the surrounding Golden Immortals.

Having observed the white array in action from above, the Golden Immortals had thought that Xiao Jinhan was actively controlling the array to ward off the golden beetle, but it seemed that this wasn't actually the case. Instead, the array possessed the ability to sense attacks and react accordingly.

Right at this moment, the light emanating from the array suddenly began to fluctuate erratically in brightness, while the patterns on the five stone pillars were rapidly becoming brighter.

Radiant white light erupted out of the five stone pillars, then converged to form a thick pillar of white light that shot forth straight up toward the heavens.

The entire white spirit domain shuddered as countless specks of spiritual light converged from all directions, while the pillar of white light grew brighter and brighter.

Seven or eight balls of white light appeared within the pillar of white light in a flash, and they began to rapidly expand.

Feng Tiandu's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly yelled, "Stop him! He's about to conjure up another domain spirit! You have to destroy these stone pillars before that!"

While it was true that he could hold his own against this formidable domain spirit, he wasn't going to be able to completely destroy it anytime soon, and if even more domain spirits were to be conjured up, then everyone would be well and truly in a dire situation.

Upon hearing Feng Tiandu's urgent call, Qi Tianxiao and the others hurriedly summoned a wide array of immortal treasures and high-grade talismans to attack the five stone pillars, but Xiao Jinhan merely made a hand seal with a derisive sneer on his face.

The white array flashed momentarily before releasing several dozen more beams of white light to keep all of the oncoming attacks at bay once again.

An urgent look appeared in Qi Tianxiao's eyes as he opened his mouth to expel a ball of blood essence, which vanished into his gray jade scepter.

The scepter immediately began to glow brightly, and the serpentine head on its tip detached itself from the rest of the scepter and flew out to transform into a giant gray serpentine head.

The serpentine head opened its cavernous mouth to devour the white light standing in its path, and with the obstacle eliminated, the jade scepter was able to fly forward as a streak of gray light, appearing in front of one of the stone pillars in a flash.

In the blink of an eye, the jade scepter transformed into a giant gray blade, the edge of which was etched with countless gray runes. The blade was giving off a burst of intensely corrosive law power as it struck the white stone pillar with tremendous force, and a hint of surprise flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes upon seeing this, but he made no attempt to stop the attack.

The gray blade exploded violently like a wave crashing against the rocks, and the jade scepter re-emerged, but the spiritual light on its surface had dimmed significantly, and it was sent flying back through the air.

As for the stone pillar, it merely swayed slightly before immediately stabilizing itself again.

"Impossible!" Qi Tianxiao exclaimed.

This didn't seem like a very remarkable transformation from the jade scepter, but it was actually its most powerful attacking form, yet it hadn't even managed to leave a mark on the stone pillar.

The stone pillars were extraordinarily resilient, and it was no wonder that Xiao Jinhan wasn't concerned about them at all.

At the same time, a resounding boom rang out from the other side. As it turned out, a thin streak of golden light that resembled a blade had erupted out of the elderly woman's golden cane, and it had somehow managed to bypass the white array to strike another one of the stone pillars.

However, just like before, this pillar also only swayed slightly before steadying itself again, and it remained completely unscathed.

The elderly woman and Qi Tianxiao exchanged a glance upon seeing this, and both of them could see their own astonishment mirrored in each other's eyes.

A cold sneer appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face as he continued to make hand seals, and the light radiating from the white array grew brighter and brighter, while streaks of white light converged from all parts of the spirit domain before surging into the balls of light within the pillar of white light.

Limbs and heads began to sprout out of the balls of light, and an ecstatic look appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face upon seeing this as he began to make hand seals with even greater urgency.

Right at this moment, things took a completely unexpected turn.

Chapter 486: Gold Devouring Immortal

All of a sudden, golden light flashed from the ground beneath one of the white stone pillars, and a golden beetle shot out of the ice before pouncing at the nearest pillar.

A thick beam of white light shot out of the white array, transforming into a white sword in the blink of an eye as it hurtled toward the golden beetle at an incredible speed.

The golden beetle opened its mouth to release a ball of golden light, which transformed into a golden vortex, and the white sword was instantly sucked into the vortex, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, the golden beetle continued onward without pause, appearing in front of the white stone pillar in a flash, then instantly swelled to several hundred feet in size before grabbing onto the pillar with its legs.

It then opened its mouth again, and the pair of scythe-like fangs shot out before it chomped down viciously onto the stone pillar.

In the face of its peerlessly sharp fangs, the stone pillar was made to look extremely fragile, and a loud crack rang out as a mark was bitten onto it.

Xiao Jinhan's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of white light that vanished into the stone pillar in a flash.

The pillar instantly began to glow radiantly, and a translucent membrane much like Han Li's True Extreme Film appeared on its surface, giving it an indestructible appearance.

However, the golden beetle's fangs were able to pierce through this membrane with ease before sinking into the stone pillar.

A crack instantly appeared on the pillar's surface, and the pillar of white light above it immediately began to ripple violently, while the balls of light inside also began to tremble in an unstable fashion.

A furious look appeared on Xiao Jinhan's face upon seeing this, and he sprang to his feet before sweeping both sleeves through the air.

The white array around him began to buzz and revolve rapidly as a thick beam of white light that was looking rather shaky and unstable was sent flying toward the golden beetle.

At the same time, two streaks of translucent white light shot out of Xiao Jinhan's hands, and they were revealed to be a pair of long white halberds that were giving off a formidable glacial aura and tremendous law power fluctuations.

As the pair of halberds hurtled through the air, they swelled drastically in size, transforming into two streaks of white light, and they reached the golden beetle before the beam of white light did.

Two metallic clangs rang out as the pair of halberds crashed down onto the golden beetle's neck, sending sparks flying in all directions.

A pair of long white marks appeared on the golden beetle's neck, and the skin there seemed to have split open slightly, but not a single drop of blood flowed out.

Immediately thereafter, the golden beetle reared up to devour the pair of white halberds, crunching on them a few times before promptly swallowing them. A burst of golden light then surged over its body, and the tiny gashes on its neck were quickly healed.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Qi Tianxiao and the other Golden Immortals were naturally ecstatic to see this.

A Golden Immortal Stage Gold Devouring Immortal? How is this possible?

Xiao Jinhan felt as if he had been thrust into a nightmare. Those two halberds were a prized trump card of his that he had refrained from unleashing upon to this point, and they were capable of tearing through virtually anything, yet not were they barely able to scratch the shell of the golden beetle, they had been eaten!

Immediately thereafter, the thick beam of white light struck the golden beetle, and countless runes were flashing within the white light, giving off an immense glacial aura.

A white ice mountain abruptly appeared out of thin air, freezing both the golden beetle and the white stone pillar within it.

Despite this, the golden beetle didn't appear to have been affected at all, and it was able to quickly struggle free from the ice around it before continuing to sink its fangs into the stone pillar, rapidly widening the cracks that had already appeared on its surface.

Before Xiao Jinhan had a chance to do anything else, the white stone pillar was snapped with a loud crack.

With the destruction of the stone pillar, the white array at the center of the pillars instantly dimmed slightly.

The pillar of white light above the stone pillars also faded, and the balls of white light within it exploded immediately thereafter.

The white light around Xiao Jinhan's body also shuddered violently, and his complexion paled significantly as he threw up a large mouthful of blood.

This sequence of events also caused the white spirit domain that encompassed the entire valley to tremble and ripple while rapidly shrinking down to its original size. In fact, it was even weaker than before and looked as if it could disintegrate entirely at any moment.

Qi Tianxiao and the others were ecstatic to see this, and three spirit domains, one gray and two red, instantly emerged, trapping Xiao Jinhan within them.

At the same time, a series of immortal treasures were sent flying toward him from all directions.

A hint of panic flashed through Xiao Jinhan's eyes as he hurriedly swept both sleeves through the air, and his spirit domain instantly shrank down even further, but as a result, it had become denser.

At the same time, countless snowflakes began swirling around him, forming a white light barrier in the blink of an eye.

The light barrier was only able to withstand the barrage of immortal treasures for a few seconds before it was shattered, but the immortal treasures were also sent flying back.

Xiao Jinhan's complexion paled even further as he threw up another mouthful of blood, and his aura had also diminished significantly.

However, there was no time for him to rest, and bright white light erupted out of his body as he shot back in retreat.

Right at this moment, the space around him rippled, and around a dozen black chains shot out in a flash before wrapping themselves around him almost instantaneously.

The white light around his body quickly faded, and he was instantly immobilized by the black chains. His aura was also completely restrained in the blink of an eye, and it was as if he had been reduced to a mere mortal.

Immediately thereafter, Feng Tiandu appeared behind him in a flash.

"Feng Tiandu! If you kill me, the Heavenly Court will be sure to hunt you down!" Xiao Jinhan roared.

Feng Tiandu paid no heed to those threats as he declared, "Looks like even the heavens are against you, Palace Master Xiao."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and a streak of translucent black light shot out of his hand before gliding over Xiao Jinhan's body.

His expression instantly stiffened, and in the next instant, his entire body was split in half from head to toe, sending blood and entrails gushing down onto the ground.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light shot out of his remains, and it was none other than his nascent soul.

The nascent soul was completely unaffected by the three enemy spirit domains as it fled the scene at an incredible speed, covering a distance of close to 10 kilometers in the blink of an eye.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Tiandu's face as he flicked a finger through the air, and a burst of spatial fluctuations emerged in front of Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul, following which a series of black chains appeared.

It was as if the chains had already been set up there well in advance, and they intertwined with one another to form a large black net in the blink of an eye before sweeping toward the nascent soul.

Formidable restrictive law power fluctuations were emanating from the black net, sealing the entire surrounding space in a radius of several hundred feet.

Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul wore a grim expression as it opened its mouth to release a white bead.

The white bead exploded to release an eruption of white light, which gave off a bone-chilling glacial aura.

The black net of chains was slowed down significantly by the glacial aura, and a layer of white ice crystals appeared over its surface, while its restrictive law powers were also significantly diminished.

The nascent soul took advantage of this brief opening to dart away to the side as a streak of white light, then continued to fly away into the distance.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately shot forth in pursuit of the nascent soul as a streak of black light.

If he were to allow Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul to get away, then the consequences would be catastrophic!

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light flashed past up ahead, and Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul abruptly vanished into thin air.

Feng Tiandu faltered slightly upon seeing this, and he stopped cold in his tracks before looking around to discover that the streak of golden light had stopped not far away from him.

The golden light faded to reveal the golden beetle, which had already freed itself from the ice mountain and had shrunk down to roughly the size of a human head.

Held in the golden beetle's mouth was none other than Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul, which was struggling with all its might, but in complete futility.

"You froze me, and now, I'm going to eat you, so we're even, silver beard!" the golden beetle declared as a burst of golden light flew out of its mouth to suck in the nascent soul.

The surrounding spirit domain of snow and ice flashed a few times before disintegrating, while the five stone pillars rapidly shrank down, reverting back to a set of pillars that were each only around 10 feet tall.

Feng Tiandu faltered slightly at the sight of Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul being devoured, following which a hint of greed flashed through his eyes as he sized up the golden beetle.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he released a burst of black light that swept up Xiao Jinhan's remains before delivering a white storage bracelet into his grasp.

Meanwhile, the other Golden Immortals had all stowed away their immortal treasures and were flying toward Feng Tiandu.

The golden beetle was on the verge of being surrounded by these formidable Golden Immortals, but it didn't seem to have a care in the world as it swallowed Xiao Jinhan's nascent soul, then climbed back onto the toppled stone pillar and began munching on it once again.

Qi Tianxiao took a glance at Feng Tiandu, then began to fly around in a covert fashion to get behind the golden beetle.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light suddenly flashed past, and a figure instantly appeared between Qi Tianxiao and the golden beetle.

Qi Tianxiao immediately stopped in his tracks, and his brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the figure that had just arrived on the scene.

It was none other than Han Li in disguise, and upon spotting Han Li's arrival, Jin Tong reverted back into the form of a little girl, which was still holding the remnants of the stone pillar in her arms.

Han Li took a glance at Qi Tianxiao, then turned to Jin Tong as he asked, "Has someone been picking on you, Jin Tong?"

As he was speaking, he made no attempt to suppress his own aura, intentionally revealing the entirety of his mid-Golden Immortal Stage cultivation base.

"I just ate silver beard. That's what he gets for freezing me!" Jin Tong replied as she licked her lips with her little tongue.

All of the other Golden Immortals immediately stopped what they were doing, and instead of continuing to approach Jin Tong, they began sizing up her and Han Li with wary looks in their eyes.

It had naturally already become apparent to them that this harmless-looking little girl was actually a Gold Devouring Immortal that possessed Golden Immortal Stage power.

None of them had ever heard of anyone from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region owning such a formidable Gold Devouring Immortal, and such a person was definitely not to be taken lightly.

Chapter 487: Golden Cloud Pill Tribulation

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni were also quite startled by Han Li's sudden arrival, and it was clear that they had no idea how Han Li had become a Golden Immortal in just a few months, as well as where he had gotten this Golden Immortal Stage Gold Devouring Immortal from.

"Why are you so late, Uncle?" Jin Tong complained with a displeased expression, completely unbothered by the sinister scrutiny she was receiving from the surrounding Golden Immortals.

Han Li turned to her and gave her a subtle look as he said, "If you've had your fill, then take a rest."

Jin Tong wasn't actually a clueless child, so she was naturally able to glean Han Li's intentions, and she pointed at the remnants of the array as she said, "This is all mine! I'm still not done eating yet, so make sure no one else takes it!"

"I'll pack it all up for you to eat later," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Fine," Jin Tong complied with a reluctant expression.

With that, Han Li cast a string of incantation seals toward the four and a half white stone pillars that were still standing, casually stowing the entire array away right before everyone's eyes.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong swept her gaze over Feng Tiandu and the others in a provocative manner, then said, "Make sure to call on me if you run into any other good treasures."

After that, she shrank down into a tiny golden beetle amid a flash of golden light, then circled around in the air for a moment before landing on Han Li's left ring finger, fitting onto the finger like a golden ring. while everyone else looked on with mixed emotions.

Just now, Xiao Jinhan was only an instant away from unleashing his ultimate trump card, which wasn't guaranteed to be able to completely turn the tide of the battle in his favor, but it would've definitely posed an immense challenge for everyone, and they would've all but certainly failed to strike him down.

It was precisely due to the sudden arrival of this Gold Devouring Immortal that Xiao Jinhan's plans had been completely foiled, ultimately leading to his demise.

In the wake of Xiao Jinhan's death, Han Li had suddenly arrived on the scene and casually subdued the Gold Devouring Immortal as its master, leading everyone to speculate about his identity.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened slightly as he began to size up Han Li, while all of the other Dawn Fall Sect cultivators were also watching Han Li with a hint of wariness and enmity in their eyes.

Meanwhile, the two Golden Immortals of the Southern Dawn Race exchanged a puzzled glance with one another.

Prior to entering the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, they had interacted briefly with the cultivators of the True Flame Sect, so they had some recollection of Han Li's current appearance.

However, they recalled that back then, he had only been at the late-True Immortal Stage and hadn't displayed any remarkable traits, so how he had suddenly returned as a Golden Immortal?

Right at this moment, Daoist Hu Yan suddenly approached Han Li as he asked, "Where did you go, Tianyu? You had me worried sick!"

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he made his way over to Daoist Hu Yan in a leisurely fashion, while everyone else looked on with surprise in their eyes.

"My apologies, Uncle. I was trapped in an underground palace earlier, and as soon as I got out, I noticed that something was happening here, so I came here right away," Han Li explained.

On the surface, Daoist Hu Yan offered no response to this, but he was understandably raising questions to Han Li in secret through voice transmission. "What is going on, Fellow Daoist Li? How did your cultivation base..."

"Here, I'll tell you the truth. I was trapped in an underground palace, only to re-emerge an instant later as a Golden Immortal. Do you believe me?" Han Li replied in a resigned voice.

"Of course not!" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed.

Meanwhile, Yun Ni was also communicating to Daoist Hu Yan through voice transmission. "Perhaps he cultivated some type of reincarnation secret technique, and he concealed his own cultivation base in the past so that he could secure our sect's Formless True Axis Scripture."

There was naturally no way that anyone would believe such a story, and the enmity that had earlier been solely directed toward Han Li from Feng Tiandu and the others had expanded to include Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni as well.

Right at this moment, Ouyang Kuishan's trio suddenly approached Daoist Hu Yan as well, and it was clear that they were aware of his true identity.

Perhaps they had chosen to side with Daoist Hu Yan as they had once been part of the same sect, or perhaps they were simply wary of the Dawn Fall Sect. In any case, their decision had completely changed the complexion of the situation, and a tense atmosphere descended upon the entire scene once again.

A mocking sneer appeared on Feng Tiandu's face as he cast his gaze toward the two Southern Dawn Race Golden Immortals, and among them, the elderly man turned to the elderly woman with an inquisitive expression, in response to which the latter shook her head, refusing to take either side.

Right as the tension in the valley was beginning to build, a resounding boom suddenly rang out high up in the sky, and everyone immediately turned their attention upward to find that countless rays of golden light had converged up above, quickly forming an enormous golden cloud.

Golden light was surging throughout the cloud, illuminating the entire sky with dazzling golden radiance, and tremendous energy fluctuations were sweeping out of the cloud, causing all of the world's origin qi in a radius of several dozen kilometers to churn incessantly.

A burst of tremendous pressure came crashing down from above alongside a flash of blinding light, and everything was illuminated a bright golden color.

This was a phenomenon that wasn't unfamiliar to Han Li, and his expression changed slightly as he turned to Daoist Hu Yan and said, "This is a pill tribulation! Could it be..."

"That's right. This valley is most likely where the High Zenith Palace is situated, and that's where High Zenith Pills are being refined. The arrival of the pill tribulation indicates that a critical stage has been reached in the pill refinement process," Daoist Hu Yan confirmed with a nod.

Feng Tiandu took a glance up at the sky, then turned his gaze to the white stone wall within the valley, and he discovered that the scenery engraved upon it seemed to have sprung to life, with the rivers flowing and the birds taking flight.

At the same time, the white light barrier around it began to become denser again.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out in the sky above the valley. "You sure got here nice and early, Fellow Daoist Feng!"

A blue water lotus flower then slowly descended out of the sky, and it vanished into thin air as soon as it landed on the ground.

Two figures were revealed, and they were none other than Luo Qinghai and his young disciple, Nan Kemeng. As for the other Vast Flow Palace cultivators, they weren't present for some reason.

After landing on the ground, Luo Qinghai took a casual glance at everyone in the valley, and his gaze lingered on Han Li for an extra second.

"I may have come early, but you came at just the right time, Fellow Daoist Luo. You've arrived right as the pill tribulation emerged," Feng Tiandu replied with a fake smile.

Luo Qinghai paid no heed to Feng Tiandu's cold demeanor as he said, "It looks like this must be the true location of the High Zenith Palace. Earlier, I discovered an underwater palace that was filled with traps, and we went to great lengths to traverse through the palace, only to find that it wasn't even the right place. By the way, where's Fellow Daoist Xiao? He doesn't seem to be around."

Internally, Feng Tiandu was cursing Luo Qinghai for his shamelessness. He had to have already arrived well in advance and observed the entire battle that was waged against Xiao Jinhan, only to show himself now in order to reap the spoils.

If it weren't for the sudden emergence of the pill tribulation, he most likely wouldn't even have shown himself now and would've only come out of hiding after the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators had battled everyone else in the valley.

"Palace Master Xiao is a busy and blessed man. Perhaps he's already stumbled upon a more significant treasure and is no longer interested in this place," Feng Tiandu replied in a cold voice.

Among all of the powers in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the only one that he had regarded as a threat was the Blaze Dragon Dao, and among all of the immortal region's cultivators, Xiao Jinhan was certainly a fierce rival of his, but in his heart, Xiao Jinhan was inferior to Baili Yan.

As for Luo Qinghai, Feng Tiandu had always looked down on him.

"I suppose we can only wish him the best of luck then. Speaking of Palace Master Xiao, I ran into him a short while ago," Luo Qinghai said with a smile.

"Now that you're here, why don't you take a look and see if you can break the restriction in this valley, Fellow Daoist Luo? You're a master of arrays, so I'm sure you'll have a way," Feng Tiandu proposed.

"I'll spare myself the trouble. There's no way that the restriction guarding the High Zenith Palace is something that I can break on my own. Instead, I'll be requiring everyone's help," Luo Qinghai said with a smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the golden cloud in the sky suddenly began to shrink, forming a giant vortex directly above the valley, and there were dull, rumbling thunderclaps ringing out within it.

Luo Qinghai's smile instantly faded upon seeing this, and a serious look appeared on his face as he said, "The pill tribulation is about to descend, so the pills must be about to take shape. We can't waste any more time here."

Feng Tiandu also nodded in response with a serious expression.

Luo Qinghai turned to everyone else and declared, "Fellow daoists, all of your efforts will be required in order to break this restriction. Otherwise, none of us will be able to enter the High Zenith Palace, and this massive opportunity will go to waste."

"We're willing to help," Daoist Hu Yan answered.

The elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race said in an unhurried manner, "I also have no objections to joining forces, but there are only two of us and so many of you. Once we enter the palace, we'll most likely be struck down on the spot."

"We're all here to secure treasures and opportunities, and risk and reward inevitably come hand in hand. If you wish to reap benefits without taking any risks, then I suggest you stay at home and wait for treasures to fall into your lap!" Qi Tianxiao scoffed.

"I think her concerns are actually quite valid, Sect Master Qi. Your Dawn Fall Sect has the most people out of all of us, so how can we not be wary of you? If you want everyone to work together with you, then I'm afraid you might have to make some concessions," Luo Qinghai said with a smile.

Qi Tianxiao was just about to respond when Feng Tiandu raised a hand to stop him, then said, "That's fine. There are only two Southern Dawn beings present and also only two cultivators from your Vast Flow Palace, so how about we set a limit of two people per side to enter the High Zenith Palace?"

Chapter 488: Immortal Envoy

Everyone was rather surprised to hear this proposal from Feng Tiandu, and Luo Qinghai was no exception. Judging from his expression, it was clear that he wasn't expecting Feng Tiandu to be so cooperative.

"I understand what all of you are concerned about, but your concerns are completely unnecessary. Time is of the essence right now, so we must work together. Otherwise, I wouldn't mind engaging all of you in battle in this valley, then turn to breaking this restriction once that battle is decided," Feng Tiandu said with a faint smile.

"This is a very good proposal from Elder Feng. Our Vast Flow Palace has no objections," Luo Qinghai said with a nod.

"The Southern Dawn Race agrees to this proposal as well," the elderly woman said in an expressionless manner.

Ouyang Kuishan was silent for a moment, then declared, "Our Blaze Dragon Dao also has no objections."

With that, the only side that was yet to make a declaration was Daoist Hu Yan's trio.

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, and he could only heave an internal sigh. He also wanted to enter the High Zenith Palace, but he didn't want to force Daoist Hu Yan to choose him, so he was already beginning to ponder ways to sneak into the palace once everyone else had gone in.

However, to his surprise, Daoist Hu Yan suddenly declared to both him and Yun Ni through voice transmission, "I'll bring Fellow Daoist Li with me into the High Zenith Palace."

Yun Ni merely nodded silently in response to this decision, while Han Li turned to Daoist Hu Yan as he raised an eyebrow in befuddlement.

"I've never been able to get a good handle on you, but there's one thing that I'm confident of, and that's that you're definitely not a treacherous person, so I have no qualms about bringing you with me. Most importantly, I have faith in your powers," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"I think you're not mentioning something. The main reason you're taking me with you is because you don't want Fellow Daoist Yun Ni to have to face the perils of the High Zenith Palace, right?" Han Li jibed.

"You didn't have to expose me, Fellow Daoist Li!" Daoist Hu Yan chuckled as he discreetly handed Han Li something. "Once we're done here, I'll follow through on my promise and give you the final two levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture."

"You have my thanks," Han Li replied with a smile as he stowed the item away in a covert fashion.

Meanwhile, Yun Ni was watching Daoist Hu Yan with a faint smile on her face, but a hint of concern in her eyes.

Finally, Daoist Hu Yan turned to everyone else as he declared, "Our True Flame Sect has no objections, either."

"Alright, in that case, let's begin right away, shall we?" Luo Qinghai proposed.

Everyone immediately gathered around and began making their way toward the stone wall upon hearing this.

"It appears to me that the scenic artwork engraved onto this stone wall is very similar to that of the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting, but at the same time, it's not completely identical. There are 13 of us present, and if all of us use the Nine Palaces Array Shattering Formation while unleashing the Nine True Spirits Technique at once, then we should be able to break this restriction," Luo Qinghai declared.

Everyone present fell into a contemplative silence upon hearing this, while Han Li turned to Daoist Hu Yan as he raised an eyebrow.

The Nine Palaces Array Shattering Formation was quite a prevalently used formation in the Immortal Realm, and as the name suggested, its purpose was to break restrictions.

As for the Nine True Spirits Technique, this was a technique that was slightly inferior to the Great Five-elemental True Light, but perhaps it could be more potent than the Great Five-elemental True Light when used in conjunction with the Nine Palaces Array Shattering Formation.

"In that case, please oversee the proceedings, and we'll begin right away," Feng Tiandu said.

Luo Qinghai nodded in response, then began instructing all of the Golden Immortals present to get into the correct formation, following which he gave everyone a detailed explanation of how to use the Nine True Spirits Technique.

After that, he declared, "Let's begin."

In total, there were 13 Golden Immortals present, one from the Vast Flow Palace, two from the Southern Dawn Race, three from the Blaze Dragon Dao, and three in Han Li's camp, and all of them began unleashing the Nine True Spirits Technique at once.

As everyone began to chant a collective incantation, their robes began to billow and sway as gusts of wind swept through the area, and the immortal spiritual power fluctuations emanating from their bodies were becoming more and more pronounced.

Han Li was standing on a point in the formation, and a peculiar feeling welled up in his heart.

This was an array of individuals using the Nine True Spirits Technique at the same time, yet due to the fact that they were arranged in the Nine Palaces Array Shattering Formation, some type of strange connection had formed between all of them. Their immortal spiritual power was like 13 streams that were drawn in by some type of force to converge into a single lake.

Luo Qinghai was situated at the forefront of the formation, and he was the only outlet for this lake.

Bright blue light was rippling around him as he made a peculiar hand seal before thrusting it forward, and all of the people in the formation instantly began to glow radiantly, while the immortal spiritual power in their bodies surged toward Luo Qinghai.

A vast volume of immortal spiritual power converged to form a lotus flower projection beneath Luo Qinghai, and it rose up like a lotus flower platform to elevate him in the sky. Blue light emerged within his eyes as well, and strands of azure light also appeared over his robes, roaming around as if they were living creatures.

He joined his palms together before pointing a finger at the white stone wall, and a pillar of blue light instantly shot out of his fingertip to strike the stone wall.

The white light barrier on the surface of the stone wall immediately began to churn like boiling water, and a series of transparent ripples surged over its surface in all directions.

......

Meanwhile, in the sky above a misty green lake.

A loud commotion was ringing out, and massive waves that were in excess of 1,000 feet tall were constantly erupting out of the lake, while streaks of light of all types of different colors were flashing through the air.

There were a series of strange vortexes on the surface of the lake that stretched all the way down to the lakebed, and several figures were traversing over the water above the vortexes with great difficulty, clashing against the blue figures that were constantly springing out of the vortexes.

It was unclear what these blue figures were. They appeared to be puppets, but their bodies were formed by water, and would be scattered upon being struck by powerful attacks, only to quickly reform to enter the battle once more.

The ones that these blue figures were attacking were none other than Xue Ying and the other Northern Glacial Immortal Palace cultivators, who had been recruited by Luo Qinghai to "assist" him.

Back when the Vast Flow Palace cultivators first arrived here, this place had still been a vast yellow desert.

They had already set up the array that was required to shatter the ovular yellow light barrier here, and all they were missing was the power of an additional Golden Immortal.

As the deputy palace master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, Xue Ying was certainly no slouch, and she had made sure to examine the array carefully. On top of that, she had also questioned Luo Qinghai extensively about the array and the surrounding environment, and only after she was absolutely certain that nothing was amiss did she agree to lend him her assistance.

However, right as the restriction guarding the ancient tomb was about to be broken, all of the sand in the vast desert suddenly began to churn violently.

Undulating ripples surged through the desert like waves in the sea, and the giant ancient tomb suddenly sank down into the ground, while the entire surrounding area in a radius of several kilometers instantly transformed into a blue lake.

At the same time, a vast golden array suddenly lit up from the ancient tomb that had sunk into the lake, creating all of these vortexes which had released immense suction force to trap her and prevent her from getting away.

After that came these strange blue figures, of which there seemed to be no end.

By the time she finally managed to regain her bearings, she discovered that all of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators had already slipped away amid the chaos, while all of the Immortal Palace True Immortals that she had brought with her were also trapped above the lake in their attempt to save her.

Xue Ying knew that she had fallen into a trap set by the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, and she was furious, but she was unable to free herself.

Right at this moment, a green jade flying carriage suddenly appeared from afar, then drew to a halt above the lake.

A graceful middle-aged man was standing at the front of the flying carriage, and he looked down at the lake with slightly furrowed brows before making a casual tossing motion.

The white jade Pixiu in his hand flew through the air in an arc, then fell into the lake with a small splash.

Moments later, a series of enormous waves suddenly swept over the surface of the lake, and a pillar of dazzling white light erupted out of the lakebed to destroy all of the vortexes in the water.

A puppet in the form of a giant white Pixiu that was thousands of feet in size then emerged from the water with a black millstone clasped in its mouth, and it sprang up into the sky, then crunched down onto the black millstone with its teeth until it was broken into pieces.

At the same time, the surface of the lake gradually began to return to its former peaceful state, and only then were Xue Ying and the others freed.

After taking a moment to compose herself, Xue Ying cast her gaze toward the flying carriage, then began to approach it before stopping around 10 feet away, where she extended a respectful curtsey toward the middle-aged man on the flying carriage.

"Junior Xue Ying pays her respects to Immortal Envoy Gongshu."

The middle-aged was none other than Gongshu Jiu, the immortal envoy sent by the Heavenly Court.

"Why are you being so formal and distant? Our clans are on very good terms with one another, and I'm also close friends with your father, so there's no need for you to be so uptight around me, Gongshu Jiu said with a warm smile.

"My apologies, Uncle Gongshu," Xue Ying replied as a smile appeared on her face.

"I received your message telling me to pay the Northern Glacial Immortal Region a visit quite some time ago, but I was busy with some other matters, so I wasn't able to get here earlier. I didn't think that things would already be this chaotic," Gongshu Jiu sighed.

"Palace Master Xiao..."

Xue Ying was just about to say something, but she suddenly stopped, then took a glance at the other Immortal Palace cultivators nearby.

"Go ahead, they won't be able to hear you," Gongshu Jiu said with a smile as he casually swept a sleeve through the air.

Chapter 489: The World Beyond the Gate

Xue Ying's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and she could sense that an invisible light barrier had appeared around herself and Gongshu Jiu.

"Over these past years, Palace Master Xiao's cultivation base has progressed quite significantly, and he was determined to unite the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region. For this purpose, he's been making many moves, and as a result, the entire immortal region has been stirred up into a state of unrest.

“After what happened to Baili Yan, it appeared on the surface that the Dawn Fall Sect and the Vast Flow Palace became much more subdued, but the reality is that they were merely accumulating power.

“If Palace Master Xiao continues down this reckless path, I fear that an all-out war will eventually be triggered in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so I had no choice but to supersede his authority and contact you directly," Xue Ying explained with a solemn expression.

"You did the right thing. The Heavenly Court has already noticed the unrest that's brewing in this immortal region. The Reincarnation Palace has become more and more active of late, so this isn't the only immortal region that could be under threat. I was late to get here precisely because I was taking care of some matters in another immortal region, and I came here directly after learning about the emergence of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor," Gongshu Jiu said.

"It's very fortunate that you just so happened to be passing through, Uncle Gongshu. Otherwise, I'm embarrassed to admit that I don't know how I would've gotten out of that trap," Xue Ying said as she cupped her fist in a grateful salute.

"This is a very intricate and powerful array that can only be broken by entering the water and destroying the mechanisms inside. The longer you're trapped in the array, the more firmly entrenched in it you'll become, so even if you possessed late-Golden Immortal Stage powers, it would've been very difficult for you to save yourself," Gongshu Jiu said with a smile.

"We all fell for Luo Qinghai's trap," Xue Ying sighed as a hint of dejection flashed through her eyes.

"Where is Xiao Jinhan right now?" Gongshu Jiu suddenly asked.

"I parted ways with him right before coming here. I'll take you to him right away," Xue Ying hurriedly replied.

"Let's go," Gongshu Jiu replied with a nod, then swept a sleeve through the air.

At this point, the giant white Pixiu had already devoured the black millstone, and it suddenly shrank back down into that jade trinket from before, then flew back into Gongshu Jiu's grasp.

The only thing that was different about it was that a small black spot had appeared within its belly.

After that, Gongshu Jiu and the Immortal Palace cultivators flew away into the distance.

......

Unbeknownst to them, there was a black stone passageway that led downward under the ancient tomb at the bottom of the lake, and the walls of the passageway were riddled with irregularly-shaped luminescent white rocks as a light source.

At this moment, there was a figure slowly making their way deeper into the passageway.

Basking in the glow of the luminescent rocks, her skin was as fair as snow, and it was none other than Lu Yuqing.

At this moment, her eyes were as bright as stars, but she was trudging along in a completely expressionless manner.

......

Inside the valley.

All of the mountains and rivers engraved onto the white stone wall were radiating dazzling golden light, and a series of golden runes were flying out of them before surging into the white light barrier.

With the injection of these golden runes, the white light barrier was significantly stabilized, and it had also taken on an extremely viscous quality.

Luo Qinghai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he switched to a different hand seal as he let loose a low roar.

The lotus platform projection beneath him immediately began to glow brightly while taking on a more substantial form, and at the same time, the sound of a light breeze rang out around the platform as a blue vortex emerged, releasing tremendous suction force.

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this, and he could feel his own immortal spiritual power surging rapidly into the vortex like floodwaters through a broken dam.

He took a quick glance at everyone else in the array to find that all of them also wore peculiar expressions, indicating that a large amount of their immortal spiritual power had just been taken as well.

"Don't be alarmed, fellow daoists. This restriction is even more formidable than I anticipated, so I'll need all of you to lend me more of your power," Luo Qinghai reassured.

"There's no need to explain anything to us, Fellow Daoist Luo. If you're trying to chip away at our immortal spiritual power, then this is far too crude a method, and I'm sure you wouldn't stoop to something like this," Feng Tiandu said.

"I'm glad I have your trust, Fellow Daoist Feng," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

As he was speaking, the lotus platform beneath him had already taken on a completely substantial form, and it looked as if it had been carved out of a piece of blue crystal.

All of a sudden, Luo Qinghai let loose a thunderous roar, and the lotus platform, which had harnessed a vast amount of immortal spiritual power from everyone, shot forth through the air.

Immediately thereafter, all of its petals drifted down from above, spiraling through the air as they passed through the golden light barrier to land upon the white stone wall.

Bursts of blue light appeared over the stone wall on the spots where the petals had descended, and a series of lotus flowers instantly bloomed to cover the entire stone wall.

Han Li was amazed to see this, but also a little apprehensive.

It had become apparent that Luo Qinghai had only asked them to adopt the Nine Palaces Array Shattering Formation and use the Nine True Spirits Technique so that he could draw upon their immortal spiritual power, while what he was actually using to break this restriction was the blue lotus flower.

Before he had a chance to think about anything, Luo Qinghai thrust both palms forward in a slow and casual motion, looking as if he were pushing open the door of his own home.

As he thrust his palms forward, then parted them down the sides, the golden light barrier over the white stone wall instantly shattered, and a golden line also appeared directly down the center of the stone wall before parting like doors.

The stone wall slowly opened inward without making a sound, and everyone in the valley was also completely silent as they stared at the radiant white light beyond the stone wall with tense and nervous expressions.

After the stone wall completely parted, all everyone could see was a vast expanse of blinding white light. No objects flew out from within, nor were there any formidable energy fluctuations.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a regenerative pill, which he promptly devoured, and he was also holding a pair of Immortal Origin Stones to replenish his immortal spiritual power reserves. At the same time, he peered into the white light with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

However, even with his spirit eye ability activated, all he could see was still just a vast expanse of white light, and his spiritual sense wasn't able to enter the white light at all.

"The restriction has already been opened. Please abide by our agreement and only send in two people per side. Otherwise, I'll be forced to close the restriction again, and only the heavens know what'll happen after that," Luo Qinghai said in a warm but implacable voice.

Feng Tiandu turned to Qi Tianxiao with a nod upon hearing this, and the two of them flew into the white light before vanishing on the spot, while all of the other Dawn Fall Sect cultivators remained outside.

Immediately thereafter, the two Southern Dawn Race cultivators flew into the white light, and Daoist Hu Yan spoke briefly to Yun Ni through voice transmission before also entering the white light with Han Li.

In the instant that he flew into the white light, Han Li felt a burst of sharp pain in his eyes, and he reflexively closed them.

In the next instant, as he reopened his eyes, he discovered that he was already situated in another strange world.

The entire surrounding area was filled with white mist that wasn't very dense, and he was able to discern between mist and space in the nearby vicinity, but the two had completely fused into one further away.

After conducting a brief inspection, Han Li discovered that not only was his visibility obstructed here, he wasn't able to release his spiritual sense very far, either.

The other people who had entered this space ahead of him were also hovering within the white mist, and they had all distanced themselves from one another as they inspected their surroundings with cautious expressions.

Having just entered this place, everyone was feeling quite tense, and no one dared to charge recklessly into the mist.

Shortly thereafter, Ouyang Kuishan and another Golden Immortal from the Blaze Dragon Dao appeared in the mist, and they took a glance at Daoist Hu Yan, but only drew a little closer instead of flying directly to Daoist Hu Yan's side.

Before long, Luo Qinghai and his disciple, Nan Kemeng, had also entered this place.

"Why are you all still here, fellow daoists? Could it be that you were all waiting for me? I am truly honored," he said with a warm smile as he also began inspecting his surroundings.

No one offered a response, and everyone was still trying to find the best way forward.

Looking at the surrounding mist, a hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face. His Brightsight Spirit Eyes were completely useless here, but perhaps he would be able to see something with his Eye of Truth.

However, this was still far too early to be exposing the fact that he was using a time-attribute cultivation art, and showing his hand too early was definitely not a good idea.

Right as he was hesitating about how to proceed, he suddenly noticed out of the corner of his eye that a cloud of white mist seemed to have risen up in the eyes of Nan Kemeng, and he was staring into the distance in a certain direction with a dazed look on his face.

Meanwhile, Luo Qinghai was pretending to search the place in an aimless fashion, but in reality, his attention had been focused on this disciple of his the entire time.

Han Li also cast his gaze in that direction in a subtle fashion, but he wasn't able to see anything there aside from white mist, and he couldn't help but wonder if Nan Kemeng possessed some type of special spirit eye ability.

With that in mind, Han Li decided to keep some tabs on him.

Moments later, Luo Qinghai suddenly said, "We can't just stand around here forever. How about we each choose a direction and do some exploring?"

"This white mist is able to keep out spiritual sense, who knows what could be lurking inside? What if we fly in straight to our deaths?" the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race harrumphed coldly.

"If none of you are willing to take a risk, then I'll be going on ahead," Luo Qinghai said with a smile, then latched onto the arm of his disciple before flying away.

Chapter 490: I Believe You

"Let's follow them, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan," Han Li immediately said to Daoist Hu Yan through voice transmission.

"Have you noticed something?" Daoist Hu Yan asked in a hesitant voice.

Under these circumstances, actively following someone could easily be seen as a gesture of provocation, and he didn't want to oppose Luo Qinghai for now.

Many years ago, Baili Yan had told him that on the surface, Luo Qinghai appeared to be a very kind and easygoing person, but in reality, he was most prone to holding grudges, and making an enemy out of even someone like Qi Tianxiao was a better alternative to getting on Luo Qinghai's bad side.

"I suspect that Luo Qinghai's disciple has some type of special ocular ability that can allow him to ascertain the location of the High Zenith Palace, but I can't be sure. However, what I can say for sure is that there's definitely something strange about them," Han Li explained.

"Given Luo Qinghai's personality, it would be much more characteristic of him to let others venture into the mist first, so it's indeed rather suspicious that he's going in first himself... Alright, let's do as you say then," Daoist Hu Yan decided after some contemplation.

With that, the two of them immediately flew into the mist, following Luo Qinghai's duo from afar.

Ouyang Kuishan took a glance at the other dao lord, and the two of them set off in another direction slightly to the left of where Daoist Hu Yan and Han Li had gone.

The pair of Southern Dawn beings also flew away in another direction, and thus, Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao were the only ones left.

Moments later, Feng Tiandu suddenly said, "They should be sufficiently far away by now. Let's go after them."

After that, he swept a hand through the air to conjure up a black light barrier that encompassed both himself and Qi Tianxiao, then set off in the same direction as Han Li.

Deep within the mist, Luo Qinghai and Nan Kemeng were flying onward at an even pace.

All of a sudden, Nan Kemeng stopped in his tracks, then took a glance at the mist behind him as he said, "Palace Master, there are people following us."

"That's only to be expected. Who are the ones following us?" Luo Qinghai asked with a smile.

"Everyone," Nan Kemeng replied with slightly furrowed brows.

Luo Qinghai was rather taken aback by this answer, and a mocking sneer appeared on his face.

"The ones closest to us are the two cultivators from the True Flame Sect. The Blaze Dragon Dao and the Southern Dawn Race have both chosen more roundabout routes, but they're all following us as well. As for the Dawn Fall Sect cultivators, they're a bit further away, but it seems like they're following the True Flame Sect cultivators," Nan Kemeng elaborated.

"True Flame Sect my arse! One of them is none other than Daoist Hu Yan of the Blaze Dragon Dao. As for that so-called nephew of his, I have no idea who that is. There's no one that fits his description in our Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and it's like he popped up out of nowhere," Luo Qinghai mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"What should we do then?" Nan Kemeng asked.

"The High Zenith Pills are about to be ready, so we have no time to waste here. Let's go," Luo Qinghai replied.

He then made a hand seal to conjure up a blue light barrier, which encompassed both himself and Nan Kemeng.

Immediately thereafter, the two of them vanished into thin air amid a flurry of rainbow bubbles.

A short while later, Han Li and Daoist Hu Yan sped onto the scene, and the latter asked, "What happened?"

"No wonder they weren't worried about us following them, they've already prepared measures to shake us off their trail," Han Li said.

"I should've known," Daoist Hu Yan sighed. "What do we do now?"

"There's something I can try, but I need you to release your spirit domain to conceal me for a short while," Han Li replied after a brief hesitation.

"Alright, go ahead," Daoist Hu Yan hurriedly said, then immediately released his fiery spirit domain to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

"I can't expand the spirit domain any more beyond this point. Otherwise, I can't guarantee that I'll be able to conceal your energy fluctuations," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"This is fine. If you make it any bigger, it'll attract attention from the others," Han Li replied with a nod, then summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of golden light.

The radiant golden axis was riddled with Time Dao Runes, and despite Daoist Hu Yan's vast wealth of experience, even he couldn't help but be astonished by the formidable time law power fluctuations emanating from the axis.

His mouth sprang open in shock, and he was completely rooted to the spot.

Han Li paid no heed to Daoist Hu Yan's reaction as he focused on scouring the surrounding area with his Eye of Truth, and it didn't take long before he spotted a burst of lingering spatial fluctuations to his right.

"I've found them!" Han Li declared as he withdrew his hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly vanished back into his body.

Daoist Hu Yan was still reeling a little as he praised, "I knew you were cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture, but I didn't think you had already reached such an extraordinary level of mastery over the laws of time."

"I encountered some strokes of fortune in the past that accelerated my mastery over this cultivation art," Han Li explained in an ambiguous manner.

"Be honest with me. Have you been concealing your true cultivation base this entire time, or have you also been cultivating the laws of reincarnation in secret? Otherwise, I can't think of any other way that you could've reached the middle-Golden Immortal Stage in such a short time," Daoist Hu Yan said with tightly furrowed brows.

Han Li heaved a resigned sigh upon hearing this.

"I was telling you the truth earlier. Not long ago, I stumbled into a strange secret area and cultivated for tens of thousands of years in there to reach the mid-Golden Immortal Stage. However, when I came out, I discovered that the flow of time in there was completely different from that of the outside world, and not even a moment had passed by outside the secret area."

Daoist Hu Yan was stunned into silence upon hearing this, then forced a smile onto his own face as he sighed, "Just how lucky of a little rascal are you?"

Han Li rolled his eyes in response, and he didn't bother to explain anything.

In his own eyes, he was far from fortunate. Whenever he encountered a stroke of fortune, it would always be preceded by extremely perilous situations that could've easily had him killed.

All of a sudden, Daoist Hu Yan reached out toward Han Li, then spread his hand open to reveal a pair of white jade slips with golden patterns etched upon them.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he asked, "What's this, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan?"

"These are the fifth and sixth levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture, and I'm giving them to you now because I have something to ask of you," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a solemn expression.

"Tell me what you want me to do first," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Once we enter the High Zenith Palace, I want you to help me secure a High Zenith Pill. Just one will do," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

"I will do my best to assist you as long as it doesn't place me in any excessive danger," Han Li replied.

"I knew you would say that," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled. "Fine, you can have these jade slips."

Han Li accepted the pair of jade slips from Daoist Hu Yan, then briefly examined them before stowing them away into his storage bracelet.

"Why didn't you wait until we left the immortal manor before you gave these to me? I would've still agreed to help you nonetheless," Han Li asked.

"Would you believe me if I told you that I want to suck up to you because you're the most prodigious cultivator I've ever seen?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

"I believe you," Han Li replied with a serious expression.

"Well, you're certainly not shy," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled with an amused expression.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as well as he flew away toward the right, followed closely by Daoist Hu Yan.

All of a sudden, Han Li vanished into thin air, much to Daoist Hu Yan's alarm, and he hurriedly accelerated forward, upon which he also vanished into the white mist in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, he and Han Li appeared in another independent space one after the other.

Hovering in mid-air several thousand feet below the two of them was a small landmass that was several hundred kilometers in size, and it was riddled with all types of intricate pavilions and buildings, as well as lush greenery.

Several rivers were flowing through the area like a series of jade belts, and they spilled down over the edge of the landmass to form numerous waterfalls that were exceptionally beautiful to behold.

On a spacious plot of land on the edge of the landmass was a lush spirit beast pen that was split up into hundreds of small areas, and there were hundreds of species of different spirit beasts being kept inside.

Directly across from the spirit beast pen was a vast spirit medicine garden with all types of spirit medicines growing inside, and their medicinal auras were so potent that they were rising up into the sky like wisps of smoke.

Daoist Hu Yan pointed some tall fiery-red horses and green jade-like lions in the pen as he exclaimed, "Those are Blusher Horses and Azure Bamboo Lions! They went extinct in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region tens of thousands of years ago!"

"That spirit medicine garden must have many high-grade immortal plants that are hundreds of thousands of years old growing in there. Otherwise, there wouldn't be so much purple smoke rising up from it," Han Li also remarked.

There were also many black-robed servants littered throughout the spirit beast pen and the spirit medicine garden.

Some of them were working in the fields while holding different types of tools, some were feeding the spirit beasts, some were watering the garden, some were grooming the beasts, and some were picking plants, fruits, and leaves from the garden.

All of them had their own duties, and they were carrying out those duties in an orderly fashion.

In between those two areas was a white stone mountain path that also had some black-robed servants on it, and they were responsible for carrying the spirit beast materials and spirit medicinal ingredients gathered by the other servants to the top of the mountain.

Chapter 491: Secret Area

After some observation, Han Li raised an eyebrow as he remarked, "These servants all seem to be puppets."

"That's right, they are indeed all puppets," Daoist Hu Yan confirmed with a nod after some close scrutiny.

As the two of them were speaking, golden light began to converge up above, and a dense golden cloud emerged. The pill tribulation that had already appeared quite some time ago in the outside world had only just begun to make an appearance in this secret area.

Han Li tracked down the exact central point of the golden cloud, then cast his gaze downward to find that there was a resplendent golden palace with a round dome perched atop the tallest point on the mountain summit.

There were two figures on the plaza outside the golden palace, and bright blue light was radiating from their bodies as they cast strings of incantation seals at the gates of the palace.

"Looks like Luo Qinghai is already working on breaking the restriction. We should go as well," Han Li said.

"Fine by me," Daoist Hu Yan replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a patch of space over 1,000 feet away began to warp slightly, following which Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao appeared.

Feng Tiandu took a quick glance at Han Li, then immediately turned his attention to the golden palace in the distance as he flew directly toward the plaza with Qi Tianxiao by his side.

"How did they find this place? Could it be that someone among them also possesses Void Spirit Eyes?" Luo Qinghai mused with a perplexed expression at the sight of the approaching Feng Tiandu and Qi Tianxiao.

"What do we do, Palace Master? The restriction is about to be broken soon," Nan Kemeng asked.

"So be it, let's focus on getting into the palace first," Luo Qinghai replied as he thrust his palms forcefully against the palace gates.

A blue leaf that was riddled with silver patterns shot out of the palm of his leading hand before pressing itself against the palace gates.

The palace gates instantly began to glow with radiant blue light, and the leaf melted away before vanishing into the gates, leaving only the silver patterns intertwining with one another to form a series of complex runes that spread over the gates.

All of the silver runes quickly turned into cracks, and before long, the golden gates were shattered amid a crisp crack.

Right as Luo Qinghai and Nan Kemeng were about to rush into the palace, Feng Tiandu's voice rang out from behind them.

"All of us worked together to break the restriction and get to this point, surely you don't intend to reap all the benefits for yourself and leave nothing for everyone else."

"Of course not, Fellow Daoist Feng. I just so happened to get here first, and time is of the essence, so I thought I'd open the palace gates to make things more convenient for everyone," Luo Qinghai replied with a smile.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Daoist Hu Yan also descended in front of the golden palace.

Luo Qinghai and Feng Tiandu both took a glance at Han Li's duo in unison, and a smile appeared on the former's face, while the latter remained completely expressionless.

Before anyone had a chance to say anything, four more streaks of light flashed into the secret area one after another, and the two Southern Dawn Race Golden Immortals and Ouyang Kuishan's duo also arrived before descending in front of the golden palace as well.

Upon landing on the ground, the elderly woman of the Southern Dawn Race immediately gate a cold harrumph to express her displeasure, while Ouyang Kuishan gave Daoist Hu Yan and subtle nod.

They had only been able to enter this place as Daoist Hu Yan had informed them of the location of the entrance through a secret technique.

With that, everyone was once again reunited.

Right at this moment, the golden cloud in the sky above began to churn violently, and in the span of just a few seconds, it encompassed the entire heavens, basking everyone in dazzling golden radiance.

Tremendous energy fluctuations were surging out of the golden cloud, striking even all of the Golden Immortals present with a sense of foreboding.

It was as if the golden cloud had already completely fused as one with the sky, and there was an extremely heavy atmosphere hanging in the air, as if the entire sky were about to come crashing down.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of rumbling began to ring out incessantly from within the cloud, and an enormous golden vortex emerged, revolving rapidly on the spot.

A burst of dazzling silver light began to slowly take shape at the center of the vortex, and it resembled a giant silver water droplet with arcs of lightning constantly flashing over its surface.

With the formation of this silver water droplet, a burst of terrifying spiritual power fluctuations descended from above, encompassing the entirety of the golden palace.

Han Li swept his gaze over the golden palace to find that countless runes had been engraved onto its pillars, doors, and window frames, and at this moment, all of these runes were glowing as radiantly as stars in the night sky.

The ground inside the palace was also etched with rings of circular patterns that resembled circles of guards defending the giant jade-like pill cauldron at the center of the palace.

The cauldron stood at over seven feet tall, and it had three feet and a pair of handles, as was the case with most standard pill refinement cauldrons.

It looked as if the cauldron were forged from jade, but that wasn't actually the case. There were scorching flames surging within the cauldron, but no heat could be felt outside of it, and that was a clear testament to its insulative properties.

On top of that, there were nine coiled dragons engraved around the cauldron amid the masses of spirit patterns, and these dragons were extremely life-like. All of them had their mouths opened upward, aimed at a statue of a three-legged golden crow on top of the cauldron's lid.

Han Li focused his gaze on the golden crow statue with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he noticed that there were wisps of white light flowing the cauldron from its three legs, which were connected to the cauldron's lid.

All of a sudden, the golden vortex up above brightened significantly, and the massive silver water droplet fell out of the sky before crashing into the top of the golden palace's roof.

A vast expanse of blinding silver light instantly erupted forth, and arcs of silver lightning exploded in all directions, inundating the entire golden palace amid a deafening boom.

Everyone's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this as they darted back in retreat, while the golden palace abruptly sank downward, as if a mountain had crashed down onto it, crushing it into the ground.

However, immediately thereafter, all of the runes on the surface of the entire palace lit up, and a vast wave of golden light swept forth to intertwine with the vast expanse of silver lightning up above.

The entire golden palace resembled a radiant golden sun, and at the same time, golden light spread from the center of its roof along its rafters to alleviate the tremendous force that was crashing down upon it.

Even so, a pillar of silver light was still able to pierce straight through the center of the roof to strike the pill refinement cauldron, and a dull thump rang out as all of the runes engraved onto the ground inside the palace lit up in rapid succession.

Immediately thereafter, layers of golden light barriers rose up from the ground, collecting the wisps of golden light and funneling them into the pill cauldron.

Radiant golden light emerged within the eyes of the nine dragons engraved onto the cauldron, while pillars of white light shot out of their mouths, converging from all directions to clash against the pillar of silver light.

Meanwhile, Han Li was observing all of this from outside the palace with an awestruck expression.

It was extremely impressive that the Infernal Frost Immortal Lord had managed to construct this High Zenith Palace and have the entire thing run by puppets. Not only were these puppets capable of collecting ingredients on their own, they were even able to refine what was clearly a dao pill!

What was most incredible of all was that this golden palace was capable of opposing pill tribulations, and that was unfathomable to Han Li. Could it be that the old daoist priest really was an unmatched genius, as he proclaimed?

Upon emerging from that secret area, Han Li had completely sealed the soul fragment that belonged to the self-proclaimed Infernal Frost Immortal Lord into the soul nurturing burner so that it was completely cut off from the outside world. Right now, he was contemplating undoing the restriction so that he could communicate with the soul fragment.

All of a sudden, Daoist Hu Yan's voice rang out to snap him out of his train of thought. "The pill tribulation is about to come to an end! Prepare yourself!"

Sure enough, the silver lightning that was raging over the ceiling of the palace had gradually begun to subside, and faint plumes of smoke were rising up from the golden palace, while a scorched scent was wafting through the air.

However, the entire palace was glowing even more radiantly than prior to the pill tribulation.

"Let's go!" someone called out, and everyone immediately flew into the palace at once.

At this point, the pillar of silver light inside the palace had already faded, but the golden light barriers were still standing, protecting the pill cauldron from all directions.

Han Li swept his gaze across the interior of the palace to find that there was a series of gray stone statues situated on either of the palace, and all of them were wielding different weapons. They were standing completely still on the spot, but there were spiritual power fluctuations emanating from their bodies, and they were clearly all puppets.

Behind the pill cauldron was a platform that was raised about three feet above the ground, upon which was a large golden chair with dragons and phoenixes engraved upon it, giving it a very grandiose appearance.

Seated atop the chair was a middle-aged man wearing a dark green daoist robe.

His hands were resting on the armrests of the chair, and his eyes were closed. He had one leg crossed over the other while leaning against the back of the chair, giving him a rather lackadaisical appearance that was somewhat of a mismatch with his handsome appearance.

Everyone was greatly startled to see this, and they immediately prepared for battle, only to discover a moment that the middle-aged man seemed to be nothing more than a corpse that was completely devoid of vitality.

However, that wasn't entirely accurate as his chest was rising and falling slightly in a rhythmic fashion as if he were breathing, and it was as if he was a living corpse.

Right at this moment, a small five-colored cloud rose up from the top of the cauldron, and out of the dragons engraved onto the cauldron, the one that was facing the palace gates suddenly flashed momentarily with silver light, following which a longan-sized silver pill flew out of its mouth.

With the emergence of the pill, an incredibly potent medicinal fragrance instantly permeated throughout the entire palace.

Everyone immediately turned their attention to the pill with fervent looks in their eyes.

"Hold on a second, everyone! Those golden rings form a protective array for the cauldron, and if we charge in recklessly, the entire cauldron of pills could be destroyed!" Luo Qinghai yelled.

"The pill has already taken shape, who cares if the cauldron is destroyed?" the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race retorted as she prepared to step forward, but a blue light barrier abruptly rose up from the ground to block her path.

"Is it finally time to fight? I've been raring to go this entire time!" the elderly man chuckled.

Han Li and Daoist Hu Yan exchanged a glance, and they immediately channeled their immortal spiritual power as well.

All of a sudden, a very tense atmosphere had descended upon the palace.

Chapter 492: High Zenith Palace

"Let's remain calm and civilized, everyone. I'm not intervening because I want to stop all of you from fighting over the pill, I simply don't want to see the other eight High Zenith Pills destroyed just for this single one," Luo Qinghai hurriedly explained.

"Oh? Are you saying that there are as many as nine High Zenith Pills in that cauldron?" Feng Tiandu asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right. If I'm not mistaken, this pill refinement cauldron should be the Nine Jewel-bearing Dragons Cauldron, an incredible cauldron that always produced nine pills per batch, one out of each dragon's mouth. However, the pills won't emerge all at once, so we should wait until all nine are ready," Luo Qinghai explained.

"Now that you mention it, I also recall hearing about this cauldron. It's said that countless years ago, an almighty figure once gathered many precious natural treasures of the True Immortal Realm, as well as the souls of true spirits to refine a pill cauldron of incredible power, and it contains some type of law power that allow pill refinement ingredients to combine with one another in a more harmonious fashion. I certainly wasn't expecting to see it here," the elderly woman mused.

Everyone's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, but a hint of greed had surfaced in their eyes as they turned their attention to the pill cauldron.

"That brings up another problem then. There are 10 of us here right now, yet only nine High Zenith Pills, so how are we going to split them?" Feng Tiandu mused with a contemplative expression.

As soon as this point was raised, everyone immediately tensed up once again.

"That's not a problem. I already said that I've only entered the Infernal Frost Immortal Palace on this occasion to broaden my disciples' horizons, and that objective has already been achieved. In light of that, our Vast Flow Palace will only claim one pill, so that evens things out perfectly." Luo Qinghai said with a smile.

Everyone was very surprised and befuddled to hear this.

Right at this moment, the golden light barriers around the pill cauldron suddenly faded, and a golden humanoid puppet suddenly stepped around from behind the pill cauldron, then reached out to grab the silver pill that had flown out of the dragon's mouth before turning back around and making its way the large golden chair.

Everyone was rather perplexed to see this, but they still followed the golden puppet nonetheless.

Right at this moment, a vast cloud of black mist suddenly emerged, then swept over everyone in a wave.

It was as if everyone had suddenly been sucked into an extremely viscous swamp, and not only was their mobility significantly hampered, even their immortal spiritual power circulation had been slowed down significantly.

The same applied to Han Li, but the time law powers in his body weren't affected at all.

Bright azure light emerged over his body as he channeled his time law powers to force out the surrounding black mist, and as he turned to look behind himself, he discovered that the source of the viscous black mist was none other than Feng Tiandu.

Plumes of black qi were surging out of his body, forming a black spirit domain that had trapped everyone inside.

The black spirit domain was extremely dense, but it wasn't very large, only encompassing less than half of the palace so it didn't trigger the golden array around the pill cauldron.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this. During that battle between Feng Tiandu and Xiao Jinhan outside the High Zenith Palace, the spirit domain that he had unleashed had been nowhere near as formidable as this one, so it was clear that he had intentionally concealed his true power.

In a rare display of animosity, the amicable smile on Luo Qinghai's face faded as he yelled in a furious voice, "What is the meaning of this, Feng Tiandu? Do you intend to take all of the High Zenith Stage for yourself?"

Immediately thereafter, a vortex of radiant blue light emerged around him, and it revolved incessantly while expanding outward, forming a blue spirit domain in the blink of an eye.

Countless turbulent wave projections were churning throughout the entire spirit domain, and while it was inferior to Feng Tiandu's black spirit domain, the gap wasn't all that significant.

In the face of the crashing blue waves, the black spirit domain was scattered a little.

At the same time, Daoist Hu Yan and the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race also unleashed their fiery spirit domains, and the combined power of the three spirit domains was instantly able to ward off the majority of the black spirit domain's power.

As a result, the pressure on the other Golden Immortal Stages present was significantly alleviated, and they immediately summoned a series of immortal treasures to launch a barrage of attacks at Feng Tiandu.

Han Li also summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, and it swelled drastically in size before hurtling toward Feng Tiandu alongside all of the other immortal treasures.

Even though Han Li had refrained from unleashing the true power of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, it still wasn't inferior in the slightest compared with all of the other immortal treasures.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Tiandu's face as he swept a sleeve through the air, and 16 thick black chains shot out of his body.

All of the chains were riddled with countless tiny translucent runes of different shapes and forms, and they were giving off extremely formidable law power fluctuations.

Feng Tiandu had unleashed these chains in the past, but as was the case with his spirit domain, these chains were far more formidable than the ones that he had previously displayed.

The 16 chains glowed with dazzling black light as they swept through the surrounding area, and a string of resounding booms rang out as all of the oncoming immortal treasures were swatted away by the chains.

As soon as the 16 black chains appeared, the entire black spirit domain immediately began to ripple and flash erratically while rapidly becoming denser and and more formidable.

As a result, the three opposing spirit domains were quickly suppressed, and the restrictive power of the black spirit domain was significantly enhanced once again as it swept toward all of the surrounding Golden Immortals.

Everyone felt as if there were a giant mountain weighing down upon them, making it extremely difficult to move.

"Your spirit domain has also reached the Spiritform Stage!" Luo Qinghai exclaimed.

Immediately thereafter, bright blue light emerged over his body as he flew toward a certain direction, and everyone else also quickly dispersed in different directions upon seeing this.

Through that battle against Xiao Jinhan, they had all experienced just how formidable a Spiritform Stage spirit domain was, and to compound their woes even further, Feng Tiandu's spirit domain seemed to be far more formidable than Xiao Jinhan's.

The only silver lining was that Feng Tiandu had kept his spirit domain very small in order to avoid triggering the restrictions around the pill cauldron, so it wouldn't take long to fly out of the spirit domain.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then flew away into the distance with radiant golden light shining from his body.

At the same time, he was channeling his time law powers into his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the sword, lashing out at the black spirit domain up ahead.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong flew out of his body, then transformed into a millstone-sized golden beetle in the blink of an eye.

With a sweep of its two front legs, a flurry of streaks of translucent light were unleashed.

In the face of Han Li and Jin Tong's combined powers, a gash was torn into the black spirit domain up ahead, and the two of them immediately flew toward the opening.

"You're not getting away!" Feng Tiandu harrumphed coldly as he made a hand seal, and a pair of black chains appeared around his body amid a flash of black light.

These were none other than the two Origin Separation Law Chains that he had sealed away.

Han Li's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately attempted to take evasive measures, but it was already too late.

The pair of black chains shot forth like lightning, then wrapped themselves around him and Jin Tong, rendering both of them completely immobilized.

With the emergence of these two Origin Separation Law Chains, the entire spirit domain began to ripple once again while becoming even denser.

Right at this moment, all of the 16 black chains around Feng Tiandu shot forth in unison, then vanished into thin air in the blink of an eye.

In the next instant, numerous black chains emerged throughout the entire black domain, and they intertwined with one another to form a cage of chains in the blink of an eye, trapping everyone inside.

Each person had several chains wrapped around them, and they were like flies stuck on a cobweb.

Luo Qinghai had been tied up by black chains like everyone else, but he remained calm and collected as he said, "I didn't think that your spirit domain would've already reached the Spiritform Stage, but there's no way that you can maintain this spirit domain for long before you exhaust all of your law powers! Do not be intimidated, everyone!"

As he was speaking, bright blue light erupted from his entire body, and countless blue wave projections emerged within the blue light, clashing against the surrounding black light.

These Origin Separation Law Chains could seal their immortal spiritual power, but it was unable to completely seal their law powers.

All of the other Golden Immortals were also instilled with a sense of calmness upon hearing this, and they began to unleash their respective law powers to resist against the black chains, causing the cage of black chains to tremble and rattle incessantly.

As a result, Feng Tiandu's complexion paled slightly, but he then gave a cold harrumph before expelling an egg-sized ball of blood essence out of his mouth.

Immediately thereafter, several drops of blood essence flew into every single one of the black chains in the spirit domain at his behest.

Bursts of black light surged over the cage of black chains with this injection of blood essence, and it was gradually stabilized.

In the case of Xiao Jinhan, he had only been able to elevate his spirit domain to the Spiritform Stage using those five stone pillars.

Due to the fact that external assistance was at play, his spirit domain had been a little weaker than a normal Spiritform Stage spirit domain, but at the same time, it also made the spirit domain less taxing on him to maintain.

In contrast, Feng Tiandu was unleashing this Spiritform Stage spirit domain solely through his own power, and he was facing so many Golden Immortals at once, so this was extremely taxing on both his immortal spiritual power and his law powers.

"All of you are important figures in our Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and today, you'll get to bear witness to my ascension to the High Zenith Stage. For that, I will grant all of you a quick and painless death!" Feng Tiandu declared as he continued to maintain his spirit domain.

"In your dreams, Feng Tiandu! Even if I have to sacrifice the entirety of my cultivation base here, I won't let you have your way!" Luo Qinghai roared in a furious voice.

At the same time, he also expelled a mouthful of blood essence to bolster his spirit domain, expending a great deal of power in the process, and the black light on the surface of the cage of black chains began to flash erratically once again.

"Fellow daoists, the High Zenith Pills are right in front of us! Are we just going to watch as Feng Tiandu takes them all for himself? I, for one, certainly won't just stand by and let him do as he pleases! Our Southern Dawn Race will fight the Dawn Fall Sect to the death!" the elderly woman yelled.

Everyone else immediately sprang into action as well, redoubling efforts to free themselves from the black cage.

Chapter 493: Intercepting the Pills

"I'll trap them here while you go secure the High Zenith Pills," Feng Tiandu said to Qi Tianxiao, paying no heed to the other Golden Immortals.

"Senior Martial Brother, why don't we kill these people first, then take our time in securing the pills?" Qi Tianxiao suggested through voice transmission as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

"Let's secure one or two High Zenith Pills first. Even though these people have been trapped by me, it's definitely not going to be an easy task to kill all of them. We have to prioritize securing the pills first!" Feng Tiandu replied.

Qi Tianxiao nodded in response, then immediately shot forth toward the golden puppet.

At this point, the golden puppet was already quite far away, and it was no more than 10,000 feet away from the large golden chair on the raised platform.

Qi Tianxiao rose up from the ground, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of gray light, which contained a gray flying sword.

The flying sword began to glow with radiant gray light, then abruptly transformed into dozens of threads of gray light that shot forth toward the golden puppet in unison.

However, right at this moment, the golden patterns on the ground lit up, and a pillar of white flames erupted out of the ground, forming a wall of fire in front of the threads of gray light.

A burst of scorching heat erupted out of the wall of white flames, causing the nearby space to twist and warp.

As soon as the threads of gray light came into contact with the white wall of fire, they were instantly incinerated into nothingness.

Qi Tianxiao's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately stopped cold in his tracks.

Meanwhile, the golden puppet seemed to remain oblivious to everything that was happening as it continued to trudge toward the golden chair.

Qi Tianxiao turned his gaze to the middle-aged man seated on the golden chair, and a thought suddenly sprang into his mind.

Could it be that the puppet is going to offer the High Zenith Pill to that living corpse?

With that in mind, an urgent look immediately flashed through his eyes.

Who knew what was going to happen if the pill were given to that living corpse.

The corrosive laws that he had mastered were naturally somewhat suppressed by flames of this nature, but it seemed that he had no choice but to force his way through.

All the while, the golden puppet was drawing closer and closer to the golden chair.

400 feet...

350 feet...

300 feet...

Large beads of sweat began to appear on Qi Tianxiao's forehead, and his mind was racing. All of a sudden, he laid a hand onto his waist, and a white ring emerged in his grasp amid a flash of white light.

A pained look flashed through his eyes as he tossed the white ring through the air with one hand while quickly casting an incantation seal with the other.

The ring instantly began to radiate dazzling white light while rapidly expanding to several times its original size, and countless runes were surging out of it in a frenzy.

Light also began to converge at the center of the ring, instantly forming a white vortex with bursts of spatial power emanating from within.

......

Meanwhile, all of the cultivators outside the High Zenith Palace had already found places to sit.

The stone gate remained open, and the dazzling white light inside was unbearably bright.

Occasionally, one of the cultivators would take a glance at the white stone gate with a hint of greed in their eyes, but no one stepped out of line.

Not long after Han Li and the others entered through the stone gates, the rest of the Vast Flow Palace cultivators also arrived on the scene, led by the fair-skinned scholar.

After some discussion, everyone arrived at a temporary agreement, which was that if the cultivators of any side were to try and enter the High Zenith Palace, then they would immediately be attacked by everyone else.

Among all of the cultivators present, the Vast Flow Palace had the most formidable lineup, which included four Golden Immortals. Aside from them, there were also several True Immortals among their ranks.

Second came the Dawn Fall Sect, which had three Golden Immortals.

Aside from them, the only ones left were Yun Ni and another one of the Blaze Dragon Dao dao lords, and the two of them were standing together, forming a triangular formation with the Vast Flow Palace and Dawn Fall Sect's forces.

Right at this moment, two of the Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals exchanged a glance with one another, and one of them suddenly suggested, "Fellow daoists, I don't think the people inside are going to be coming out anytime soon, and sitting around like this is really unproductive. There may be other treasures to be found in this mountain range, so how about we leave some people behind while the rest of us go and do some exploring?"

Peculiar looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this.

They had been ordered to stand on guard duty here, and that was their top priority, so there was no way that they could go wandering off now.

"Not interested," the fair-skinned scholar of the Vast Flow Palace said. "If you want to go, then you can go by yourselves."

Yun Ni and the Blaze Dragon Dao Golden Immortal didn't say anything, but it was clear that they had no intention of leaving, either.

"Suit yourselves. In that case, we'll go on our own," the Golden Immortal of the Dawn Fall Sect said, then stood up with the other Golden Immortal, and both of them flew away into the distance, quickly vanishing out of sight.

Yun Ni's brows were slightly furrowed as she watched them depart.

Once the two of them had flown out of everyone else's spiritual sensory range, they immediately drew to a halt, then descended onto the ground in a secretive location.

There, one of the Golden Immortals flipped a hand over to produce a white ring, and the two of them cast a string of incantation seals into the ring, upon which it began to rapidly expand while giving off bursts of white light.

Before long, a white vortex had appeared within the ring as well, and the two of them immediately flew into the vortex.

After the two of them flew into the white ring, countless cracks instantly appeared over its surface, and it shattered before disintegrating into specks of white light.

......

Inside the High Zenith Palace, Qi Tianxiao was hovering in mid-air as he made a hand seal, and two streaks of light shot out of the white ring in front of him, then faded to reveal the pair of Golden Immortals from earlier.

The expressions of Han Li and the others instantly darkened slightly as they saw this from afar.

Following the arrival of the two Golden Immortals, countless cracks appeared over this white ring as well, and it was also shattered.

The two Golden Immortals were rather taken aback by the sight that they were greeted by, and they both cupped their fists in a salute as they greeted, "Greetings, Sect Master, Grand Elder."

"No need for formalities. I've teleported the two of you in here as I need you to unleash your Sun Moon Chaos Arts to help me break through this wall of fire," Qi Tianxiao said.

The two Golden Immortals knew that the situation was urgent, so they didn't ask any further questions, and they immediately split apart, then began to chant a collective incantation as black and white light emerged over their bodies.

Both the black and white lights were giving off bursts of law fluctuations, and Han Li was quite intrigued by this.

He could sense that these two bursts of law fluctuations were very special, and they were completely different from the five-elemental laws that he was familiar with.

The law power fluctuations emanating out of the white light were as radiant as the sun, while the black light's law fluctuations were dark and gloomy, but not cold or sinister in the slightest.

Could these be laws related to yin and yang? Han Li speculated.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong's voice suddenly rang out in his mind. "You're not actually trapped by these chains, are you, Uncle?"

He turned to discover that Jin Tong was still struggling with all its might, and golden light was flashing over its sharp claws as it hacked away viciously at the black chains.

However, these black chains were extraordinarily resilient, rendering its struggles completely futile, so it could only turn to Han Li with a helpless expression.

Han Li gave Jin Tong a subtle look, but offered no response outside of that.

Jin Tong was ecstatic to see this, and it immediately urged, "So you do have a way to break out of these chains! Hurry and free me so I can go kill that old zombie!"

"Be quiet! The situation is really unclear right now, so we have to wait," Han Li hurriedly said through voice transmission.

Even though his immortal spiritual power was restricted by this Origin Separation Law Chains, he was still able to use his time law powers, so it wasn't impossible for him to break free from these chains, but now wasn't the right time to do so.

As Han Li and Jin Tong were communicating with one another, the two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals let loose a collective low roar, and the black and white light around them immediately shot forth toward the wall of fire as two pillars of light, one black and one white.

The black and white pillars of light intertwined with one another before quickly fusing as one to form a black and white vortex.

As the two Golden Immortals continued to make a rapid string of hand seals, the two bursts of law powers also fused together.

The black and white vortex instantly swelled significantly in size, while the two bursts of law powers were also bolstered by about twofold in unison, and they struck the wall of fire with tremendous force.

This was the first time that Han Li had seen two completely different types of law powers that could enhance each other, and he was very intrigued.

At the same time, he was struck by a hint of enlightenment, as if he had just grasped a key point pertaining to the usage of law powers, but in this situation, he couldn't dwell on this train of thought for long, so he would just have to slowly explore it another time.

The black and white vortex was revolving rapidly, while the wall of fire churned violently, and bursts of scorching flames surged toward the black and white vortex as if they had a mine of their own, trying to incinerate the vortex. However, the vortex was only becoming brighter and brighter as it flew rapidly into the wall of fire.

A few seconds later, the black and white vortex was able to pierce straight through the wall of fire to open up a black and white passageway.

At this point, the golden puppet was already no more than 150 feet away from the raised platform.

Qi Tianxiao immediately shot through the black and white passageway as a streak of gray light, hurtling toward the golden puppet like lightning.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release the same gray jade scepter from before, and it swelled to the size of a house in the blink of an eye.

A vast expanse of dense gray mist was swirling around the scepter, and there were countless gray runes interspersed throughout the mist as the scepter came crashing down upon the golden puppet.

Meanwhile, the other two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals also flew through the black and white passageway before pouncing at the golden puppet.

At the same time, both of them opened their mouths to release two streaks of light, one white and one black, and they contained a pair of large triangular flags.

One flag was a pristine white color with a blazing sun embroidered onto its center, and it was giving off blinding white light, while the other flag was pitch-black with a moon embroidered onto its surface, giving off a faint glow that was more subtle and profound.

The two of them cast a string of incantation seals into the pair of flags, and they instantly transformed into a pair of massive balls of light. A sun was hovering within one of the balls of light, and a moon in the other, both of which were giving off immense auras.

The two balls of light were giving off a thunderous rumbling sound as they hurtled toward the golden puppet from either side.

Chapter 494: Slain

Right at this moment, the golden puppet abruptly turned around to look at its assailants with a wooden expression, and bright golden light emerged over its body alongside a series of golden lightning veins.

A loud crackling sound rang out as thick arcs of golden lightning emerged. There were countless lightning runes dancing within the arcs of lightning, and they were giving formidable law power fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, the golden puppet raised an arm before throwing a forceful punch, and a thick bolt of golden lightning erupted forth before striking the gray jade scepter.

A resounding boom rang out as the jade scepter shuddered violently, then tumbled back through the air end over end. The dense gray mist that it was emitting was torn apart by the golden lightning, and the spiritual light that it was giving off was also a little scattered, indicating that its spiritual nature had been harmed.

The golden puppet also shuddered violently, and only after stumbling back a few steps did it manage to steady itself. At the same time, the golden lightning surging over its body had also dimmed significantly.

The two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals were ecstatic to see this, and the two giant balls of light instantly transformed into two massive hands at their behest, one black and one white, before grabbing toward the golden puppet.

Right at this moment, two gray humanoid figures suddenly joined the golden puppet in a wraith-like manner.

As it turned out, two of the gray statues standing on either side of the palace had suddenly sprung to life, and yellow spirit patterns had appeared over the entirety of their bodies.

The two statues were giving off radiant yellow light that was interspersed with bursts of tremendous law power fluctuations, and each of them was wielding a pair of yellow sabers, which they slashed through the air.

Two pairs of giant yellow saber projections were sent flying through the air, crossing over one another to form a pair of huge crosses.

Serrated edges appeared on the edges of the saber projections, giving them a menacing appearance, and they were giving off incredibly heavy law power fluctuations that caused all of the space in their wake to twist and warp violently.

Two resounding booms rang out as the pair of giant hands were destroyed, reverting back into a pair of large flags that were sent flying back through the air.

Meanwhile, the two gray statues remained completely still like a pair of immovable mountains.

Qi Tianxiao's trio was stunned to see this, as were Han Li and the others.

Right at this moment, all of the gray statues on either side of the palace shot forth at once, landing at the center of the palace. There were somewhere between 40 to 50 of them in total, and they instantly surrounded Qi Tianxiao's trio.

"Trespassers must be killed!" the statues roared in unison in a ghastly voice that resembled the sound of metal grating on metal.

Powerful soundwaves swept through the air in all directions, causing the entire palace to buzz and tremble.

The soundwaves converged from all directions, and ripples that were visible even to the naked eye appeared in the air, inundating Qi Tianxiao's trio.

The three of them immediately began to tremble uncontrollably as painful looks appeared on their faces.

Right at this moment, bright yellow light began to radiate from the dozens of gray statues, and the yellow light quickly connected together to form a giant yellow go board projection around the three Golden Immortals in the blink of an eye.

Every single line on the go board projection was giving off extremely heavy law power fluctuations, and these fluctuations were compounding upon one another.

Encompassed within the go board projection, Qi Tianxiao's trio instantly felt as if there were countless mountains weighing down upon them, and even with their Golden Immortal Stage powers, they were rendered completely immobilized.

After successfully trapping the trio, the dozens of puppets slashed their blades through the air at once, unleashing a storm of saber and sword projections.

At the same time, all of the golden patterns on the ground abruptly lit up, releasing bursts of white flames that instantly inundated the entire go board projection, transforming it into a sea of flames.

Waves of scorching heat spread in all directions, causing the nearby space to shimmer and warp, and even Han Li and the others in the distance were feeling the intense heat.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Han Li and the others were astonished by what they were seeing, but there was also no lack of schadenfreude in their expressions.

"Thank heavens you didn't free me, Uncle. It's much safer here than over there," Jin Tong said with a hint of lingering fear in its voice.

Han Li offered no response, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Meanwhile, Feng Tiandu's expression had darkened significantly, and he wanted to assist his allies, but there was no way that he could leave after unleashing this cage of chains.

Looking at the sea of flames before him, a hint of remorse welled up in his heart.

If he had known that there were such formidable restrictions and puppets here, then he would've allowed Luo Qinghai and the others to test the waters first.

However, thanks to his greed, he had turned everyone against him, and there was no longer any possibility for a peaceful resolution. Furthermore, they had to deal with these restrictions and puppets as well, and they were well and truly stuck between a rock and a hard place.

Right at this moment, one part of the sea of fire rippled slightly, and a streak of gray light shot out before landing near the palace gates to reveal Qi Tianxiao.

At this moment, his entire body was charred black, and most of his hair had also been incinerated. His complexion was extremely pale, and there was blood trailing down from the corners of his lips, giving him a very sorry appearance.

After landing on the ground, Qi Tianxiao stumbled a few steps before steadying himself, and there was a hint of alarm and horror in his eyes.

Meanwhile, the sea of white flames began to rapidly recede, and before long, it had entirely vanished into the ground.

Shortly thereafter, the two large flags from earlier drifted down onto the ground, but the spiritual light emanating from them had completely faded, indicating that they had also been severely damaged.

As for the other two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals, they were nowhere to be seen, and it was clear that their bodies, nascent souls, and even their storage treasures had been incinerated into nothingness by the white flames, while only the pair of resilient immortal treasures remained.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened even further upon seeing this.

Han Li and the others were also all astonished by the power of these white flames.

Before long, the yellow light radiating from the dozens of gray statues also faded, as did the yellow go board projection.

The gray statues then turned and made their way back to their original spots before standing still again, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

Meanwhile, the golden puppet continued to step forward, and it quickly arrived in front of the golden chair, following which the silver pill flew out of its grasp and into the living corpse's mouth.

Everyone could only watch as the pill rolled down into the living corpse's stomach, following which a layer of gentle green light quickly appeared over its body.

A few seconds later, the green light faded, and the living corpse's aura was slightly elevated.

Han Li and the others were all very surprised to see this.

Right at this moment, another one of the dragons engraved onto the pill cauldron opened its mouth to release a burst of five-colored light.

Almost at the exact same moment, yet another dragon did the exact same thing, and a vast golden cloud quickly took shape in the sky above the palace again, then transformed into a swirling golden vortex.

A terrifying aura that was even more formidable than that of the previous pill tribulation erupted out of the golden vortex, and everyone was immediately struck by a sense of asphyxiation, as if there were a huge rock weighing down onto each of their chests.

The immense pressure was weighing down upon the entirety of Feng Tiandu's spirit domain, so he was the one who was most heavily impacted. He felt as if he had been dealt a heavy blow to the chest, and his complexion instantly paled, while his spirit domain also began to ripple.

Luo Qinghai immediately pounced on this opportunity as radiant blue light emerged over his entire body, forming countless blue waves that swept toward the black spirit domain with tremendous power.

An opening was blasted into the spirit domain, and a speck of blue light appeared beside Luo Qinghai's hand before shooting out of the opening like lightning, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Feng Tiandu immediately swung around and swept both sleeves through the air, releasing two balls of black light with countless runes flashing within them.

The two balls of black light quickly fused into the spirit domain, instantly stabilizing it, while the opening that had been created by Luo Qinghai was mended.

At the same time, bursts of black light converged to suppress the blue light around Luo Qinghai once again.

A cold sneer appeared on Luo Qinghai's face as he began making a string of hand seals while chanting an incantation, and the blue light around his body formed a light barrier with countless wave projections flashing over its surface.

"What did you do just now, Luo Qinghai?" Feng Tiandu asked in a cold voice.

Luo Qinghai offered no response as he continued to make more hand seals, and the blue light barrier around him grew brighter and brighter.

It was unable to keep out the Origin Separation Law Chains, but all of the surrounding black light was kept at bay.

A cold look flashed through Feng Tiandu's eyes, but before he had a chance to do anything, two bursts of water-droplet-like silver light emerged from within the golden vortex.

Arcs of lightning were flashing incessantly over the burst of silver light, which then descended to fall upon the roof of the golden palace.

A vast expanse of blinding silver light instantly enveloped the entire golden palace, and all of the runes that riddled the palace instantly lit up once again, releasing dazzling golden radiance to keep the silver light at bay.

The combination of silver and golden radiance was so bright that everyone was temporarily blinded.

......

Meanwhile, the entrance of the stone gates at the center of the valley suddenly flashed momentarily, following which a streak of blue light flew out from within before shattering to form a blue light screen.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this as they rose to their feet.

The blue screen of light rippled momentarily, following which a clear image appeared on its surface, depicting the scene during which the two Dawn Fall Sect Golden Immortals had flown into the palace.

"Those bastards! They said they were going to explore the mountain range, but they actually snuck into the palace!"

"The Dawn Fall Sect has broken the agreement!"

Everyone in the valley was furious, and they collectively turned to the only remaining Dawn Fall Sect cultivator present, an elderly Golden Immortal with a rotund frame.

The elderly man seemed to have been prepared for this eventuality, and he immediately began spinning like a top, then fled into the distance as a ball of azure light.

Everyone looked on with tightly furrowed brows, but no one set off to pursue him. Moments later, everyone turned their attention back to the entrance before them, then began to exchange glances with one another.

Chapter 495: Time to Strike

"Everyone, the Dawn Fall Sect has broken the agreement, so we should all disregard it as well!" the Golden Immortal of the Blaze Dragon Dao declared, then immediately shot forth through the air as if he were worried that the Vast Flow Palace cultivators would try and intercept him, vanishing into the stone gates in the blink of an eye.

Yun Ni took a glance at the four Vast Flow Palace cultivators, then also flew through the stone gates as a streak of silver light.

The Vast Flow Palace cultivators made no attempt to stop them.

With that, the only ones still left outside were the Vast Flow Palace cultivators, and they exchanged a glance with one another, then made a series of hand seals to cast a string of incantation seals into the blue light screen.

At the same time that the blue light screen emerged, they had received a secret message from Luo Qinghai through voice transmission.

The light screen rippled slightly, then rapidly shrank down into a blue door of light.

"Keep guarding the entrance," the fair-skinned scholar instructed as he turned to the True Immortals of the Vast Flow Palace.

The True Immortals instantly nodded in response, following which the four Golden Immortals flew into the blue door of light in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the door of light began to ripple before quickly beginning to fade away.

Right at this moment, Yun Ni appeared out of thin air amid a flash of white light, much to the surprise of the Vast Flow Palace True Immortals.

Yun Ni paid no heed to them at all as she also flew into the door of blue light, just in time before it completely faded out of existence, leaving the Vast Flow Palace True Immortals to stare at each other with bewildered expressions.

......

Inside the palace, the vast expanse of dazzling silver light suddenly flashed momentarily before receding like the tide.

All of the golden light within the palace faded away as well, and yet another pill tribulation was successfully negotiated.

Two of the dragon's engraved onto the pill cauldron opened their mouths, and a pair of High Zenith Pills shot out, filling the entire palace with a rich medicinal aroma once again.

A hint of greed flashed through Feng Tiandu's eyes at the sight of the two pills.

Right at this moment, two more golden puppets popped up, seemingly out of nowhere, then grabbed the pair of High Zenith Pills before making their way toward the golden chair once again.

"Are you alright, Junior Martial Brother?" Feng Tiandu asked through voice transmission.

Qi Tianxiao took a deep breath, then replied, "I had to use a secret technique to escape from that sea of fire, so I'm feeling a little drained, but I managed to escape serious injury."

"At this point, I definitely won't settle for leaving this place empty-handed, and I'm sure the same goes for you as well. Luo Qinghai most likely did something just now to contact all of the Golden Immortals outside, and once those people get in here, we'll be in an even worse situation, so we must claim High Zenith Pill now!" Feng Tiandu declared in a cold voice.

"But the restrictions and those statues are far too powerful for me to contend with on my own," Qi Tianxiao said with slightly furrowed brows.

"That's fine. From my observations, it seems like while those gray statues are very formidable, they don't appear to be very intelligent or adaptable. Here's the plan: I'll find a way to distract them, and you take the pills while they're distracted!" Feng Tiandu said.

"Alright, I'll give it another shot," Qi Tianxiao replied after a brief hesitation.

While the two of them were communicating with one another through voice transmission, Han Li took a glance at the other people around him.

The situation in the palace seemed to be worsening by the second. He was confident that he would be able to free himself from these Origin Separation Law Chains, but it would take some time to do so, and continuing to allow himself to be trapped like this didn't seem to be a good idea.

Right as Han Li was hesitating about whether this was the right time to break free from the Origin Separation Law Chains, Feng Tiandu suddenly raised both hands to cast a pair of incantation seals into two of the black chains, namely the ones wrapped around Daoist Hu Yan and Ouyang Kuishan.

The two chains instantly began to glow brightly as countless black runes surged out of them, then converged to form a blurry black figure that was around half a foot tall.

That's a domain spirit!

As soon as the domain spirit took shape, it immediately flew into the bodies of Daoist Hu Yan and Ouyang Kuishan in a flash.

A series of black patterns instantly began to spread rapidly over their bodies, and their expressions changed drastically as they channeled their law powers to resist the invasive force with all their might, but to no avail.

"Feng Tiandu! What did you do?"

In the blink of an eye, the entirety of their bodies were covered in black patterns, and their auras already took on a drastic change.

Immediately thereafter, the two of them were freed from the cage of chains and landed on the ground, but there was still a black chain connected to each of their dantians.

"Go!" Feng Tiandu instructed, and the two of them immediately flew toward the pill cauldron.

A hint of elation appeared on Qi Tianxiao's face upon seeing this, and he quickly took a regenerative pill as a gray cloud began to emerge out of his body.

Han Li immediately understood Feng Tiandu's intentions, and a cold look appeared on his face.

He was quite close with Daoist Hu Yan to begin with, and the latter had just given him the next three levels of the Mantra Treasured Axis, so he definitely couldn't just watch him fall to his demise.

With that in mind, golden light flashed over his body, yet right as he was about to do something, a blue door of light suddenly appeared at the entrance of the palace.

The four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals flew out from within, and they were clearly rather taken aback by the sight that they were greeted by.

Immediately thereafter, Yun Ni flew out of the door of light as well, and the surprise on the faces of the four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals became even more pronounced at the sight of her.

As soon as Yun Ni appeared in the golden palace, she immediately spotted Daoist Hu Yan, and she conjured up a giant white snow lotus flower projection around herself, while a strange flying sword that resembled a lotus flower stem appeared in her hand.

The lotus flower projection flew through the air, carrying her with it as she shot forth toward Daoist Hu Yan as quickly as she could.

In this instant, it was as if she could see nothing but Daoist Hu Yan, and all of the surrounding perils were completely disregarded.

"What a loyal woman you are!" Feng Tiandu remarked with a cold sneer.

At the same time, two black chains shot out of the black light barrier up above, then crossed over one another in mid-air before hurtling directly toward Yun Ni.

"Look out!" Daoist Hu Yan hurriedly called out in an alarmed voice.

However, Yun Ni was desperate to save him, and even though she knew that an attack was descending upon her from above, she still refused to take evasive measures, instead accelerating even further on a straight-line trajectory toward Daoist Hu Yan.

However, she was situated in Feng Tiandu's spirit domain, and there was no way that he would allow her to do as she pleased.

Before she even had a chance to get close to Daoist Hu Yan, two more chains came flying at her from either side, and in conjunction with the pair of chains shooting down from above, all avenues for retreat and evasion were completely cut off.

Right at this moment, a burst of bright golden light suddenly lit up on Han Li's chest.

Immediately thereafter, the burst of golden light flickered slightly like a flame, then instantly transformed into a golden light barrier that encompassed the entire palace.

Countless golden ripples appeared in the air above, and they were giving off a burst of tremendous law power fluctuations.

In the instant that the chains converging toward Yun Ni came into contact with these golden ripples, they were instantly slowed down significantly.

An incredulous look flashed through Yun Ni's eyes as she slipped through the gaps between the chains with ease, then arrived by Daoist Hu Yan's side.

"Nice one, kid!" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed as he turned to take a glance back at Han Li.

At this moment, they were the only two people in this entire palace who weren't affected by the golden spirit domain, while everyone else, including Feng Tiandu and Luo Qinghai, could feel a burst of pronounced time law powers hanging in the air.

Everyone was greatly alarmed by this abrupt turn of events, and a furious look appeared on Feng Tiandu's face.

At the same time, he pointed a finger directly at Han Li, and a black chain shot out of his sleeve, then hurtled toward Han Li's dantian at an incredible speed.

"You want to seal my nascent soul away again? Shouldn't you know better than to try the same trick twice?" Han Li chuckled with a derisive sneer on his face.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a streak of azure light abruptly appeared in front of him. It was an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, and it swept directly toward the black chain around Han Li's body.

Arcs of golden lightning flashed over the sword's surface, further enhancing its already peerlessly sharp aura as it crashed into the black chain with a loud clang.

The chain was instantly snapped, then disintegrated into a plume of black mist that fused back into the black spirit domain.

"Impossible!"

Feng Tiandu's expression changed drastically as he stared intently at the sword in Han Li's hand, and he was struggling to believe that just a single strike from this sword was able to sever his Origin Separation Law Chain.

Unbeknownst to him, this was actually three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords fused as one, and that was the maximum number that Han Li could control at once. At this moment, the boundless sword qi emanating from the combined sword was far more formidable than the aura of any average immortal treasure.

This seemed like quite a lengthy process, but in reality, all of it had taken place in an instant.

After the chain around Han Li's body was snapped, the other black chain was already no more than an inch away from his lower abdomen, but all of a sudden, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

As it turned out, in the same instant that he had freed himself from that chain, he had also unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability to drastically enhance his own speed. After evading the oncoming chain, he arrived by Jin Tong's side in a flash, then snapped the chain around her body as well with another slash of his sword.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and if it weren't for the fact that he had to remain on the spot to control everyone else, he would've immediately stormed at Han Li to strike him down.

A complex look had also appeared on Luo Qinghai's face upon seeing this, and at this moment, the Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals that he had summoned into the palace were also moving around in a very slow and sluggish fashion under the effects of Han Li's spirit domain.

Chapter 496: Chaotic Battle

After being freed from the black chain, Jin Tong took a moment to stretch out her limbs as she said, "About time, Uncle! What do you need me to do? I'm itching for a fight!"

"Ignore him for now, focus on getting me a High Zenith Pill first," Han Li hurriedly instructed.

At this moment, everyone else was still trapped in Feng Tiandu's cage of chains, so this was the perfect opportunity for him to secure a High Zenith Pill.

Jin Tong looked back and forth between Feng Tiandu and the pill cauldron for a moment, clearly feeling a little conflicted.

In the end, she conceded, "Fine. I've been dying to sink my teeth into that pill cauldron this entire time, so I guess I'll just eat that first..."

Everyone present was astonished to hear this.

Everyone had seen how she had eaten Xiao Jinhan's treasures and nascent souls, so they knew that she wasn't bluffing, and if she were to eat the cauldron now, then all of the remaining pills inside would be ruined!

"No! Don't do that!" Luo Qinghai hurriedly yelled in a panicked voice.

At the same time, the blue light around his body reared up in powerful blue waves, and it seemed that the chain wrapped around his body was about to burst apart at any moment.

Feng Tiandu immediately refocused his efforts on bolstering his chains, making sure to keep Luo Qinghai firmly under control. After all, out of all of the people in this palace, Luo Qinghai was the one that he was most wary of.

Feng Tiandu and Luo Qinghai possessed the most advanced cultivation bases among all of the Golden Immortals present, so even though they were also affected by Han Li's time spirit domain, the impact that it had on them was far less significant.

Han Li was also feeling quite exasperated as he hurriedly called out, "There are still pills that are yet to be formed inside that cauldron, so you can't eat it!"

"I can't do this, I can't do that! What can I do? It's so annoying!" Jin Tong grumbled to herself, and it was unclear whether she was going to follow Han Li's instruction as she flew directly toward the sea of fire.

A cold sneer appeared on Qi Tianxiao's face upon seeing this, and he remained still on the spot as he observed Jin Tong from afar, making no effort to go after her.

Given the childish nature that she had displayed, Qi Tianxiao presumed that she had no idea just how formidable that sea of fire was. Once she flew into it, she would undoubtedly suffer severe burns, and once that happened, he would swoop in and restrain her before slowly taming her into his spirit pet over time.

However, to his surprise, Han Li also set off after her, then appeared in front of her in a flash.

He then made a strange hand seal, and a burst of silver flames emerged over the palms of his hands as he thrust them into the sea of fire.

As soon as his hands came into contact with the edge of the sea of fire, his brows instantly furrowed tightly as an agonized look appeared on his face.

These flames were far more formidable than he had anticipated.

He spread his hands apart, and the silver flame instantly formed a ring-shaped fiery barrier that parted the surrounding flames to open up a circular hole that was slowly expanding.

However, as he did this, his time spirit domain was clearly impacted, and everyone inside it was freed up a little.

"Hurry up! I can't keep this up for long..."

Han Li's hands had already become bright red, and a large section of his sleeves had also been incinerated into ashes as he persevered with tightly gritted teeth.

Jin Tong immediately spread her wings and flew toward the hole, but right at this moment, a cloud of dense gray mist suddenly surged toward her from the side, then appeared in front of her before taking on the form of Qi Tianxiao.

"Piss off!" Jin Tong roared, but Qi Tianxiao refused to budge, releasing plumes of gray mist out of his sleeves, and the mist instantly transformed into seven or eight giant gray pythons that pounced at Jin Tong.

Jin Tong was infuriated and immediately began attacking the gray pythons.

Meanwhile, Han Li was struggling to hold on, and his hands had become virtually transparent, while his time spirit domain was also becoming thinner and thinner.

"Don't worry about me, go and secure the High Zenith Pill!" Luo Qinghai hurriedly yelled, and the four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals immediately stopped in their tracks, then channeled their law powers to oppose Han Li's time spirit domain as they rushed toward the pill cauldron.

Luo Qinghai took a glance in that direction, then raised a question to Nan Kemeng through voice transmission. "Have you found a way to break the restriction?"

Nan Kemeng shook his head in response. "I've managed to spot a few weak points, but I haven't been able to think of a way to break the restriction yet."

"That's fine, just tell those four the weak points that you've spotted so they at least have some targets," Luo Qinghai replied.

Even though the conversation was taking place through voice transmission, Feng Tiandu could see that they were plotting something, and he mused, "Looks like this disciple of yours has some interesting abilities, Grand Palace Master Luo. No wonder you bring him with you everywhere you go."

He made a hand seal as he spoke, and a black chain shot out of his robes before instantly piercing into Nan Kemeng's dantian.

The nascent soul inside was immediately sealed away by an Origin Separation Law Chain, while the light in his eyes instantly faded.

"Meng'er!" Luo Qinghai called out as his expression changed drastically.

At the same time, the blue light radiating from his body became even brighter, and they crashed against the Origin Separation Law Chain around him like an endless barrage of waves.

Feng Tiandu's expression remained unchanged as he injected more immortal spiritual power into his chains to suppress Luo Qinghai, but internally, he was feeling very frustrated.

Never had he imagined the restrictions around the pill cauldron would be this formidable, to the point that two of his sect's Golden Immortals had met their demise here without even being able to put up a fight. As a result, the overall power of the Dawn Fall Sect was significantly diminished, and it was now the Vast Flow Palace that had the upper hand.

On top of that, Han Li was also proving to be very troublesome, so there was a good chance that his plans could be completely foiled here.

Before he had a chance to fully suppress Luo Qinghai, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from the chain that was connected to Daoist Hu Yan's body.

Yun Ni's lotus branch fire sword had been inserted into the chain no more than a foot away from Daoist Hu Yan's lower abdomen, and the pink floral projection it abruptly bloomed before exploding, instantly snapping the black chain.

At the same time, Yun Ni drifted down from above with blood trickling down from the corner of her lips as she stumbled backward.

Daoist Hu Yan immediately arrived by her side to catch her, and there was a pained look in his eyes as he yelled, "What are you doing? Don't be so reckless!"

"I'm fine as long as you're alright," Yun Ni said in a gentle voice as she wiped the blood from the corner of her lips.

Daoist Hu Yan's brows were tightly furrowed, and he wanted to say something more, but she shook her head to stop him.

Not far away from them, Ouyang Kuishan was still involuntarily charging toward the sea of fire, but his gaze had been fixed on Daoist Hu Yan this entire time with a hint of envy and sorrow in his eyes.

Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni exchanged a glance with one another, following which the two of them arrived on either side of Ouyang Kuishan in a flash.

With a flick of her wrist, Yun Ni sent a red streamer flying through the air, and it wrapped itself tightly around Ouyang Kuishan to lock him firmly into place.

At the same time, Daoist Hu Yan made a grabbing motion, and a fiery flying sword appeared in his grasp.

He raised the sword up high before slashing it down upon the black chain that was protruding out of Ouyang Kuishan's dantian, and a thin crimson line instantly appeared on the chain before it was split into two.

"You have my thanks."

Ouyang Kuishan gave the two of them a grateful nod as the black patterns all over his body slowly faded.

Feng Tiandu's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and he made a beckoning motion with one hand, upon which the two Origin Separation Law Chains that had been severed by Han Li returned to his grasp.

"Finally, I've recovered the full set," Feng Tiandu murmured to himself as he stroked the pair of chains.

He then raised a hand, and the two chains instantly reared up like a pair of spirit snakes, then crawled up into his sleeve before trailing down onto the ground like his other chains.

Feng Tiandu took a glance down at the chains beneath him, following which he raised his head and began to cackle in a gravelly voice.

He reached out with both hands, and blood began to gather between his fingers before flowing down onto the black chains beneath him.

A burst of crimson light spread over the chains, and a burst of urgent clattering suddenly rang out as countless dark red chains swept over the ground like an enormous mass of spirit snakes.

Luo Qinghai and the others, who were still trapped in the cage of chains, were instantly wrapped up in layers upon layers of additional chains, encasing each of them in a dark red cocoon.

Daoist Hu Yan immediately turned his sword upside-down upon seeing this, then pierced the tip of the sword into the ground.

A crimson light barrier instantly spread from the tip of his sword, and it was giving off waves of scorching heat that forced back the oncoming chains.

Meanwhile, each of the four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals was holding a jade badge, all of which were radiating dazzling blue light, forming a square crystal house that also kept the chains at bay.

"What do we do?" one of the Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals, an elderly man, asked as he took a hesitant glance in Luo Qinghai's direction.

"The palace master told us to prioritize securing the pills, so we'll just have to follow his instruction," the fair-skinned scholar replied.

With that, the four Golden Immortals began to discuss ways to ward off the sea of fire to secure the High Zenith PIlls within.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong felt like the palace was too confined a space for her to fight Qi Tianxiao to her heart's content, so the two of them had taken their battle outside of the palace.

With the mass of dark red chains rapidly closing in on him, Han Li could only heave a faint sigh as he withdrew his hands, and with that, the opening in the sea of fire slowly sealed itself again.

Immediately thereafter, he flew over to Daoist Hu Yan's trio, then summoned a pair of Immortal Origin Stones, which he was using to replenish his immortal spiritual power. At the same time, he had also already withdrawn his time spirit domain.

Simultaneously maintaining his spirit domain, using three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, and releasing his Flame of Essence had been extremely taxing on his immortal spiritual power.

"Now that the Gold Devouring Immortal is gone, it's time for us to settle the score," Feng Tiandu said as he cast his gaze toward Han Li with burning fury in his eyes.

As he was speaking, he began to drift toward Han Li and the others, while his lower body was concealed within the sea of hains down below.

Chapter 497: Infiltration

"Your time law powers confirms it... You were the one who killed my disciples, weren't you?" Feng Tiandu asked in a cold voice as he glowered intently at Han Li.

"That's right," Han Li replied in a calm manner.

"Don't think that you have a right to get cocky just because you've developed a half-assed mastery over the laws of time! I'll send you to your grave right here and now!" Feng Tiandu threatened in a dark voice.

"You killed two of his disciples? Well done! I'll have to treat you to a cup of wine for that alone!" Daoist Hu Yan jibed.

"I want an entire flagon," Han Li negotiated with a smile.

"Deal!" Daoist Hu Yan immediately chuckled as he tightened his grip around his longsword.

Right at this moment, Ouyang Kuishan took a glance at the pill cauldron, then exclaimed in an urgent voice, "We have to hurry! Those two pills are about to be fed to that living corpse!"

Daoist Hu Yan was just about to respond when Han Li said, "Focus on breaking the restriction and securing the pills. In the meantime, I'll show Grand Elder Feng here just how cocky I can get with my half-assed mastery over the laws of time!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he shot out of Daoist Hu Yan's fiery spirit domain, charging toward Feng Tiandu alone.

Yun Ni and Ouyang Kuishan were both quite startled by this, and they turned to Daoist Hu Yan with surprised expressions.

"There's no need to worry about him, let's go secure the pills," Daoist Hu Yan said with a smile.

After that, the three of them really did abandon Han Li to face Feng Tiandu on his own, while they began to devise a plan to break the fiery restriction.

However, what everyone failed to notice wast that one of the cocoons of chains not far away from the palace gates had suddenly toppled over, and the pile of dark red chains had clattered down onto the ground to reveal that the person who was supposed to be trapped inside was nowhere to be seen.

Almost at the exact same moment, a figure silently emerged above the undulating sea of chains to the right of the palace, then rushed toward a corner of the palace, and it was none other than that elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race.

At this point, her golden cane had already disappeared, and it was replaced in her grasp by a palm-sized yellow badge that had a very irregular shape.

The badge was riddled with layers upon layers of strange runes, which were giving off peculiar law power fluctuations.

There was a layer of dark red light over her body, and she was traveling at an extraordinary speed, leaving a crimson shadow in her wake. Before anyone else had a chance to react, she had already arrived in front of the sea of fire.

Once there, she immediately tossed the yellow badge forward, and it vanished into the sea of fire in the blink of an eye.

As soon as the badge entered the flames, it immediately melted away as if it were made from wax, and a series of runes flew out of it before fusing into the surrounding flames.

On the other side of the palace, a string of loud clangs rang out as a barrage of dark red chains shot through the air like crimson spears, raining down upon Han Li with tremendous force.

Han Li was holding his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in one hand, while silver light surged over his body, and he was whizzing through the air in a wraith-like fashion, evading the barrage of dark red chains with ease.

Feng Tiandu was becoming more and more frustrated by the second, and he began charging forward himself while making a string of hand seals, sending countless black chains shooting toward Han Li from all directions out of his black spirit domain.

At the same time, he made a beckoning motion with one hand, and a dark red chain abruptly sprang up from beneath Han Li's feet like a spitting viper, and its sharp tip was giving off a cold flame as it pierced toward his ankle.

Han Li had already anticipated such an attack, and he slashed his longsword downward, releasing a bolt of golden lightning that struck the dark red chain in the blink of an eye.

The bolt of lightning shot through the chain as an electric current, rapidly spreading through all of the chains in a large area to form a sea of golden lightning.

As soon as Feng Tiandu flew into the sea of lightning, he felt as if he had jumped into a pot of scalding oil, and he involuntarily let loose an agonized howl.

Everyone's attention was instantly drawn to him upon hearing this, and even the elderly woman from the Southern Dawn Race had temporarily diverted her gaze away from the sea of fire.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through her eyes as she took a glance at Han Li, following which she returned her gaze to the sea of fire before her.

Right at this moment, the flames that the yellow badge had just melted into suddenly began to contract drastically, forming a series of tiny crimson flames.

The elderly woman's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and she shot through the opening in a flash.

She was immediately followed by the four Vast Flow Palace Golden Immortals, who attempted to pass through the opening after her, but as soon as they got close, the opening was abruptly sealed again, and the flames almost swallowed up the Golden Immortal that was leading the way out of the four.

"What is that badge? It seemed to have contained some type of law powers," Yun Ni mused with a puzzled expression.

"Could it be the laws of fire?" Ouyang Kuishan speculated with furrowed brows.

"No. I don't know what it is, but I can sense that it's not the laws of fire. In any case, let's focus on breaking this restriction," Daoist Hu Yan replied with a shake of his head.

Meanwhile, the elderly woman had only just charged into the sea of fire when she was confronted by a pair of white humanoid figures.

The yellow spirit patterns on their bodies were glowing brightly, and each of them was holding a standard yellow saber as they rushed at her from the left and the right.

Layers of ripples were spreading through the surrounding space, and a burst of extremely heavy law power fluctuations were converging from both directions, as if there were a pair of mountain faces closing in on the elderly woman.

The elderly woman could feel the air constrict around her, and right at this moment, a burst of dark red light shot out of her body, then instantly swelled to form a spirit domain that was over 100 feet in radius, just large enough to encompass the two gray puppets.

Immediately thereafter, a series of thin dark red threads emerged in the space within the spirit domain, and they shot forth toward all of the gray puppets' joints.

The dark red threads were able to pierce through the bodies of the seemingly indestructible puppets with ease, making them appear like a pair of wooden puppets on strings.

However, what was rather strange was that their movements weren't affected at all, and they continued to charge at the elderly woman, compressing the air around her to such an extent that her robes were tightly pressed against her body.

The elderly woman's eyes narrowed slightly, and she crossed her hands over, upon which two of the thin threads that had pierced into the gray puppets abruptly stretched taut, yanking their heads backward.

"There it is," she murmured to herself as she made a rapid string of hand seals, and the pair of gray puppets instantly stiffened as bursts of yellow light lit up on the backs of their necks, flowing incessantly along the pair of dark red threads before dissipating into the air.

As the yellow light faded, so did the yellow spirit patterns on the puppets' bodies, and by the time the yellow light was completely gone, the pressure weighing down upon the elderly woman was also completely lifted.

Without their earth law powers, the two gray puppets could no longer pose any impediment to the elderly woman, and she passed between them in a flash, charging directly at the pill cauldron behind them.

The two golden puppets who were carrying the High Zenith Pills to the living corpse seemed to have sensed her approach, and they both swung around at once before each throwing an almighty punch.

Countless lightning runes surged over their fists, and a golden vortex took shape at the center, releasing a burst of peculiar suction force that acted upon the elderly woman's body.

At the same time, the gray stone statues standing on either side of the palace began to move as yellow light emerged over their bodies, while the giant yellow go board projection was also beginning to take shape.

"What a fool," the elderly Golden Immortal from the Vast Flow Palace scoffed with a cold sneer on his face.

However, as soon as his voice trailed off, he felt a blur flash past his eyes, immediately following which the elderly woman appeared at the foot of the raised platform that held the large golden chair, having passed through between the pair of golden puppets in the blink of an eye.

The golden vortex between them was already nowhere to be seen, and there were only some thin arcs of golden lightning flashing through the air, but they no longer held any degree of significant power.

As for the yellow go board projection, it didn't even have a chance to activate before she was already past it.

Everyone was astonished to see this, and their attention was instantly drawn to the elderly woman.

Meanwhile, Feng Tiandu had already emerged from Han Li's sea of golden lightning, and he seemed to have realized that Han Li was not an opponent to be taken lightly, so he was taking a more patient approach, temporarily engaging in a standoff against Han Li.

Both of them also had their attention drawn to what was happening on the other side of the palace, and to their befuddlement, they noticed that two golden puppets were still each holding a High Zenith Pill.

For some reason, the elderly woman hadn't taken those pills as she was passing by the puppets.

Instead, she strode directly onto the stone platform, then flipped a hand over to produce a black pill that was giving off hints of law power fluctuations.

That's an Origin Void Pill!

Han Li was immediately able to identify the pill as none other than the Origin Void Pill that he had personally refined, and he cast his gaze toward the elderly woman with slightly furrowed brows.

"What are you doing?" Feng Tiandu yelled as his expression changed drastically.

The elderly woman turned around to take a glance at everyone, following which a peculiar smile appeared on her face, and she pinched the living corpse's chin between her fingers, then tilted its head back before feeding it the Origin Void Pill.

The pill slid straight down into the living corpse's stomach, which the elderly woman observed it intently with anticipation in her eyes.

As for everyone else, they were all looking on in befuddlement.